{"question": "The secretaries introduced the judges .", "answer": "The judges introduced the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The doctor saw the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes saw the doctor ."}
{"question": "The judge encouraged the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete encouraged the judge ."}
{"question": "The actor recommended the managers .", "answer": "The managers recommended the actor ."}
{"question": "The actor recognized the professors .", "answer": "The professors recognized the actor ."}
{"question": "The senator believed the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary believed the senator ."}
{"question": "The presidents contacted the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes contacted the presidents ."}
{"question": "The judges supported the actors .", "answer": "The actors supported the judges ."}
{"question": "The lawyers advised the authors .", "answer": "The authors advised the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The banker introduced the authors .", "answer": "The authors introduced the banker ."}
{"question": "The judge called the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers called the judge ."}
{"question": "The lawyer helped the judges .", "answer": "The judges helped the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The actor avoided the authors .", "answer": "The authors avoided the actor ."}
{"question": "The scientist admired the actors .", "answer": "The actors admired the scientist ."}
{"question": "The secretary stopped the manager .", "answer": "The manager stopped the secretary ."}
{"question": "The tourists saw the authors .", "answer": "The authors saw the tourists ."}
{"question": "The tourist introduced the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete introduced the tourist ."}
{"question": "The authors mentioned the banker .", "answer": "The banker mentioned the authors ."}
{"question": "The tourists recommended the managers .", "answer": "The managers recommended the tourists ."}
{"question": "The lawyers saw the managers .", "answer": "The managers saw the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The lawyers admired the judges .", "answer": "The judges admired the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The banker called the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes called the banker ."}
{"question": "The secretaries introduced the author .", "answer": "The author introduced the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The lawyer mentioned the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor mentioned the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The senator called the artist .", "answer": "The artist called the senator ."}
{"question": "The professors avoided the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes avoided the professors ."}
{"question": "The doctors introduced the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists introduced the doctors ."}
{"question": "The manager admired the senator .", "answer": "The senator admired the manager ."}
{"question": "The doctor supported the judges .", "answer": "The judges supported the doctor ."}
{"question": "The banker supported the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist supported the banker ."}
{"question": "The managers called the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist called the managers ."}
{"question": "The doctors supported the managers .", "answer": "The managers supported the doctors ."}
{"question": "The judges advised the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries advised the judges ."}
{"question": "The presidents introduced the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete introduced the presidents ."}
{"question": "The doctors stopped the artists .", "answer": "The artists stopped the doctors ."}
{"question": "The banker thanked the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete thanked the banker ."}
{"question": "The artist recommended the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete recommended the artist ."}
{"question": "The senator mentioned the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary mentioned the senator ."}
{"question": "The judge recommended the student .", "answer": "The student recommended the judge ."}
{"question": "The judges admired the professor .", "answer": "The professor admired the judges ."}
{"question": "The doctor stopped the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist stopped the doctor ."}
{"question": "The athletes advised the artists .", "answer": "The artists advised the athletes ."}
{"question": "The authors thanked the actor .", "answer": "The actor thanked the authors ."}
{"question": "The student recommended the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer recommended the student ."}
{"question": "The judges introduced the student .", "answer": "The student introduced the judges ."}
{"question": "The judges advised the actor .", "answer": "The actor advised the judges ."}
{"question": "The secretaries contacted the actor .", "answer": "The actor contacted the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The students avoided the managers .", "answer": "The managers avoided the students ."}
{"question": "The judge thanked the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer thanked the judge ."}
{"question": "The doctor admired the banker .", "answer": "The banker admired the doctor ."}
{"question": "The president avoided the manager .", "answer": "The manager avoided the president ."}
{"question": "The senator stopped the banker .", "answer": "The banker stopped the senator ."}
{"question": "The manager encouraged the judges .", "answer": "The judges encouraged the manager ."}
{"question": "The scientists supported the senators .", "answer": "The senators supported the scientists ."}
{"question": "The secretaries recommended the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor recommended the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The doctor saw the actor .", "answer": "The actor saw the doctor ."}
{"question": "The athletes introduced the professors .", "answer": "The professors introduced the athletes ."}
{"question": "The authors advised the managers .", "answer": "The managers advised the authors ."}
{"question": "The actor saw the banker .", "answer": "The banker saw the actor ."}
{"question": "The scientist saw the senator .", "answer": "The senator saw the scientist ."}
{"question": "The scientist contacted the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries contacted the scientist ."}
{"question": "The senator helped the artists .", "answer": "The artists helped the senator ."}
{"question": "The judge thanked the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes thanked the judge ."}
{"question": "The students stopped the artist .", "answer": "The artist stopped the students ."}
{"question": "The actor avoided the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary avoided the actor ."}
{"question": "The authors believed the artist .", "answer": "The artist believed the authors ."}
{"question": "The athlete recognized the senators .", "answer": "The senators recognized the athlete ."}
{"question": "The judges admired the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors admired the judges ."}
{"question": "The actor called the authors .", "answer": "The authors called the actor ."}
{"question": "The senator admired the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers admired the senator ."}
{"question": "The senators recognized the professor .", "answer": "The professor recognized the senators ."}
{"question": "The professors advised the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete advised the professors ."}
{"question": "The actors supported the professor .", "answer": "The professor supported the actors ."}
{"question": "The judges supported the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist supported the judges ."}
{"question": "The student saw the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor saw the student ."}
{"question": "The tourist believed the artists .", "answer": "The artists believed the tourist ."}
{"question": "The student encouraged the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers encouraged the student ."}
{"question": "The senators called the judge .", "answer": "The judge called the senators ."}
{"question": "The secretaries advised the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers advised the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The managers contacted the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete contacted the managers ."}
{"question": "The lawyers saw the student .", "answer": "The student saw the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The tourists stopped the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes stopped the tourists ."}
{"question": "The author helped the professor .", "answer": "The professor helped the author ."}
{"question": "The tourists called the senator .", "answer": "The senator called the tourists ."}
{"question": "The actor called the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents called the actor ."}
{"question": "The author saw the president .", "answer": "The president saw the author ."}
{"question": "The professor helped the senators .", "answer": "The senators helped the professor ."}
{"question": "The actor supported the banker .", "answer": "The banker supported the actor ."}
{"question": "The scientist saw the judge .", "answer": "The judge saw the scientist ."}
{"question": "The author admired the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers admired the author ."}
{"question": "The student avoided the author .", "answer": "The author avoided the student ."}
{"question": "The professor introduced the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers introduced the professor ."}
{"question": "The tourist helped the professors .", "answer": "The professors helped the tourist ."}
{"question": "The manager recommended the artist .", "answer": "The artist recommended the manager ."}
{"question": "The secretaries thanked the judge .", "answer": "The judge thanked the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The manager supported the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors supported the manager ."}
{"question": "The lawyer saw the artist .", "answer": "The artist saw the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The tourist thanked the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist thanked the tourist ."}
{"question": "The tourist advised the students .", "answer": "The students advised the tourist ."}
{"question": "The doctors introduced the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer introduced the doctors ."}
{"question": "The manager avoided the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer avoided the manager ."}
{"question": "The lawyer supported the judges .", "answer": "The judges supported the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The tourist advised the actor .", "answer": "The actor advised the tourist ."}
{"question": "The athlete stopped the banker .", "answer": "The banker stopped the athlete ."}
{"question": "The author contacted the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete contacted the author ."}
{"question": "The author mentioned the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary mentioned the author ."}
{"question": "The judges supported the author .", "answer": "The author supported the judges ."}
{"question": "The senator recommended the judge .", "answer": "The judge recommended the senator ."}
{"question": "The tourist encouraged the actors .", "answer": "The actors encouraged the tourist ."}
{"question": "The judges saw the artist .", "answer": "The artist saw the judges ."}
{"question": "The doctors encouraged the students .", "answer": "The students encouraged the doctors ."}
{"question": "The tourist helped the judges .", "answer": "The judges helped the tourist ."}
{"question": "The judge introduced the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete introduced the judge ."}
{"question": "The president recommended the banker .", "answer": "The banker recommended the president ."}
{"question": "The judges contacted the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary contacted the judges ."}
{"question": "The bankers helped the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers helped the bankers ."}
{"question": "The lawyers introduced the professor .", "answer": "The professor introduced the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The president stopped the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists stopped the president ."}
{"question": "The athlete saw the president .", "answer": "The president saw the athlete ."}
{"question": "The lawyer stopped the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists stopped the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The professor supported the judge .", "answer": "The judge supported the professor ."}
{"question": "The tourists introduced the author .", "answer": "The author introduced the tourists ."}
{"question": "The president advised the artist .", "answer": "The artist advised the president ."}
{"question": "The athlete believed the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists believed the athlete ."}
{"question": "The manager contacted the authors .", "answer": "The authors contacted the manager ."}
{"question": "The actor advised the artist .", "answer": "The artist advised the actor ."}
{"question": "The banker stopped the actor .", "answer": "The actor stopped the banker ."}
{"question": "The president recognized the senators .", "answer": "The senators recognized the president ."}
{"question": "The president thanked the professor .", "answer": "The professor thanked the president ."}
{"question": "The bankers recognized the professors .", "answer": "The professors recognized the bankers ."}
{"question": "The lawyer admired the banker .", "answer": "The banker admired the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The student mentioned the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor mentioned the student ."}
{"question": "The actor avoided the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor avoided the actor ."}
{"question": "The students supported the artists .", "answer": "The artists supported the students ."}
{"question": "The student encouraged the senators .", "answer": "The senators encouraged the student ."}
{"question": "The scientists called the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors called the scientists ."}
{"question": "The tourists believed the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor believed the tourists ."}
{"question": "The doctor recommended the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist recommended the doctor ."}
{"question": "The judges believed the managers .", "answer": "The managers believed the judges ."}
{"question": "The managers advised the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist advised the managers ."}
{"question": "The tourists helped the senators .", "answer": "The senators helped the tourists ."}
{"question": "The managers recognized the authors .", "answer": "The authors recognized the managers ."}
{"question": "The president helped the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists helped the president ."}
{"question": "The author recognized the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors recognized the author ."}
{"question": "The professor contacted the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers contacted the professor ."}
{"question": "The athletes saw the manager .", "answer": "The manager saw the athletes ."}
{"question": "The senator helped the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist helped the senator ."}
{"question": "The doctor mentioned the judges .", "answer": "The judges mentioned the doctor ."}
{"question": "The artist recommended the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes recommended the artist ."}
{"question": "The students encouraged the authors .", "answer": "The authors encouraged the students ."}
{"question": "The actors called the students .", "answer": "The students called the actors ."}
{"question": "The lawyer helped the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists helped the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The manager advised the artist .", "answer": "The artist advised the manager ."}
{"question": "The author recognized the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete recognized the author ."}
{"question": "The artist stopped the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes stopped the artist ."}
{"question": "The judges mentioned the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer mentioned the judges ."}
{"question": "The artists contacted the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer contacted the artists ."}
{"question": "The tourist helped the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists helped the tourist ."}
{"question": "The artist mentioned the professors .", "answer": "The professors mentioned the artist ."}
{"question": "The secretary admired the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers admired the secretary ."}
{"question": "The doctor introduced the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete introduced the doctor ."}
{"question": "The scientists encouraged the actor .", "answer": "The actor encouraged the scientists ."}
{"question": "The professor believed the students .", "answer": "The students believed the professor ."}
{"question": "The professors helped the students .", "answer": "The students helped the professors ."}
{"question": "The banker stopped the artists .", "answer": "The artists stopped the banker ."}
{"question": "The managers thanked the senator .", "answer": "The senator thanked the managers ."}
{"question": "The athlete stopped the artist .", "answer": "The artist stopped the athlete ."}
{"question": "The scientist contacted the senator .", "answer": "The senator contacted the scientist ."}
{"question": "The senators avoided the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist avoided the senators ."}
{"question": "The scientists stopped the judges .", "answer": "The judges stopped the scientists ."}
{"question": "The scientist thanked the senator .", "answer": "The senator thanked the scientist ."}
{"question": "The actors believed the banker .", "answer": "The banker believed the actors ."}
{"question": "The author believed the artists .", "answer": "The artists believed the author ."}
{"question": "The lawyers mentioned the artist .", "answer": "The artist mentioned the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The judge supported the artist .", "answer": "The artist supported the judge ."}
{"question": "The artist thanked the professors .", "answer": "The professors thanked the artist ."}
{"question": "The actor supported the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers supported the actor ."}
{"question": "The presidents saw the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor saw the presidents ."}
{"question": "The presidents advised the actor .", "answer": "The actor advised the presidents ."}
{"question": "The president believed the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist believed the president ."}
{"question": "The tourist called the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor called the tourist ."}
{"question": "The author avoided the actor .", "answer": "The actor avoided the author ."}
{"question": "The artists thanked the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers thanked the artists ."}
{"question": "The tourists saw the judges .", "answer": "The judges saw the tourists ."}
{"question": "The actors called the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents called the actors ."}
{"question": "The scientists supported the managers .", "answer": "The managers supported the scientists ."}
{"question": "The doctors introduced the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers introduced the doctors ."}
{"question": "The judges recommended the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers recommended the judges ."}
{"question": "The doctor mentioned the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist mentioned the doctor ."}
{"question": "The tourist saw the students .", "answer": "The students saw the tourist ."}
{"question": "The president recommended the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer recommended the president ."}
{"question": "The secretaries believed the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete believed the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The secretary advised the authors .", "answer": "The authors advised the secretary ."}
{"question": "The banker recommended the judge .", "answer": "The judge recommended the banker ."}
{"question": "The senators encouraged the professor .", "answer": "The professor encouraged the senators ."}
{"question": "The actors advised the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists advised the actors ."}
{"question": "The scientist thanked the artist .", "answer": "The artist thanked the scientist ."}
{"question": "The senator saw the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers saw the senator ."}
{"question": "The judges stopped the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist stopped the judges ."}
{"question": "The bankers saw the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists saw the bankers ."}
{"question": "The banker supported the senator .", "answer": "The senator supported the banker ."}
{"question": "The professors helped the artists .", "answer": "The artists helped the professors ."}
{"question": "The student recognized the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists recognized the student ."}
{"question": "The senators believed the professors .", "answer": "The professors believed the senators ."}
{"question": "The artists recommended the president .", "answer": "The president recommended the artists ."}
{"question": "The actor encouraged the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists encouraged the actor ."}
{"question": "The professor encouraged the judge .", "answer": "The judge encouraged the professor ."}
{"question": "The professor recommended the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer recommended the professor ."}
{"question": "The actor thanked the banker .", "answer": "The banker thanked the actor ."}
{"question": "The actors avoided the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary avoided the actors ."}
{"question": "The senator helped the managers .", "answer": "The managers helped the senator ."}
{"question": "The authors mentioned the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists mentioned the authors ."}
{"question": "The professors stopped the president .", "answer": "The president stopped the professors ."}
{"question": "The artist advised the senator .", "answer": "The senator advised the artist ."}
{"question": "The athlete saw the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor saw the athlete ."}
{"question": "The judge thanked the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor thanked the judge ."}
{"question": "The senators advised the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents advised the senators ."}
{"question": "The professor thanked the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist thanked the professor ."}
{"question": "The scientists admired the actor .", "answer": "The actor admired the scientists ."}
{"question": "The authors saw the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary saw the authors ."}
{"question": "The banker recommended the artist .", "answer": "The artist recommended the banker ."}
{"question": "The athlete recognized the banker .", "answer": "The banker recognized the athlete ."}
{"question": "The professors thanked the president .", "answer": "The president thanked the professors ."}
{"question": "The actors stopped the artist .", "answer": "The artist stopped the actors ."}
{"question": "The actors supported the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists supported the actors ."}
{"question": "The president thanked the actors .", "answer": "The actors thanked the president ."}
{"question": "The secretaries advised the professors .", "answer": "The professors advised the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The author avoided the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers avoided the author ."}
{"question": "The actor saw the senator .", "answer": "The senator saw the actor ."}
{"question": "The athletes supported the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries supported the athletes ."}
{"question": "The doctors advised the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist advised the doctors ."}
{"question": "The senators called the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer called the senators ."}
{"question": "The presidents admired the senators .", "answer": "The senators admired the presidents ."}
{"question": "The author advised the actors .", "answer": "The actors advised the author ."}
{"question": "The actor thanked the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes thanked the actor ."}
{"question": "The actors introduced the authors .", "answer": "The authors introduced the actors ."}
{"question": "The author stopped the actor .", "answer": "The actor stopped the author ."}
{"question": "The students mentioned the senator .", "answer": "The senator mentioned the students ."}
{"question": "The student supported the judge .", "answer": "The judge supported the student ."}
{"question": "The secretaries stopped the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents stopped the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The artist saw the professor .", "answer": "The professor saw the artist ."}
{"question": "The bankers introduced the artist .", "answer": "The artist introduced the bankers ."}
{"question": "The student called the authors .", "answer": "The authors called the student ."}
{"question": "The doctors introduced the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary introduced the doctors ."}
{"question": "The tourist supported the student .", "answer": "The student supported the tourist ."}
{"question": "The senator thanked the artists .", "answer": "The artists thanked the senator ."}
{"question": "The authors recognized the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes recognized the authors ."}
{"question": "The doctor introduced the judge .", "answer": "The judge introduced the doctor ."}
{"question": "The judge recognized the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes recognized the judge ."}
{"question": "The lawyers contacted the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist contacted the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The judge encouraged the author .", "answer": "The author encouraged the judge ."}
{"question": "The secretaries thanked the author .", "answer": "The author thanked the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The doctors mentioned the president .", "answer": "The president mentioned the doctors ."}
{"question": "The athletes encouraged the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers encouraged the athletes ."}
{"question": "The scientist thanked the actors .", "answer": "The actors thanked the scientist ."}
{"question": "The scientist advised the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries advised the scientist ."}
{"question": "The author thanked the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents thanked the author ."}
{"question": "The senator admired the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist admired the senator ."}
{"question": "The artists believed the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist believed the artists ."}
{"question": "The tourist avoided the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors avoided the tourist ."}
{"question": "The lawyer advised the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists advised the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The professor called the president .", "answer": "The president called the professor ."}
{"question": "The professors supported the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists supported the professors ."}
{"question": "The lawyers supported the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries supported the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The professor stopped the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists stopped the professor ."}
{"question": "The artists mentioned the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists mentioned the artists ."}
{"question": "The banker recognized the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors recognized the banker ."}
{"question": "The author thanked the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary thanked the author ."}
{"question": "The athlete stopped the judge .", "answer": "The judge stopped the athlete ."}
{"question": "The doctor recognized the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists recognized the doctor ."}
{"question": "The senators stopped the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor stopped the senators ."}
{"question": "The professor mentioned the senators .", "answer": "The senators mentioned the professor ."}
{"question": "The athletes recognized the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist recognized the athletes ."}
{"question": "The doctor mentioned the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists mentioned the doctor ."}
{"question": "The authors contacted the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer contacted the authors ."}
{"question": "The lawyers helped the students .", "answer": "The students helped the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The professors encouraged the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete encouraged the professors ."}
{"question": "The doctors supported the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers supported the doctors ."}
{"question": "The manager advised the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents advised the manager ."}
{"question": "The senator advised the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents advised the senator ."}
{"question": "The students avoided the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer avoided the students ."}
{"question": "The tourists helped the banker .", "answer": "The banker helped the tourists ."}
{"question": "The judge admired the senator .", "answer": "The senator admired the judge ."}
{"question": "The doctors avoided the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist avoided the doctors ."}
{"question": "The doctor stopped the judge .", "answer": "The judge stopped the doctor ."}
{"question": "The athletes thanked the president .", "answer": "The president thanked the athletes ."}
{"question": "The actor avoided the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete avoided the actor ."}
{"question": "The doctor recommended the actor .", "answer": "The actor recommended the doctor ."}
{"question": "The artists recognized the banker .", "answer": "The banker recognized the artists ."}
{"question": "The lawyers admired the manager .", "answer": "The manager admired the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The scientist helped the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers helped the scientist ."}
{"question": "The managers believed the judge .", "answer": "The judge believed the managers ."}
{"question": "The lawyers believed the students .", "answer": "The students believed the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The professor supported the manager .", "answer": "The manager supported the professor ."}
{"question": "The professors thanked the actor .", "answer": "The actor thanked the professors ."}
{"question": "The artist introduced the students .", "answer": "The students introduced the artist ."}
{"question": "The student recognized the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist recognized the student ."}
{"question": "The senators contacted the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors contacted the senators ."}
{"question": "The actor believed the students .", "answer": "The students believed the actor ."}
{"question": "The student admired the authors .", "answer": "The authors admired the student ."}
{"question": "The managers advised the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes advised the managers ."}
{"question": "The lawyer believed the professor .", "answer": "The professor believed the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The artist admired the senators .", "answer": "The senators admired the artist ."}
{"question": "The senators recognized the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor recognized the senators ."}
{"question": "The professors admired the actors .", "answer": "The actors admired the professors ."}
{"question": "The judges contacted the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete contacted the judges ."}
{"question": "The student helped the actors .", "answer": "The actors helped the student ."}
{"question": "The lawyers introduced the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary introduced the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The judges encouraged the student .", "answer": "The student encouraged the judges ."}
{"question": "The managers stopped the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents stopped the managers ."}
{"question": "The lawyers mentioned the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete mentioned the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The lawyer mentioned the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist mentioned the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The banker recognized the judges .", "answer": "The judges recognized the banker ."}
{"question": "The banker supported the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer supported the banker ."}
{"question": "The managers helped the students .", "answer": "The students helped the managers ."}
{"question": "The judge recognized the senator .", "answer": "The senator recognized the judge ."}
{"question": "The senator recommended the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist recommended the senator ."}
{"question": "The scientists stopped the professor .", "answer": "The professor stopped the scientists ."}
{"question": "The president helped the banker .", "answer": "The banker helped the president ."}
{"question": "The secretaries called the managers .", "answer": "The managers called the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The scientists supported the judges .", "answer": "The judges supported the scientists ."}
{"question": "The athlete thanked the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor thanked the athlete ."}
{"question": "The manager avoided the professor .", "answer": "The professor avoided the manager ."}
{"question": "The judge introduced the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists introduced the judge ."}
{"question": "The tourist stopped the students .", "answer": "The students stopped the tourist ."}
{"question": "The artists advised the students .", "answer": "The students advised the artists ."}
{"question": "The judge recommended the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes recommended the judge ."}
{"question": "The presidents avoided the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers avoided the presidents ."}
{"question": "The doctor saw the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers saw the doctor ."}
{"question": "The students supported the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist supported the students ."}
{"question": "The author supported the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers supported the author ."}
{"question": "The secretaries believed the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists believed the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The artists supported the managers .", "answer": "The managers supported the artists ."}
{"question": "The tourists thanked the president .", "answer": "The president thanked the tourists ."}
{"question": "The professors introduced the artists .", "answer": "The artists introduced the professors ."}
{"question": "The lawyer advised the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents advised the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The students admired the artists .", "answer": "The artists admired the students ."}
{"question": "The managers stopped the students .", "answer": "The students stopped the managers ."}
{"question": "The actor supported the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries supported the actor ."}
{"question": "The scientists avoided the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer avoided the scientists ."}
{"question": "The senators helped the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers helped the senators ."}
{"question": "The authors contacted the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes contacted the authors ."}
{"question": "The authors recognized the professors .", "answer": "The professors recognized the authors ."}
{"question": "The senators thanked the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers thanked the senators ."}
{"question": "The professor recommended the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes recommended the professor ."}
{"question": "The author helped the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary helped the author ."}
{"question": "The tourists encouraged the actor .", "answer": "The actor encouraged the tourists ."}
{"question": "The athletes recognized the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries recognized the athletes ."}
{"question": "The artist contacted the judges .", "answer": "The judges contacted the artist ."}
{"question": "The managers introduced the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary introduced the managers ."}
{"question": "The tourist believed the author .", "answer": "The author believed the tourist ."}
{"question": "The professors introduced the students .", "answer": "The students introduced the professors ."}
{"question": "The student recommended the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor recommended the student ."}
{"question": "The presidents supported the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete supported the presidents ."}
{"question": "The senator avoided the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists avoided the senator ."}
{"question": "The actor encouraged the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes encouraged the actor ."}
{"question": "The judge avoided the banker .", "answer": "The banker avoided the judge ."}
{"question": "The presidents helped the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists helped the presidents ."}
{"question": "The student admired the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist admired the student ."}
{"question": "The scientists stopped the artist .", "answer": "The artist stopped the scientists ."}
{"question": "The judge believed the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers believed the judge ."}
{"question": "The authors advised the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents advised the authors ."}
{"question": "The judges saw the president .", "answer": "The president saw the judges ."}
{"question": "The lawyers recommended the president .", "answer": "The president recommended the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The president recommended the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist recommended the president ."}
{"question": "The manager mentioned the professors .", "answer": "The professors mentioned the manager ."}
{"question": "The scientists believed the artists .", "answer": "The artists believed the scientists ."}
{"question": "The professors mentioned the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete mentioned the professors ."}
{"question": "The tourist admired the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary admired the tourist ."}
{"question": "The athletes mentioned the actor .", "answer": "The actor mentioned the athletes ."}
{"question": "The manager supported the artist .", "answer": "The artist supported the manager ."}
{"question": "The banker thanked the president .", "answer": "The president thanked the banker ."}
{"question": "The artists supported the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary supported the artists ."}
{"question": "The actor mentioned the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist mentioned the actor ."}
{"question": "The student encouraged the judges .", "answer": "The judges encouraged the student ."}
{"question": "The artists introduced the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary introduced the artists ."}
{"question": "The doctor encouraged the authors .", "answer": "The authors encouraged the doctor ."}
{"question": "The students helped the author .", "answer": "The author helped the students ."}
{"question": "The judge thanked the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists thanked the judge ."}
{"question": "The doctor thanked the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries thanked the doctor ."}
{"question": "The scientists avoided the artists .", "answer": "The artists avoided the scientists ."}
{"question": "The senator thanked the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents thanked the senator ."}
{"question": "The actor admired the professor .", "answer": "The professor admired the actor ."}
{"question": "The actors admired the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists admired the actors ."}
{"question": "The artists thanked the senator .", "answer": "The senator thanked the artists ."}
{"question": "The secretary recommended the banker .", "answer": "The banker recommended the secretary ."}
{"question": "The professors introduced the author .", "answer": "The author introduced the professors ."}
{"question": "The judge advised the actor .", "answer": "The actor advised the judge ."}
{"question": "The tourist avoided the professors .", "answer": "The professors avoided the tourist ."}
{"question": "The artists advised the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors advised the artists ."}
{"question": "The judges avoided the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer avoided the judges ."}
{"question": "The lawyers advised the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist advised the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The bankers saw the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes saw the bankers ."}
{"question": "The artists mentioned the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary mentioned the artists ."}
{"question": "The students mentioned the artists .", "answer": "The artists mentioned the students ."}
{"question": "The scientists thanked the student .", "answer": "The student thanked the scientists ."}
{"question": "The lawyers contacted the manager .", "answer": "The manager contacted the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The tourists recommended the authors .", "answer": "The authors recommended the tourists ."}
{"question": "The professor called the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer called the professor ."}
{"question": "The athletes helped the judges .", "answer": "The judges helped the athletes ."}
{"question": "The professors believed the judge .", "answer": "The judge believed the professors ."}
{"question": "The actor called the professors .", "answer": "The professors called the actor ."}
{"question": "The artists contacted the students .", "answer": "The students contacted the artists ."}
{"question": "The scientists advised the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete advised the scientists ."}
{"question": "The authors advised the judge .", "answer": "The judge advised the authors ."}
{"question": "The artist called the senator .", "answer": "The senator called the artist ."}
{"question": "The senator stopped the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries stopped the senator ."}
{"question": "The actor called the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes called the actor ."}
{"question": "The scientists believed the student .", "answer": "The student believed the scientists ."}
{"question": "The presidents stopped the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer stopped the presidents ."}
{"question": "The president supported the artist .", "answer": "The artist supported the president ."}
{"question": "The managers called the artists .", "answer": "The artists called the managers ."}
{"question": "The senators helped the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor helped the senators ."}
{"question": "The scientist introduced the senators .", "answer": "The senators introduced the scientist ."}
{"question": "The judge helped the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers helped the judge ."}
{"question": "The doctors called the authors .", "answer": "The authors called the doctors ."}
{"question": "The athletes encouraged the president .", "answer": "The president encouraged the athletes ."}
{"question": "The actor thanked the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents thanked the actor ."}
{"question": "The professors contacted the president .", "answer": "The president contacted the professors ."}
{"question": "The doctor recognized the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries recognized the doctor ."}
{"question": "The lawyer advised the professors .", "answer": "The professors advised the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The senator believed the students .", "answer": "The students believed the senator ."}
{"question": "The scientist recommended the author .", "answer": "The author recommended the scientist ."}
{"question": "The professor mentioned the artists .", "answer": "The artists mentioned the professor ."}
{"question": "The authors thanked the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers thanked the authors ."}
{"question": "The athlete recognized the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors recognized the athlete ."}
{"question": "The manager saw the artists .", "answer": "The artists saw the manager ."}
{"question": "The athlete believed the actor .", "answer": "The actor believed the athlete ."}
{"question": "The doctor called the student .", "answer": "The student called the doctor ."}
{"question": "The tourists helped the senator .", "answer": "The senator helped the tourists ."}
{"question": "The actors contacted the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist contacted the actors ."}
{"question": "The author mentioned the student .", "answer": "The student mentioned the author ."}
{"question": "The athlete helped the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists helped the athlete ."}
{"question": "The professor believed the president .", "answer": "The president believed the professor ."}
{"question": "The authors advised the senator .", "answer": "The senator advised the authors ."}
{"question": "The professor contacted the actor .", "answer": "The actor contacted the professor ."}
{"question": "The professors avoided the authors .", "answer": "The authors avoided the professors ."}
{"question": "The athlete introduced the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary introduced the athlete ."}
{"question": "The senators encouraged the actor .", "answer": "The actor encouraged the senators ."}
{"question": "The lawyers recommended the managers .", "answer": "The managers recommended the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The senator believed the artists .", "answer": "The artists believed the senator ."}
{"question": "The judge introduced the artists .", "answer": "The artists introduced the judge ."}
{"question": "The artists contacted the senator .", "answer": "The senator contacted the artists ."}
{"question": "The students advised the banker .", "answer": "The banker advised the students ."}
{"question": "The judges advised the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete advised the judges ."}
{"question": "The athletes saw the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors saw the athletes ."}
{"question": "The tourist thanked the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries thanked the tourist ."}
{"question": "The senator believed the author .", "answer": "The author believed the senator ."}
{"question": "The manager mentioned the judge .", "answer": "The judge mentioned the manager ."}
{"question": "The president helped the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary helped the president ."}
{"question": "The lawyers mentioned the professor .", "answer": "The professor mentioned the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The banker avoided the actor .", "answer": "The actor avoided the banker ."}
{"question": "The secretaries believed the students .", "answer": "The students believed the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The scientists helped the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist helped the scientists ."}
{"question": "The students recommended the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist recommended the students ."}
{"question": "The students contacted the artists .", "answer": "The artists contacted the students ."}
{"question": "The tourist supported the professors .", "answer": "The professors supported the tourist ."}
{"question": "The doctors recommended the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents recommended the doctors ."}
{"question": "The artist thanked the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer thanked the artist ."}
{"question": "The scientists helped the author .", "answer": "The author helped the scientists ."}
{"question": "The judge believed the artists .", "answer": "The artists believed the judge ."}
{"question": "The author recognized the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes recognized the author ."}
{"question": "The banker thanked the professors .", "answer": "The professors thanked the banker ."}
{"question": "The artist thanked the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers thanked the artist ."}
{"question": "The senators contacted the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries contacted the senators ."}
{"question": "The secretaries saw the students .", "answer": "The students saw the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The manager stopped the artists .", "answer": "The artists stopped the manager ."}
{"question": "The actors encouraged the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist encouraged the actors ."}
{"question": "The doctors called the author .", "answer": "The author called the doctors ."}
{"question": "The tourist contacted the professors .", "answer": "The professors contacted the tourist ."}
{"question": "The actor helped the artist .", "answer": "The artist helped the actor ."}
{"question": "The professor believed the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary believed the professor ."}
{"question": "The author believed the artist .", "answer": "The artist believed the author ."}
{"question": "The students mentioned the judge .", "answer": "The judge mentioned the students ."}
{"question": "The scientists thanked the artist .", "answer": "The artist thanked the scientists ."}
{"question": "The actors admired the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries admired the actors ."}
{"question": "The bankers helped the actor .", "answer": "The actor helped the bankers ."}
{"question": "The doctors helped the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer helped the doctors ."}
{"question": "The presidents supported the judges .", "answer": "The judges supported the presidents ."}
{"question": "The tourists contacted the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers contacted the tourists ."}
{"question": "The professors thanked the judges .", "answer": "The judges thanked the professors ."}
{"question": "The scientists advised the author .", "answer": "The author advised the scientists ."}
{"question": "The senators saw the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary saw the senators ."}
{"question": "The professor avoided the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries avoided the professor ."}
{"question": "The tourist avoided the student .", "answer": "The student avoided the tourist ."}
{"question": "The banker introduced the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist introduced the banker ."}
{"question": "The student introduced the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete introduced the student ."}
{"question": "The actors stopped the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete stopped the actors ."}
{"question": "The lawyer recommended the banker .", "answer": "The banker recommended the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The scientist recognized the authors .", "answer": "The authors recognized the scientist ."}
{"question": "The tourist recognized the student .", "answer": "The student recognized the tourist ."}
{"question": "The student called the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist called the student ."}
{"question": "The doctors encouraged the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer encouraged the doctors ."}
{"question": "The students avoided the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors avoided the students ."}
{"question": "The students admired the authors .", "answer": "The authors admired the students ."}
{"question": "The senators stopped the students .", "answer": "The students stopped the senators ."}
{"question": "The author stopped the actors .", "answer": "The actors stopped the author ."}
{"question": "The judge called the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor called the judge ."}
{"question": "The managers believed the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary believed the managers ."}
{"question": "The doctor recognized the managers .", "answer": "The managers recognized the doctor ."}
{"question": "The artist stopped the professors .", "answer": "The professors stopped the artist ."}
{"question": "The artists helped the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist helped the artists ."}
{"question": "The lawyers believed the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries believed the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The actor helped the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes helped the actor ."}
{"question": "The bankers thanked the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes thanked the bankers ."}
{"question": "The secretary called the artist .", "answer": "The artist called the secretary ."}
{"question": "The athletes admired the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists admired the athletes ."}
{"question": "The tourist contacted the managers .", "answer": "The managers contacted the tourist ."}
{"question": "The secretary supported the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors supported the secretary ."}
{"question": "The presidents supported the manager .", "answer": "The manager supported the presidents ."}
{"question": "The athlete mentioned the artist .", "answer": "The artist mentioned the athlete ."}
{"question": "The presidents recognized the judge .", "answer": "The judge recognized the presidents ."}
{"question": "The presidents thanked the authors .", "answer": "The authors thanked the presidents ."}
{"question": "The managers recommended the judges .", "answer": "The judges recommended the managers ."}
{"question": "The students helped the professors .", "answer": "The professors helped the students ."}
{"question": "The secretaries mentioned the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes mentioned the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The senator recommended the artist .", "answer": "The artist recommended the senator ."}
{"question": "The presidents encouraged the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers encouraged the presidents ."}
{"question": "The artist admired the judges .", "answer": "The judges admired the artist ."}
{"question": "The lawyer mentioned the manager .", "answer": "The manager mentioned the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The tourists thanked the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor thanked the tourists ."}
{"question": "The doctor admired the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary admired the doctor ."}
{"question": "The doctor encouraged the manager .", "answer": "The manager encouraged the doctor ."}
{"question": "The judge avoided the professors .", "answer": "The professors avoided the judge ."}
{"question": "The athletes mentioned the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist mentioned the athletes ."}
{"question": "The senators contacted the banker .", "answer": "The banker contacted the senators ."}
{"question": "The senators stopped the manager .", "answer": "The manager stopped the senators ."}
{"question": "The author saw the artist .", "answer": "The artist saw the author ."}
{"question": "The judges believed the authors .", "answer": "The authors believed the judges ."}
{"question": "The artists supported the actor .", "answer": "The actor supported the artists ."}
{"question": "The judge saw the students .", "answer": "The students saw the judge ."}
{"question": "The artists supported the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists supported the artists ."}
{"question": "The tourist advised the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary advised the tourist ."}
{"question": "The bankers believed the professor .", "answer": "The professor believed the bankers ."}
{"question": "The judges advised the author .", "answer": "The author advised the judges ."}
{"question": "The authors recommended the managers .", "answer": "The managers recommended the authors ."}
{"question": "The manager supported the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries supported the manager ."}
{"question": "The tourist encouraged the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary encouraged the tourist ."}
{"question": "The doctors recognized the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary recognized the doctors ."}
{"question": "The secretary called the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor called the secretary ."}
{"question": "The athlete supported the actor .", "answer": "The actor supported the athlete ."}
{"question": "The professors avoided the student .", "answer": "The student avoided the professors ."}
{"question": "The authors contacted the artist .", "answer": "The artist contacted the authors ."}
{"question": "The students admired the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries admired the students ."}
{"question": "The professors contacted the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists contacted the professors ."}
{"question": "The presidents recognized the professors .", "answer": "The professors recognized the presidents ."}
{"question": "The artists introduced the actors .", "answer": "The actors introduced the artists ."}
{"question": "The presidents advised the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries advised the presidents ."}
{"question": "The presidents thanked the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer thanked the presidents ."}
{"question": "The student encouraged the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer encouraged the student ."}
{"question": "The secretaries admired the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents admired the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The authors admired the professors .", "answer": "The professors admired the authors ."}
{"question": "The athlete advised the managers .", "answer": "The managers advised the athlete ."}
{"question": "The president recognized the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers recognized the president ."}
{"question": "The president thanked the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer thanked the president ."}
{"question": "The actor stopped the professor .", "answer": "The professor stopped the actor ."}
{"question": "The lawyers advised the artists .", "answer": "The artists advised the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The scientists advised the authors .", "answer": "The authors advised the scientists ."}
{"question": "The bankers introduced the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists introduced the bankers ."}
{"question": "The judge supported the author .", "answer": "The author supported the judge ."}
{"question": "The professors contacted the judges .", "answer": "The judges contacted the professors ."}
{"question": "The presidents mentioned the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists mentioned the presidents ."}
{"question": "The bankers introduced the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors introduced the bankers ."}
{"question": "The lawyers avoided the actors .", "answer": "The actors avoided the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The judges admired the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer admired the judges ."}
{"question": "The authors avoided the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers avoided the authors ."}
{"question": "The secretaries stopped the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists stopped the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The tourist helped the artist .", "answer": "The artist helped the tourist ."}
{"question": "The tourists admired the banker .", "answer": "The banker admired the tourists ."}
{"question": "The actor called the president .", "answer": "The president called the actor ."}
{"question": "The lawyers supported the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete supported the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The banker stopped the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries stopped the banker ."}
{"question": "The bankers saw the students .", "answer": "The students saw the bankers ."}
{"question": "The athlete avoided the artist .", "answer": "The artist avoided the athlete ."}
{"question": "The senators thanked the students .", "answer": "The students thanked the senators ."}
{"question": "The secretary called the manager .", "answer": "The manager called the secretary ."}
{"question": "The professor encouraged the artist .", "answer": "The artist encouraged the professor ."}
{"question": "The professor recognized the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists recognized the professor ."}
{"question": "The actor recognized the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors recognized the actor ."}
{"question": "The tourists stopped the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries stopped the tourists ."}
{"question": "The managers encouraged the artist .", "answer": "The artist encouraged the managers ."}
{"question": "The artist stopped the author .", "answer": "The author stopped the artist ."}
{"question": "The tourist encouraged the artist .", "answer": "The artist encouraged the tourist ."}
{"question": "The presidents thanked the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist thanked the presidents ."}
{"question": "The artist helped the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer helped the artist ."}
{"question": "The secretaries avoided the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists avoided the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The athlete mentioned the artists .", "answer": "The artists mentioned the athlete ."}
{"question": "The athletes thanked the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist thanked the athletes ."}
{"question": "The scientists helped the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents helped the scientists ."}
{"question": "The tourist encouraged the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete encouraged the tourist ."}
{"question": "The author recommended the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes recommended the author ."}
{"question": "The judges supported the student .", "answer": "The student supported the judges ."}
{"question": "The presidents helped the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers helped the presidents ."}
{"question": "The authors recognized the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries recognized the authors ."}
{"question": "The authors believed the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists believed the authors ."}
{"question": "The tourists saw the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers saw the tourists ."}
{"question": "The author called the managers .", "answer": "The managers called the author ."}
{"question": "The professor encouraged the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer encouraged the professor ."}
{"question": "The lawyer saw the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists saw the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The senators called the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists called the senators ."}
{"question": "The athlete helped the judges .", "answer": "The judges helped the athlete ."}
{"question": "The senators helped the artist .", "answer": "The artist helped the senators ."}
{"question": "The students recognized the senator .", "answer": "The senator recognized the students ."}
{"question": "The lawyer believed the judges .", "answer": "The judges believed the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The senator supported the professors .", "answer": "The professors supported the senator ."}
{"question": "The scientists recommended the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries recommended the scientists ."}
{"question": "The author recognized the actor .", "answer": "The actor recognized the author ."}
{"question": "The banker encouraged the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist encouraged the banker ."}
{"question": "The lawyer stopped the professors .", "answer": "The professors stopped the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The secretary introduced the senator .", "answer": "The senator introduced the secretary ."}
{"question": "The president supported the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers supported the president ."}
{"question": "The athlete helped the actors .", "answer": "The actors helped the athlete ."}
{"question": "The artist contacted the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers contacted the artist ."}
{"question": "The actor advised the professors .", "answer": "The professors advised the actor ."}
{"question": "The actors introduced the author .", "answer": "The author introduced the actors ."}
{"question": "The secretaries called the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete called the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The tourist helped the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers helped the tourist ."}
{"question": "The tourists advised the actor .", "answer": "The actor advised the tourists ."}
{"question": "The professor helped the judge .", "answer": "The judge helped the professor ."}
{"question": "The presidents admired the senator .", "answer": "The senator admired the presidents ."}
{"question": "The professor stopped the author .", "answer": "The author stopped the professor ."}
{"question": "The scientist contacted the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary contacted the scientist ."}
{"question": "The doctors thanked the judges .", "answer": "The judges thanked the doctors ."}
{"question": "The secretaries encouraged the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes encouraged the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The artist encouraged the authors .", "answer": "The authors encouraged the artist ."}
{"question": "The presidents supported the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary supported the presidents ."}
{"question": "The doctor helped the manager .", "answer": "The manager helped the doctor ."}
{"question": "The bankers avoided the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist avoided the bankers ."}
{"question": "The lawyers thanked the student .", "answer": "The student thanked the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The banker recommended the senators .", "answer": "The senators recommended the banker ."}
{"question": "The professors stopped the student .", "answer": "The student stopped the professors ."}
{"question": "The manager recognized the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers recognized the manager ."}
{"question": "The professors recognized the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers recognized the professors ."}
{"question": "The scientists advised the senator .", "answer": "The senator advised the scientists ."}
{"question": "The lawyers avoided the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor avoided the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The judges called the authors .", "answer": "The authors called the judges ."}
{"question": "The judge thanked the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist thanked the judge ."}
{"question": "The presidents helped the professor .", "answer": "The professor helped the presidents ."}
{"question": "The secretary admired the judges .", "answer": "The judges admired the secretary ."}
{"question": "The doctor advised the professors .", "answer": "The professors advised the doctor ."}
{"question": "The scientists helped the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists helped the scientists ."}
{"question": "The secretary admired the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes admired the secretary ."}
{"question": "The artists helped the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents helped the artists ."}
{"question": "The lawyer called the authors .", "answer": "The authors called the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The judge helped the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists helped the judge ."}
{"question": "The actors stopped the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents stopped the actors ."}
{"question": "The managers recognized the judge .", "answer": "The judge recognized the managers ."}
{"question": "The actor helped the senators .", "answer": "The senators helped the actor ."}
{"question": "The athletes mentioned the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents mentioned the athletes ."}
{"question": "The managers introduced the actors .", "answer": "The actors introduced the managers ."}
{"question": "The judge mentioned the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors mentioned the judge ."}
{"question": "The athlete stopped the managers .", "answer": "The managers stopped the athlete ."}
{"question": "The lawyer stopped the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes stopped the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The doctors contacted the authors .", "answer": "The authors contacted the doctors ."}
{"question": "The actors mentioned the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor mentioned the actors ."}
{"question": "The actors saw the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist saw the actors ."}
{"question": "The judge recognized the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary recognized the judge ."}
{"question": "The doctor avoided the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists avoided the doctor ."}
{"question": "The judge advised the authors .", "answer": "The authors advised the judge ."}
{"question": "The bankers avoided the author .", "answer": "The author avoided the bankers ."}
{"question": "The doctors called the actor .", "answer": "The actor called the doctors ."}
{"question": "The senators called the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents called the senators ."}
{"question": "The author stopped the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes stopped the author ."}
{"question": "The doctor recognized the actor .", "answer": "The actor recognized the doctor ."}
{"question": "The lawyer avoided the judges .", "answer": "The judges avoided the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The president admired the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist admired the president ."}
{"question": "The athletes introduced the judges .", "answer": "The judges introduced the athletes ."}
{"question": "The artists saw the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists saw the artists ."}
{"question": "The artists believed the senator .", "answer": "The senator believed the artists ."}
{"question": "The author called the banker .", "answer": "The banker called the author ."}
{"question": "The author saw the actor .", "answer": "The actor saw the author ."}
{"question": "The secretaries recommended the authors .", "answer": "The authors recommended the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The scientist advised the senator .", "answer": "The senator advised the scientist ."}
{"question": "The professors advised the senators .", "answer": "The senators advised the professors ."}
{"question": "The authors contacted the banker .", "answer": "The banker contacted the authors ."}
{"question": "The senators avoided the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents avoided the senators ."}
{"question": "The senator introduced the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers introduced the senator ."}
{"question": "The bankers stopped the judge .", "answer": "The judge stopped the bankers ."}
{"question": "The bankers contacted the senators .", "answer": "The senators contacted the bankers ."}
{"question": "The banker recommended the senator .", "answer": "The senator recommended the banker ."}
{"question": "The secretaries mentioned the actors .", "answer": "The actors mentioned the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The lawyers thanked the professor .", "answer": "The professor thanked the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The manager supported the students .", "answer": "The students supported the manager ."}
{"question": "The senator advised the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete advised the senator ."}
{"question": "The judges introduced the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor introduced the judges ."}
{"question": "The tourist admired the actors .", "answer": "The actors admired the tourist ."}
{"question": "The authors stopped the students .", "answer": "The students stopped the authors ."}
{"question": "The lawyer believed the students .", "answer": "The students believed the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The students supported the author .", "answer": "The author supported the students ."}
{"question": "The managers supported the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents supported the managers ."}
{"question": "The lawyers called the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete called the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The scientists admired the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete admired the scientists ."}
{"question": "The authors supported the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer supported the authors ."}
{"question": "The professors admired the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists admired the professors ."}
{"question": "The students mentioned the judges .", "answer": "The judges mentioned the students ."}
{"question": "The secretaries helped the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists helped the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The managers contacted the president .", "answer": "The president contacted the managers ."}
{"question": "The authors saw the artist .", "answer": "The artist saw the authors ."}
{"question": "The banker saw the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor saw the banker ."}
{"question": "The lawyer avoided the author .", "answer": "The author avoided the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The authors encouraged the student .", "answer": "The student encouraged the authors ."}
{"question": "The secretaries encouraged the artist .", "answer": "The artist encouraged the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The judge advised the author .", "answer": "The author advised the judge ."}
{"question": "The president supported the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary supported the president ."}
{"question": "The artist stopped the president .", "answer": "The president stopped the artist ."}
{"question": "The actors introduced the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries introduced the actors ."}
{"question": "The bankers stopped the judges .", "answer": "The judges stopped the bankers ."}
{"question": "The senator recommended the professor .", "answer": "The professor recommended the senator ."}
{"question": "The actors helped the artists .", "answer": "The artists helped the actors ."}
{"question": "The doctors advised the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer advised the doctors ."}
{"question": "The scientists recognized the student .", "answer": "The student recognized the scientists ."}
{"question": "The secretary advised the senator .", "answer": "The senator advised the secretary ."}
{"question": "The artist avoided the professor .", "answer": "The professor avoided the artist ."}
{"question": "The authors thanked the artist .", "answer": "The artist thanked the authors ."}
{"question": "The athlete encouraged the senators .", "answer": "The senators encouraged the athlete ."}
{"question": "The president encouraged the professor .", "answer": "The professor encouraged the president ."}
{"question": "The manager mentioned the actors .", "answer": "The actors mentioned the manager ."}
{"question": "The judges introduced the manager .", "answer": "The manager introduced the judges ."}
{"question": "The athletes introduced the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors introduced the athletes ."}
{"question": "The artist stopped the students .", "answer": "The students stopped the artist ."}
{"question": "The author avoided the student .", "answer": "The student avoided the author ."}
{"question": "The tourist avoided the senators .", "answer": "The senators avoided the tourist ."}
{"question": "The president encouraged the actors .", "answer": "The actors encouraged the president ."}
{"question": "The banker admired the professors .", "answer": "The professors admired the banker ."}
{"question": "The actors saw the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer saw the actors ."}
{"question": "The bankers advised the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries advised the bankers ."}
{"question": "The student recommended the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists recommended the student ."}
{"question": "The athlete thanked the actors .", "answer": "The actors thanked the athlete ."}
{"question": "The actors advised the artists .", "answer": "The artists advised the actors ."}
{"question": "The senator recommended the professors .", "answer": "The professors recommended the senator ."}
{"question": "The tourist encouraged the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries encouraged the tourist ."}
{"question": "The banker advised the authors .", "answer": "The authors advised the banker ."}
{"question": "The students admired the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers admired the students ."}
{"question": "The tourists introduced the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers introduced the tourists ."}
{"question": "The manager helped the senators .", "answer": "The senators helped the manager ."}
{"question": "The banker encouraged the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist encouraged the banker ."}
{"question": "The tourists admired the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes admired the tourists ."}
{"question": "The scientists called the banker .", "answer": "The banker called the scientists ."}
{"question": "The managers recommended the professor .", "answer": "The professor recommended the managers ."}
{"question": "The senator stopped the professors .", "answer": "The professors stopped the senator ."}
{"question": "The senator believed the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer believed the senator ."}
{"question": "The students admired the artist .", "answer": "The artist admired the students ."}
{"question": "The athletes stopped the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists stopped the athletes ."}
{"question": "The author encouraged the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists encouraged the author ."}
{"question": "The scientists saw the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist saw the scientists ."}
{"question": "The artists encouraged the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists encouraged the artists ."}
{"question": "The athlete thanked the professor .", "answer": "The professor thanked the athlete ."}
{"question": "The professor saw the judges .", "answer": "The judges saw the professor ."}
{"question": "The lawyer supported the managers .", "answer": "The managers supported the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The scientist recommended the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary recommended the scientist ."}
{"question": "The professor mentioned the managers .", "answer": "The managers mentioned the professor ."}
{"question": "The artist helped the banker .", "answer": "The banker helped the artist ."}
{"question": "The secretary contacted the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents contacted the secretary ."}
{"question": "The scientists recommended the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary recommended the scientists ."}
{"question": "The author stopped the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries stopped the author ."}
{"question": "The scientist stopped the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary stopped the scientist ."}
{"question": "The doctors believed the banker .", "answer": "The banker believed the doctors ."}
{"question": "The tourist saw the professor .", "answer": "The professor saw the tourist ."}
{"question": "The students recognized the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents recognized the students ."}
{"question": "The secretary called the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes called the secretary ."}
{"question": "The professors introduced the manager .", "answer": "The manager introduced the professors ."}
{"question": "The scientist admired the authors .", "answer": "The authors admired the scientist ."}
{"question": "The judge recognized the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist recognized the judge ."}
{"question": "The professor supported the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes supported the professor ."}
{"question": "The managers helped the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers helped the managers ."}
{"question": "The professors mentioned the author .", "answer": "The author mentioned the professors ."}
{"question": "The secretary thanked the artists .", "answer": "The artists thanked the secretary ."}
{"question": "The banker helped the judges .", "answer": "The judges helped the banker ."}
{"question": "The scientists believed the author .", "answer": "The author believed the scientists ."}
{"question": "The athlete called the president .", "answer": "The president called the athlete ."}
{"question": "The manager saw the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists saw the manager ."}
{"question": "The banker admired the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents admired the banker ."}
{"question": "The tourists recognized the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer recognized the tourists ."}
{"question": "The actors stopped the banker .", "answer": "The banker stopped the actors ."}
{"question": "The artists thanked the professor .", "answer": "The professor thanked the artists ."}
{"question": "The student recognized the authors .", "answer": "The authors recognized the student ."}
{"question": "The scientist advised the professor .", "answer": "The professor advised the scientist ."}
{"question": "The authors called the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer called the authors ."}
{"question": "The students encouraged the senators .", "answer": "The senators encouraged the students ."}
{"question": "The artists called the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary called the artists ."}
{"question": "The scientist admired the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer admired the scientist ."}
{"question": "The judges recognized the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents recognized the judges ."}
{"question": "The manager thanked the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor thanked the manager ."}
{"question": "The senator encouraged the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer encouraged the senator ."}
{"question": "The scientists supported the president .", "answer": "The president supported the scientists ."}
{"question": "The scientist recommended the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers recommended the scientist ."}
{"question": "The actor believed the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes believed the actor ."}
{"question": "The secretaries encouraged the student .", "answer": "The student encouraged the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The scientist encouraged the student .", "answer": "The student encouraged the scientist ."}
{"question": "The professor called the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries called the professor ."}
{"question": "The artist advised the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers advised the artist ."}
{"question": "The bankers supported the managers .", "answer": "The managers supported the bankers ."}
{"question": "The student contacted the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete contacted the student ."}
{"question": "The artists recommended the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor recommended the artists ."}
{"question": "The scientists mentioned the managers .", "answer": "The managers mentioned the scientists ."}
{"question": "The banker called the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors called the banker ."}
{"question": "The actors avoided the judges .", "answer": "The judges avoided the actors ."}
{"question": "The senators helped the student .", "answer": "The student helped the senators ."}
{"question": "The lawyers saw the president .", "answer": "The president saw the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The banker thanked the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers thanked the banker ."}
{"question": "The banker supported the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists supported the banker ."}
{"question": "The secretaries recommended the senator .", "answer": "The senator recommended the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The scientist helped the author .", "answer": "The author helped the scientist ."}
{"question": "The actor thanked the professors .", "answer": "The professors thanked the actor ."}
{"question": "The athlete supported the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists supported the athlete ."}
{"question": "The senators encouraged the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist encouraged the senators ."}
{"question": "The banker contacted the professors .", "answer": "The professors contacted the banker ."}
{"question": "The judge believed the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor believed the judge ."}
{"question": "The tourist supported the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor supported the tourist ."}
{"question": "The students called the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists called the students ."}
{"question": "The bankers recommended the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries recommended the bankers ."}
{"question": "The authors helped the actor .", "answer": "The actor helped the authors ."}
{"question": "The tourist mentioned the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer mentioned the tourist ."}
{"question": "The artists admired the manager .", "answer": "The manager admired the artists ."}
{"question": "The president mentioned the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary mentioned the president ."}
{"question": "The authors recognized the banker .", "answer": "The banker recognized the authors ."}
{"question": "The secretary stopped the students .", "answer": "The students stopped the secretary ."}
{"question": "The tourists contacted the artists .", "answer": "The artists contacted the tourists ."}
{"question": "The lawyer contacted the professor .", "answer": "The professor contacted the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The presidents stopped the manager .", "answer": "The manager stopped the presidents ."}
{"question": "The artists thanked the president .", "answer": "The president thanked the artists ."}
{"question": "The manager recognized the artists .", "answer": "The artists recognized the manager ."}
{"question": "The judge contacted the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers contacted the judge ."}
{"question": "The secretaries stopped the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer stopped the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The athlete supported the actors .", "answer": "The actors supported the athlete ."}
{"question": "The secretaries introduced the actor .", "answer": "The actor introduced the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The athletes called the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors called the athletes ."}
{"question": "The senators helped the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist helped the senators ."}
{"question": "The doctors recommended the president .", "answer": "The president recommended the doctors ."}
{"question": "The athletes mentioned the managers .", "answer": "The managers mentioned the athletes ."}
{"question": "The athlete avoided the student .", "answer": "The student avoided the athlete ."}
{"question": "The author stopped the student .", "answer": "The student stopped the author ."}
{"question": "The doctor stopped the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers stopped the doctor ."}
{"question": "The senator called the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete called the senator ."}
{"question": "The scientists recommended the artist .", "answer": "The artist recommended the scientists ."}
{"question": "The student introduced the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors introduced the student ."}
{"question": "The students recognized the senators .", "answer": "The senators recognized the students ."}
{"question": "The secretaries contacted the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete contacted the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The president helped the artist .", "answer": "The artist helped the president ."}
{"question": "The banker stopped the actors .", "answer": "The actors stopped the banker ."}
{"question": "The managers admired the judges .", "answer": "The judges admired the managers ."}
{"question": "The student encouraged the senator .", "answer": "The senator encouraged the student ."}
{"question": "The athletes recognized the judges .", "answer": "The judges recognized the athletes ."}
{"question": "The scientists encouraged the senators .", "answer": "The senators encouraged the scientists ."}
{"question": "The managers supported the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist supported the managers ."}
{"question": "The lawyers introduced the students .", "answer": "The students introduced the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The judge called the professors .", "answer": "The professors called the judge ."}
{"question": "The tourist thanked the actors .", "answer": "The actors thanked the tourist ."}
{"question": "The professors helped the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor helped the professors ."}
{"question": "The lawyer contacted the author .", "answer": "The author contacted the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The tourists recognized the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete recognized the tourists ."}
{"question": "The authors supported the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers supported the authors ."}
{"question": "The professors avoided the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist avoided the professors ."}
{"question": "The lawyers thanked the manager .", "answer": "The manager thanked the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The judges recommended the actors .", "answer": "The actors recommended the judges ."}
{"question": "The lawyer recognized the professors .", "answer": "The professors recognized the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The manager mentioned the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor mentioned the manager ."}
{"question": "The presidents encouraged the students .", "answer": "The students encouraged the presidents ."}
{"question": "The scientist thanked the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists thanked the scientist ."}
{"question": "The artist mentioned the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries mentioned the artist ."}
{"question": "The judge saw the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist saw the judge ."}
{"question": "The senators contacted the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist contacted the senators ."}
{"question": "The president avoided the senator .", "answer": "The senator avoided the president ."}
{"question": "The presidents recognized the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists recognized the presidents ."}
{"question": "The banker helped the authors .", "answer": "The authors helped the banker ."}
{"question": "The artists helped the banker .", "answer": "The banker helped the artists ."}
{"question": "The presidents recognized the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist recognized the presidents ."}
{"question": "The secretaries thanked the students .", "answer": "The students thanked the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The scientist admired the judges .", "answer": "The judges admired the scientist ."}
{"question": "The authors avoided the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete avoided the authors ."}
{"question": "The authors supported the professors .", "answer": "The professors supported the authors ."}
{"question": "The secretaries helped the author .", "answer": "The author helped the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The student believed the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists believed the student ."}
{"question": "The athletes admired the professor .", "answer": "The professor admired the athletes ."}
{"question": "The bankers contacted the manager .", "answer": "The manager contacted the bankers ."}
{"question": "The professor encouraged the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist encouraged the professor ."}
{"question": "The lawyers encouraged the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers encouraged the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The bankers recommended the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete recommended the bankers ."}
{"question": "The judge called the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers called the judge ."}
{"question": "The scientists recommended the banker .", "answer": "The banker recommended the scientists ."}
{"question": "The scientist encouraged the senator .", "answer": "The senator encouraged the scientist ."}
{"question": "The scientist encouraged the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors encouraged the scientist ."}
{"question": "The athlete helped the manager .", "answer": "The manager helped the athlete ."}
{"question": "The secretary thanked the professor .", "answer": "The professor thanked the secretary ."}
{"question": "The tourist introduced the professor .", "answer": "The professor introduced the tourist ."}
{"question": "The students supported the managers .", "answer": "The managers supported the students ."}
{"question": "The lawyers believed the actor .", "answer": "The actor believed the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The athletes avoided the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers avoided the athletes ."}
{"question": "The managers mentioned the authors .", "answer": "The authors mentioned the managers ."}
{"question": "The secretaries avoided the authors .", "answer": "The authors avoided the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The professors recognized the senators .", "answer": "The senators recognized the professors ."}
{"question": "The authors believed the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers believed the authors ."}
{"question": "The presidents avoided the artists .", "answer": "The artists avoided the presidents ."}
{"question": "The professors recommended the judges .", "answer": "The judges recommended the professors ."}
{"question": "The senator thanked the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries thanked the senator ."}
{"question": "The secretary recognized the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists recognized the secretary ."}
{"question": "The presidents stopped the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers stopped the presidents ."}
{"question": "The professors avoided the artist .", "answer": "The artist avoided the professors ."}
{"question": "The bankers recommended the authors .", "answer": "The authors recommended the bankers ."}
{"question": "The presidents thanked the student .", "answer": "The student thanked the presidents ."}
{"question": "The senators thanked the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer thanked the senators ."}
{"question": "The actor saw the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor saw the actor ."}
{"question": "The secretaries called the actors .", "answer": "The actors called the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The banker recognized the professor .", "answer": "The professor recognized the banker ."}
{"question": "The lawyers believed the president .", "answer": "The president believed the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The president avoided the senators .", "answer": "The senators avoided the president ."}
{"question": "The tourist avoided the judge .", "answer": "The judge avoided the tourist ."}
{"question": "The secretaries supported the manager .", "answer": "The manager supported the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The doctors called the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists called the doctors ."}
{"question": "The judges avoided the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors avoided the judges ."}
{"question": "The athletes introduced the senator .", "answer": "The senator introduced the athletes ."}
{"question": "The banker supported the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries supported the banker ."}
{"question": "The scientist contacted the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor contacted the scientist ."}
{"question": "The student recognized the banker .", "answer": "The banker recognized the student ."}
{"question": "The senators stopped the judge .", "answer": "The judge stopped the senators ."}
{"question": "The athletes admired the authors .", "answer": "The authors admired the athletes ."}
{"question": "The manager mentioned the students .", "answer": "The students mentioned the manager ."}
{"question": "The artists stopped the managers .", "answer": "The managers stopped the artists ."}
{"question": "The secretaries supported the professors .", "answer": "The professors supported the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The professors believed the managers .", "answer": "The managers believed the professors ."}
{"question": "The lawyers stopped the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes stopped the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The doctor contacted the judges .", "answer": "The judges contacted the doctor ."}
{"question": "The students admired the banker .", "answer": "The banker admired the students ."}
{"question": "The actor recommended the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists recommended the actor ."}
{"question": "The managers stopped the senators .", "answer": "The senators stopped the managers ."}
{"question": "The artist recommended the students .", "answer": "The students recommended the artist ."}
{"question": "The judges recognized the senator .", "answer": "The senator recognized the judges ."}
{"question": "The doctor saw the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries saw the doctor ."}
{"question": "The secretary believed the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete believed the secretary ."}
{"question": "The managers advised the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor advised the managers ."}
{"question": "The author recognized the senator .", "answer": "The senator recognized the author ."}
{"question": "The artists avoided the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes avoided the artists ."}
{"question": "The artist contacted the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists contacted the artist ."}
{"question": "The president thanked the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists thanked the president ."}
{"question": "The author advised the judges .", "answer": "The judges advised the author ."}
{"question": "The manager saw the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries saw the manager ."}
{"question": "The scientist thanked the professor .", "answer": "The professor thanked the scientist ."}
{"question": "The professors mentioned the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists mentioned the professors ."}
{"question": "The professor advised the actor .", "answer": "The actor advised the professor ."}
{"question": "The authors saw the actor .", "answer": "The actor saw the authors ."}
{"question": "The scientists mentioned the senators .", "answer": "The senators mentioned the scientists ."}
{"question": "The manager admired the professors .", "answer": "The professors admired the manager ."}
{"question": "The author recognized the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor recognized the author ."}
{"question": "The president supported the judges .", "answer": "The judges supported the president ."}
{"question": "The manager supported the judge .", "answer": "The judge supported the manager ."}
{"question": "The authors encouraged the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes encouraged the authors ."}
{"question": "The professors saw the judge .", "answer": "The judge saw the professors ."}
{"question": "The athlete supported the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary supported the athlete ."}
{"question": "The managers admired the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries admired the managers ."}
{"question": "The president mentioned the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers mentioned the president ."}
{"question": "The senators recognized the judges .", "answer": "The judges recognized the senators ."}
{"question": "The doctor mentioned the judge .", "answer": "The judge mentioned the doctor ."}
{"question": "The tourists admired the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists admired the tourists ."}
{"question": "The judges thanked the president .", "answer": "The president thanked the judges ."}
{"question": "The artist avoided the manager .", "answer": "The manager avoided the artist ."}
{"question": "The judge called the actor .", "answer": "The actor called the judge ."}
{"question": "The doctors helped the professors .", "answer": "The professors helped the doctors ."}
{"question": "The student called the actor .", "answer": "The actor called the student ."}
{"question": "The athletes contacted the actors .", "answer": "The actors contacted the athletes ."}
{"question": "The professor supported the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents supported the professor ."}
{"question": "The artists admired the president .", "answer": "The president admired the artists ."}
{"question": "The scientist encouraged the president .", "answer": "The president encouraged the scientist ."}
{"question": "The athletes saw the actor .", "answer": "The actor saw the athletes ."}
{"question": "The actor supported the judge .", "answer": "The judge supported the actor ."}
{"question": "The judge stopped the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries stopped the judge ."}
{"question": "The bankers recommended the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer recommended the bankers ."}
{"question": "The tourist avoided the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers avoided the tourist ."}
{"question": "The actors called the student .", "answer": "The student called the actors ."}
{"question": "The senator recognized the judges .", "answer": "The judges recognized the senator ."}
{"question": "The senator stopped the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists stopped the senator ."}
{"question": "The athletes advised the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers advised the athletes ."}
{"question": "The secretary called the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers called the secretary ."}
{"question": "The banker contacted the professor .", "answer": "The professor contacted the banker ."}
{"question": "The tourists helped the authors .", "answer": "The authors helped the tourists ."}
{"question": "The professor mentioned the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers mentioned the professor ."}
{"question": "The lawyers recognized the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete recognized the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The senator avoided the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries avoided the senator ."}
{"question": "The doctor avoided the president .", "answer": "The president avoided the doctor ."}
{"question": "The student believed the banker .", "answer": "The banker believed the student ."}
{"question": "The doctors stopped the professor .", "answer": "The professor stopped the doctors ."}
{"question": "The athletes admired the student .", "answer": "The student admired the athletes ."}
{"question": "The tourist contacted the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer contacted the tourist ."}
{"question": "The artist advised the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists advised the artist ."}
{"question": "The scientist helped the manager .", "answer": "The manager helped the scientist ."}
{"question": "The managers thanked the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents thanked the managers ."}
{"question": "The senators saw the judges .", "answer": "The judges saw the senators ."}
{"question": "The lawyer contacted the manager .", "answer": "The manager contacted the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The secretaries thanked the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors thanked the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The actor thanked the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor thanked the actor ."}
{"question": "The senators encouraged the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete encouraged the senators ."}
{"question": "The doctors encouraged the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents encouraged the doctors ."}
{"question": "The author thanked the judge .", "answer": "The judge thanked the author ."}
{"question": "The senator recognized the actors .", "answer": "The actors recognized the senator ."}
{"question": "The students admired the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor admired the students ."}
{"question": "The students called the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers called the students ."}
{"question": "The actors helped the professor .", "answer": "The professor helped the actors ."}
{"question": "The managers contacted the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries contacted the managers ."}
{"question": "The senator saw the artist .", "answer": "The artist saw the senator ."}
{"question": "The tourist stopped the managers near the scientist .", "answer": "The managers stopped the scientist ."}
{"question": "The tourist by the secretary introduced the students .", "answer": "The students introduced the tourist ."}
{"question": "The president mentioned the tourists near the senators .", "answer": "The senators mentioned the president ."}
{"question": "The managers by the president recognized the judge .", "answer": "The judge recognized the managers ."}
{"question": "The judge behind the authors avoided the scientists .", "answer": "The authors avoided the judge ."}
{"question": "The doctors next to the professor stopped the managers .", "answer": "The managers stopped the doctors ."}
{"question": "The artist called the actors near the doctors .", "answer": "The actors called the artist ."}
{"question": "The lawyer called the artists near the athlete .", "answer": "The artists called the athlete ."}
{"question": "The managers supported the lawyers next to the professor .", "answer": "The lawyers supported the managers ."}
{"question": "The artist believed the judge by the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist believed the artist ."}
{"question": "The professors next to the artists saw the judge .", "answer": "The judge saw the professors ."}
{"question": "The managers introduced the athletes behind the senator .", "answer": "The athletes introduced the managers ."}
{"question": "The actors helped the scientists near the student .", "answer": "The scientists helped the actors ."}
{"question": "The student encouraged the scientist near the judges .", "answer": "The scientist encouraged the judges ."}
{"question": "The secretary by the athlete contacted the bankers .", "answer": "The athlete contacted the secretary ."}
{"question": "The tourist believed the manager near the senators .", "answer": "The senators believed the tourist ."}
{"question": "The students behind the actors believed the presidents .", "answer": "The actors believed the students ."}
{"question": "The students by the scientists encouraged the senator .", "answer": "The senator encouraged the students ."}
{"question": "The lawyer helped the senator behind the judges .", "answer": "The senator helped the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The judge saw the athletes by the authors .", "answer": "The athletes saw the judge ."}
{"question": "The secretaries thanked the professors next to the president .", "answer": "The professors thanked the president ."}
{"question": "The professors behind the athletes supported the artists .", "answer": "The athletes supported the professors ."}
{"question": "The student introduced the senators next to the manager .", "answer": "The manager introduced the student ."}
{"question": "The lawyer by the senator avoided the judge .", "answer": "The judge avoided the senator ."}
{"question": "The banker by the managers saw the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents saw the managers ."}
{"question": "The doctors in front of the scientist recognized the banker .", "answer": "The scientist recognized the doctors ."}
{"question": "The tourist next to the author stopped the student .", "answer": "The author stopped the tourist ."}
{"question": "The tourist helped the artists by the professor .", "answer": "The artists helped the professor ."}
{"question": "The scientists in front of the author thanked the professor .", "answer": "The author thanked the scientists ."}
{"question": "The secretary encouraged the bankers next to the professor .", "answer": "The professor encouraged the secretary ."}
{"question": "The presidents called the manager next to the student .", "answer": "The manager called the presidents ."}
{"question": "The tourists next to the senators supported the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors supported the senators ."}
{"question": "The secretaries behind the lawyers recommended the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist recommended the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The artist in front of the scientists recommended the senator .", "answer": "The senator recommended the artist ."}
{"question": "The scientists by the tourists advised the student .", "answer": "The tourists advised the scientists ."}
{"question": "The author supported the managers in front of the students .", "answer": "The students supported the author ."}
{"question": "The author stopped the secretary next to the artist .", "answer": "The secretary stopped the artist ."}
{"question": "The judge behind the managers avoided the student .", "answer": "The managers avoided the judge ."}
{"question": "The judge behind the bankers mentioned the manager .", "answer": "The manager mentioned the judge ."}
{"question": "The athletes in front of the artist called the judge .", "answer": "The judge called the artist ."}
{"question": "The lawyer stopped the bankers behind the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor stopped the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The scientist by the judges called the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete called the scientist ."}
{"question": "The tourists avoided the athlete near the doctor .", "answer": "The athlete avoided the doctor ."}
{"question": "The authors near the president introduced the actor .", "answer": "The actor introduced the authors ."}
{"question": "The athlete near the scientist called the managers .", "answer": "The managers called the scientist ."}
{"question": "The students recommended the doctors near the author .", "answer": "The doctors recommended the students ."}
{"question": "The tourist near the actor believed the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete believed the actor ."}
{"question": "The athletes recommended the artists next to the bankers .", "answer": "The artists recommended the bankers ."}
{"question": "The students thanked the doctors in front of the senators .", "answer": "The doctors thanked the senators ."}
{"question": "The judge introduced the athletes behind the professor .", "answer": "The professor introduced the judge ."}
{"question": "The senator encouraged the secretaries in front of the scientists .", "answer": "The secretaries encouraged the scientists ."}
{"question": "The judges by the lawyer thanked the actor .", "answer": "The lawyer thanked the judges ."}
{"question": "The student admired the scientist next to the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete admired the student ."}
{"question": "The judges behind the lawyer called the professors .", "answer": "The professors called the judges ."}
{"question": "The lawyer next to the student recognized the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers recognized the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The scientist recommended the banker in front of the actor .", "answer": "The banker recommended the actor ."}
{"question": "The presidents contacted the student near the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors contacted the presidents ."}
{"question": "The athletes recommended the doctor next to the tourist .", "answer": "The doctor recommended the tourist ."}
{"question": "The artist near the manager avoided the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers avoided the artist ."}
{"question": "The actor called the doctor behind the athlete .", "answer": "The doctor called the actor ."}
{"question": "The secretary behind the actor believed the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist believed the actor ."}
{"question": "The secretaries stopped the authors next to the professors .", "answer": "The professors stopped the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The artists admired the lawyers in front of the actor .", "answer": "The lawyers admired the artists ."}
{"question": "The athlete in front of the presidents recommended the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers recommended the athlete ."}
{"question": "The artists in front of the secretary advised the doctor .", "answer": "The secretary advised the artists ."}
{"question": "The presidents in front of the judge advised the actor .", "answer": "The actor advised the presidents ."}
{"question": "The athlete encouraged the tourist in front of the senators .", "answer": "The tourist encouraged the athlete ."}
{"question": "The author in front of the secretaries saw the banker .", "answer": "The banker saw the author ."}
{"question": "The athlete introduced the senator behind the managers .", "answer": "The senator introduced the athlete ."}
{"question": "The artists in front of the student thanked the manager .", "answer": "The manager thanked the student ."}
{"question": "The doctor next to the scientist thanked the manager .", "answer": "The manager thanked the doctor ."}
{"question": "The president by the students called the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists called the president ."}
{"question": "The lawyers next to the actors helped the banker .", "answer": "The actors helped the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The artist next to the author admired the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries admired the artist ."}
{"question": "The judges thanked the professor in front of the authors .", "answer": "The authors thanked the judges ."}
{"question": "The actors by the presidents called the artist .", "answer": "The presidents called the actors ."}
{"question": "The artists in front of the managers helped the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers helped the managers ."}
{"question": "The athletes contacted the secretaries behind the senator .", "answer": "The secretaries contacted the athletes ."}
{"question": "The manager saw the actors next to the doctor .", "answer": "The actors saw the doctor ."}
{"question": "The artists introduced the managers near the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes introduced the artists ."}
{"question": "The authors next to the senator helped the banker .", "answer": "The banker helped the authors ."}
{"question": "The authors behind the judges mentioned the managers .", "answer": "The judges mentioned the authors ."}
{"question": "The professors stopped the bankers next to the tourist .", "answer": "The bankers stopped the professors ."}
{"question": "The actors behind the judge encouraged the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor encouraged the judge ."}
{"question": "The senators near the bankers recognized the athlete .", "answer": "The bankers recognized the senators ."}
{"question": "The tourists by the actors recommended the author .", "answer": "The actors recommended the tourists ."}
{"question": "The artists recommended the lawyer in front of the author .", "answer": "The author recommended the artists ."}
{"question": "The senators behind the judges admired the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist admired the senators ."}
{"question": "The doctors next to the manager avoided the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents avoided the manager ."}
{"question": "The actors behind the senators believed the artist .", "answer": "The artist believed the actors ."}
{"question": "The doctors stopped the athlete in front of the author .", "answer": "The athlete stopped the author ."}
{"question": "The tourist in front of the professors introduced the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes introduced the tourist ."}
{"question": "The doctor behind the lawyer saw the judge .", "answer": "The lawyer saw the doctor ."}
{"question": "The senator near the secretaries encouraged the tourists .", "answer": "The secretaries encouraged the senator ."}
{"question": "The senator near the doctor contacted the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary contacted the senator ."}
{"question": "The banker next to the authors helped the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents helped the banker ."}
{"question": "The actors recommended the author behind the presidents .", "answer": "The author recommended the actors ."}
{"question": "The banker stopped the manager near the student .", "answer": "The student stopped the banker ."}
{"question": "The authors in front of the tourist recommended the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries recommended the authors ."}
{"question": "The secretary thanked the athlete near the senators .", "answer": "The athlete thanked the senators ."}
{"question": "The tourists next to the presidents mentioned the student .", "answer": "The student mentioned the tourists ."}
{"question": "The tourists supported the professors next to the judges .", "answer": "The professors supported the tourists ."}
{"question": "The manager called the authors near the actor .", "answer": "The authors called the manager ."}
{"question": "The lawyers thanked the athlete by the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist thanked the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The actor near the president encouraged the senator .", "answer": "The senator encouraged the president ."}
{"question": "The banker recommended the students in front of the scientist .", "answer": "The students recommended the scientist ."}
{"question": "The manager believed the lawyer by the professor .", "answer": "The professor believed the manager ."}
{"question": "The lawyer mentioned the secretaries by the tourist .", "answer": "The secretaries mentioned the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The secretaries recommended the actor near the manager .", "answer": "The actor recommended the manager ."}
{"question": "The actors called the artists behind the president .", "answer": "The artists called the president ."}
{"question": "The senators in front of the presidents helped the authors .", "answer": "The authors helped the presidents ."}
{"question": "The professor in front of the students supported the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete supported the professor ."}
{"question": "The students saw the secretary in front of the professors .", "answer": "The secretary saw the students ."}
{"question": "The judge near the presidents admired the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor admired the presidents ."}
{"question": "The author supported the doctors near the artist .", "answer": "The doctors supported the author ."}
{"question": "The artists near the author mentioned the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists mentioned the author ."}
{"question": "The tourist avoided the scientist by the students .", "answer": "The scientist avoided the students ."}
{"question": "The bankers recommended the tourist near the athlete .", "answer": "The tourist recommended the bankers ."}
{"question": "The artist recognized the lawyer near the professors .", "answer": "The lawyer recognized the professors ."}
{"question": "The scientists next to the managers admired the bankers .", "answer": "The managers admired the scientists ."}
{"question": "The secretary helped the student by the senators .", "answer": "The student helped the senators ."}
{"question": "The authors in front of the athlete recommended the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists recommended the athlete ."}
{"question": "The author avoided the bankers by the senators .", "answer": "The bankers avoided the author ."}
{"question": "The managers next to the tourists introduced the judge .", "answer": "The tourists introduced the managers ."}
{"question": "The manager behind the author thanked the artist .", "answer": "The artist thanked the manager ."}
{"question": "The scientist by the actors encouraged the senators .", "answer": "The senators encouraged the actors ."}
{"question": "The athlete next to the professor admired the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries admired the athlete ."}
{"question": "The athletes recommended the senator near the artists .", "answer": "The senator recommended the artists ."}
{"question": "The scientist stopped the manager behind the lawyer .", "answer": "The manager stopped the scientist ."}
{"question": "The lawyer near the actors stopped the athlete .", "answer": "The actors stopped the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The secretary recognized the judges in front of the authors .", "answer": "The authors recognized the secretary ."}
{"question": "The judges recognized the authors behind the president .", "answer": "The authors recognized the president ."}
{"question": "The authors contacted the actors behind the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer contacted the authors ."}
{"question": "The artists contacted the professors near the student .", "answer": "The student contacted the artists ."}
{"question": "The president helped the professors by the managers .", "answer": "The professors helped the president ."}
{"question": "The athletes introduced the artists near the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers introduced the athletes ."}
{"question": "The presidents near the scientists believed the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries believed the presidents ."}
{"question": "The author thanked the athletes by the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers thanked the author ."}
{"question": "The doctor advised the scientists in front of the secretaries .", "answer": "The scientists advised the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The managers next to the tourists believed the artists .", "answer": "The artists believed the tourists ."}
{"question": "The bankers supported the doctor near the students .", "answer": "The doctor supported the students ."}
{"question": "The senators behind the manager advised the authors .", "answer": "The authors advised the manager ."}
{"question": "The professor encouraged the tourists by the doctors .", "answer": "The tourists encouraged the doctors ."}
{"question": "The authors encouraged the banker next to the secretary .", "answer": "The banker encouraged the secretary ."}
{"question": "The tourist by the author encouraged the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor encouraged the author ."}
{"question": "The tourists near the author saw the actors .", "answer": "The actors saw the tourists ."}
{"question": "The managers mentioned the lawyer next to the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers mentioned the managers ."}
{"question": "The professor helped the secretary in front of the actor .", "answer": "The secretary helped the professor ."}
{"question": "The lawyer helped the author in front of the banker .", "answer": "The author helped the banker ."}
{"question": "The actors called the secretary next to the athlete .", "answer": "The secretary called the athlete ."}
{"question": "The president near the artists supported the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist supported the president ."}
{"question": "The presidents next to the scientists saw the students .", "answer": "The scientists saw the presidents ."}
{"question": "The doctors believed the scientists next to the presidents .", "answer": "The scientists believed the doctors ."}
{"question": "The athlete believed the president near the judge .", "answer": "The president believed the judge ."}
{"question": "The lawyer helped the judges by the artist .", "answer": "The artist helped the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The artist advised the bankers behind the tourist .", "answer": "The bankers advised the artist ."}
{"question": "The scientist in front of the managers thanked the senators .", "answer": "The managers thanked the scientist ."}
{"question": "The actor by the artist supported the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors supported the actor ."}
{"question": "The managers stopped the athlete behind the secretary .", "answer": "The athlete stopped the secretary ."}
{"question": "The students near the author stopped the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete stopped the author ."}
{"question": "The artists thanked the secretaries by the author .", "answer": "The author thanked the artists ."}
{"question": "The presidents near the scientist believed the actors .", "answer": "The scientist believed the presidents ."}
{"question": "The scientists saw the professors behind the lawyer .", "answer": "The professors saw the scientists ."}
{"question": "The authors in front of the banker stopped the president .", "answer": "The president stopped the banker ."}
{"question": "The senator by the athletes thanked the actors .", "answer": "The athletes thanked the senator ."}
{"question": "The judge introduced the secretary behind the scientist .", "answer": "The secretary introduced the scientist ."}
{"question": "The tourists helped the secretaries behind the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor helped the tourists ."}
{"question": "The lawyers helped the author next to the scientists .", "answer": "The author helped the scientists ."}
{"question": "The artist recommended the senators by the student .", "answer": "The student recommended the artist ."}
{"question": "The author saw the bankers near the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer saw the author ."}
{"question": "The lawyers next to the scientist advised the president .", "answer": "The president advised the scientist ."}
{"question": "The manager by the senator supported the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary supported the manager ."}
{"question": "The actors next to the student called the authors .", "answer": "The student called the actors ."}
{"question": "The scientist introduced the senator in front of the professor .", "answer": "The senator introduced the scientist ."}
{"question": "The presidents near the tourists stopped the senator .", "answer": "The tourists stopped the presidents ."}
{"question": "The banker stopped the lawyers behind the authors .", "answer": "The authors stopped the banker ."}
{"question": "The managers in front of the actors called the authors .", "answer": "The authors called the managers ."}
{"question": "The banker saw the actors in front of the professors .", "answer": "The actors saw the banker ."}
{"question": "The president in front of the judges saw the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists saw the judges ."}
{"question": "The doctors stopped the presidents next to the lawyers .", "answer": "The presidents stopped the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The doctors saw the authors near the senator .", "answer": "The authors saw the senator ."}
{"question": "The professor near the senators contacted the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor contacted the professor ."}
{"question": "The judges stopped the presidents behind the manager .", "answer": "The presidents stopped the manager ."}
{"question": "The lawyers admired the student near the manager .", "answer": "The student admired the manager ."}
{"question": "The manager supported the presidents near the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists supported the manager ."}
{"question": "The secretaries called the senator next to the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents called the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The author called the secretary by the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes called the author ."}
{"question": "The student recognized the doctors behind the lawyers .", "answer": "The doctors recognized the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The actor avoided the doctor in front of the author .", "answer": "The author avoided the actor ."}
{"question": "The tourists advised the bankers next to the doctors .", "answer": "The bankers advised the doctors ."}
{"question": "The judge by the doctor contacted the president .", "answer": "The doctor contacted the judge ."}
{"question": "The senators supported the secretaries in front of the tourist .", "answer": "The secretaries supported the tourist ."}
{"question": "The lawyer contacted the senator by the athletes .", "answer": "The senator contacted the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The secretaries in front of the lawyers admired the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete admired the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The scientist in front of the professor thanked the bankers .", "answer": "The professor thanked the scientist ."}
{"question": "The professor in front of the student recommended the managers .", "answer": "The managers recommended the professor ."}
{"question": "The scientists advised the managers behind the author .", "answer": "The managers advised the author ."}
{"question": "The president called the judge in front of the athletes .", "answer": "The judge called the athletes ."}
{"question": "The senator behind the students stopped the judge .", "answer": "The judge stopped the senator ."}
{"question": "The tourists in front of the senator thanked the student .", "answer": "The student thanked the senator ."}
{"question": "The authors next to the doctors advised the banker .", "answer": "The banker advised the authors ."}
{"question": "The senator encouraged the tourist in front of the judge .", "answer": "The judge encouraged the senator ."}
{"question": "The artists behind the managers recommended the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists recommended the managers ."}
{"question": "The scientist in front of the secretary saw the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents saw the scientist ."}
{"question": "The doctors next to the professor advised the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes advised the doctors ."}
{"question": "The bankers recommended the managers by the scientist .", "answer": "The managers recommended the bankers ."}
{"question": "The artists mentioned the judges behind the secretary .", "answer": "The judges mentioned the artists ."}
{"question": "The scientists behind the managers avoided the judge .", "answer": "The judge avoided the managers ."}
{"question": "The judges next to the athlete thanked the student .", "answer": "The student thanked the athlete ."}
{"question": "The artists behind the student recommended the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents recommended the student ."}
{"question": "The president saw the authors in front of the athletes .", "answer": "The authors saw the athletes ."}
{"question": "The presidents avoided the students behind the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers avoided the presidents ."}
{"question": "The artists saw the secretaries in front of the tourist .", "answer": "The secretaries saw the tourist ."}
{"question": "The presidents near the professor recommended the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers recommended the professor ."}
{"question": "The tourist by the scientist mentioned the judges .", "answer": "The judges mentioned the tourist ."}
{"question": "The president in front of the scientists supported the secretaries .", "answer": "The scientists supported the president ."}
{"question": "The lawyers behind the professors supported the authors .", "answer": "The authors supported the professors ."}
{"question": "The manager believed the students in front of the scientist .", "answer": "The students believed the scientist ."}
{"question": "The doctors in front of the athletes contacted the judge .", "answer": "The judge contacted the athletes ."}
{"question": "The doctor avoided the scientists near the manager .", "answer": "The manager avoided the doctor ."}
{"question": "The president avoided the tourists near the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary avoided the president ."}
{"question": "The scientists helped the doctors in front of the authors .", "answer": "The doctors helped the authors ."}
{"question": "The judge called the student behind the senators .", "answer": "The student called the senators ."}
{"question": "The athlete by the actors believed the judge .", "answer": "The judge believed the athlete ."}
{"question": "The president called the scientists by the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers called the president ."}
{"question": "The secretaries near the managers recognized the authors .", "answer": "The managers recognized the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The president behind the tourist advised the artists .", "answer": "The artists advised the president ."}
{"question": "The student introduced the managers by the professors .", "answer": "The professors introduced the student ."}
{"question": "The doctors thanked the lawyer next to the senator .", "answer": "The senator thanked the doctors ."}
{"question": "The doctors next to the lawyer recommended the actor .", "answer": "The actor recommended the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The tourists by the bankers contacted the professor .", "answer": "The professor contacted the bankers ."}
{"question": "The judges believed the scientist next to the manager .", "answer": "The scientist believed the judges ."}
{"question": "The scientist saw the tourists behind the athletes .", "answer": "The tourists saw the scientist ."}
{"question": "The professor by the artists advised the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries advised the professor ."}
{"question": "The scientist introduced the judge behind the tourist .", "answer": "The judge introduced the tourist ."}
{"question": "The actors in front of the tourists stopped the judges .", "answer": "The judges stopped the tourists ."}
{"question": "The president by the doctor contacted the senator .", "answer": "The senator contacted the president ."}
{"question": "The author near the athletes supported the senators .", "answer": "The athletes supported the author ."}
{"question": "The artist by the manager advised the senators .", "answer": "The senators advised the manager ."}
{"question": "The president behind the artists admired the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries admired the president ."}
{"question": "The secretaries in front of the author thanked the judges .", "answer": "The judges thanked the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The tourist next to the judge mentioned the student .", "answer": "The student mentioned the judge ."}
{"question": "The students near the professors believed the artists .", "answer": "The artists believed the professors ."}
{"question": "The authors thanked the secretaries in front of the doctor .", "answer": "The secretaries thanked the authors ."}
{"question": "The artists in front of the presidents introduced the judges .", "answer": "The judges introduced the artists ."}
{"question": "The senators mentioned the doctor behind the lawyers .", "answer": "The doctor mentioned the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The lawyers in front of the author believed the senators .", "answer": "The senators believed the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The author in front of the tourists avoided the actors .", "answer": "The actors avoided the tourists ."}
{"question": "The artist mentioned the president next to the professor .", "answer": "The president mentioned the professor ."}
{"question": "The artists in front of the athletes called the author .", "answer": "The athletes called the artists ."}
{"question": "The president mentioned the professor behind the artist .", "answer": "The artist mentioned the president ."}
{"question": "The senators saw the tourist by the authors .", "answer": "The tourist saw the authors ."}
{"question": "The author by the judges saw the artists .", "answer": "The artists saw the author ."}
{"question": "The professor mentioned the scientists near the actors .", "answer": "The actors mentioned the professor ."}
{"question": "The senators saw the presidents near the artists .", "answer": "The artists saw the senators ."}
{"question": "The professor next to the scientists recommended the banker .", "answer": "The banker recommended the scientists ."}
{"question": "The senator next to the judge avoided the artists .", "answer": "The artists avoided the senator ."}
{"question": "The doctors supported the professor next to the bankers .", "answer": "The professor supported the bankers ."}
{"question": "The artist in front of the authors recognized the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete recognized the artist ."}
{"question": "The tourists near the banker supported the actor .", "answer": "The banker supported the tourists ."}
{"question": "The artist encouraged the student in front of the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries encouraged the artist ."}
{"question": "The judges introduced the bankers near the artists .", "answer": "The bankers introduced the artists ."}
{"question": "The bankers avoided the author near the judges .", "answer": "The author avoided the judges ."}
{"question": "The doctors near the senators helped the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete helped the doctors ."}
{"question": "The presidents in front of the doctor supported the student .", "answer": "The student supported the presidents ."}
{"question": "The secretaries next to the banker avoided the professor .", "answer": "The banker avoided the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The senators recommended the scientist near the lawyers .", "answer": "The scientist recommended the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The author next to the judge called the managers .", "answer": "The managers called the judge ."}
{"question": "The professors supported the lawyer by the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists supported the professors ."}
{"question": "The lawyers behind the athlete stopped the student .", "answer": "The student stopped the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The bankers in front of the author helped the doctor .", "answer": "The author helped the bankers ."}
{"question": "The scientists by the lawyer contacted the president .", "answer": "The president contacted the scientists ."}
{"question": "The presidents in front of the athletes introduced the judges .", "answer": "The athletes introduced the presidents ."}
{"question": "The lawyers saw the students near the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents saw the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The doctors avoided the student in front of the artists .", "answer": "The student avoided the doctors ."}
{"question": "The tourists recommended the artist near the authors .", "answer": "The artist recommended the tourists ."}
{"question": "The scientist next to the tourist admired the secretaries .", "answer": "The tourist admired the scientist ."}
{"question": "The manager admired the presidents near the doctor .", "answer": "The presidents admired the manager ."}
{"question": "The president behind the doctors called the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary called the president ."}
{"question": "The senators recommended the secretaries next to the actors .", "answer": "The actors recommended the senators ."}
{"question": "The banker believed the judges behind the students .", "answer": "The judges believed the banker ."}
{"question": "The doctors next to the banker advised the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary advised the doctors ."}
{"question": "The artists behind the banker mentioned the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist mentioned the artists ."}
{"question": "The manager thanked the banker near the lawyers .", "answer": "The banker thanked the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The manager saw the senators next to the scientists .", "answer": "The senators saw the scientists ."}
{"question": "The presidents stopped the athlete near the senators .", "answer": "The athlete stopped the senators ."}
{"question": "The banker recognized the scientist in front of the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors recognized the banker ."}
{"question": "The artist near the actor mentioned the president .", "answer": "The president mentioned the actor ."}
{"question": "The scientist near the professor stopped the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents stopped the scientist ."}
{"question": "The tourists saw the students next to the lawyer .", "answer": "The students saw the tourists ."}
{"question": "The secretary believed the senator behind the authors .", "answer": "The senator believed the authors ."}
{"question": "The athletes in front of the scientists advised the judges .", "answer": "The judges advised the athletes ."}
{"question": "The senator supported the artists near the authors .", "answer": "The artists supported the senator ."}
{"question": "The senators by the doctors mentioned the scientists .", "answer": "The doctors mentioned the senators ."}
{"question": "The authors near the professor saw the bankers .", "answer": "The professor saw the authors ."}
{"question": "The doctors recognized the athlete near the authors .", "answer": "The athlete recognized the doctors ."}
{"question": "The senator behind the judges thanked the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary thanked the judges ."}
{"question": "The student near the author encouraged the managers .", "answer": "The author encouraged the student ."}
{"question": "The secretaries saw the professors by the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists saw the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The professor by the author admired the students .", "answer": "The students admired the author ."}
{"question": "The artists in front of the author introduced the doctor .", "answer": "The author introduced the artists ."}
{"question": "The author by the actors helped the artists .", "answer": "The artists helped the author ."}
{"question": "The tourists helped the athlete near the secretary .", "answer": "The athlete helped the tourists ."}
{"question": "The judge in front of the actors mentioned the student .", "answer": "The student mentioned the judge ."}
{"question": "The author mentioned the manager next to the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors mentioned the author ."}
{"question": "The secretary stopped the banker next to the managers .", "answer": "The managers stopped the secretary ."}
{"question": "The artists called the tourist in front of the students .", "answer": "The tourist called the artists ."}
{"question": "The judge next to the professors saw the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists saw the professors ."}
{"question": "The scientists recommended the banker by the judge .", "answer": "The banker recommended the judge ."}
{"question": "The professor in front of the doctors supported the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists supported the doctors ."}
{"question": "The actor in front of the senator encouraged the secretaries .", "answer": "The senator encouraged the actor ."}
{"question": "The banker in front of the lawyer contacted the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete contacted the banker ."}
{"question": "The senator near the student avoided the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes avoided the senator ."}
{"question": "The scientist behind the author supported the manager .", "answer": "The author supported the scientist ."}
{"question": "The doctor behind the student supported the manager .", "answer": "The student supported the doctor ."}
{"question": "The bankers behind the professors introduced the athletes .", "answer": "The professors introduced the bankers ."}
{"question": "The lawyers thanked the judges by the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries thanked the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The student near the doctor introduced the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists introduced the doctor ."}
{"question": "The senator contacted the artist near the judges .", "answer": "The artist contacted the senator ."}
{"question": "The athletes supported the managers in front of the lawyers .", "answer": "The managers supported the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The actor supported the managers in front of the tourist .", "answer": "The managers supported the actor ."}
{"question": "The president near the authors believed the judge .", "answer": "The judge believed the president ."}
{"question": "The tourists near the doctors thanked the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers thanked the doctors ."}
{"question": "The secretary advised the manager next to the judge .", "answer": "The judge advised the secretary ."}
{"question": "The professors contacted the bankers next to the artist .", "answer": "The artist contacted the professors ."}
{"question": "The artists recommended the senators by the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists recommended the artists ."}
{"question": "The athlete behind the lawyers mentioned the banker .", "answer": "The lawyers mentioned the athlete ."}
{"question": "The manager supported the judge near the tourists .", "answer": "The judge supported the tourists ."}
{"question": "The professor mentioned the secretary by the senator .", "answer": "The secretary mentioned the senator ."}
{"question": "The author contacted the actors behind the student .", "answer": "The actors contacted the student ."}
{"question": "The actors behind the professor believed the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary believed the actors ."}
{"question": "The professor recognized the tourist next to the managers .", "answer": "The tourist recognized the professor ."}
{"question": "The actors near the judges advised the students .", "answer": "The students advised the actors ."}
{"question": "The student by the artist saw the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists saw the artist ."}
{"question": "The doctors next to the scientists encouraged the professor .", "answer": "The professor encouraged the doctors ."}
{"question": "The authors near the tourist introduced the artist .", "answer": "The artist introduced the authors ."}
{"question": "The judges saw the senators next to the lawyer .", "answer": "The senators saw the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The athletes thanked the professors behind the artist .", "answer": "The professors thanked the artist ."}
{"question": "The tourist by the senators saw the president .", "answer": "The president saw the senators ."}
{"question": "The authors by the lawyer saw the senator .", "answer": "The lawyer saw the authors ."}
{"question": "The athletes behind the scientist believed the actor .", "answer": "The actor believed the scientist ."}
{"question": "The doctor by the senators encouraged the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries encouraged the senators ."}
{"question": "The banker behind the senators stopped the tourists .", "answer": "The senators stopped the banker ."}
{"question": "The lawyer behind the authors stopped the professor .", "answer": "The professor stopped the authors ."}
{"question": "The senators saw the presidents behind the artist .", "answer": "The presidents saw the senators ."}
{"question": "The banker thanked the manager behind the professors .", "answer": "The manager thanked the professors ."}
{"question": "The authors next to the senator called the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents called the authors ."}
{"question": "The presidents behind the student advised the actors .", "answer": "The actors advised the presidents ."}
{"question": "The judge near the secretary advised the professor .", "answer": "The professor advised the judge ."}
{"question": "The judges introduced the artist in front of the professor .", "answer": "The artist introduced the judges ."}
{"question": "The scientists contacted the professor behind the artists .", "answer": "The artists contacted the scientists ."}
{"question": "The judges avoided the secretary next to the tourist .", "answer": "The secretary avoided the judges ."}
{"question": "The scientist near the manager contacted the bankers .", "answer": "The manager contacted the scientist ."}
{"question": "The artist in front of the secretary contacted the manager .", "answer": "The manager contacted the secretary ."}
{"question": "The athletes next to the doctor encouraged the professors .", "answer": "The professors encouraged the athletes ."}
{"question": "The professors in front of the tourist supported the banker .", "answer": "The tourist supported the professors ."}
{"question": "The senators admired the professors next to the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete admired the senators ."}
{"question": "The doctor in front of the athlete thanked the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists thanked the doctor ."}
{"question": "The tourist advised the managers behind the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes advised the tourist ."}
{"question": "The students next to the tourist believed the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries believed the students ."}
{"question": "The lawyer in front of the professor called the actors .", "answer": "The professor called the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The doctors by the actor called the president .", "answer": "The president called the doctors ."}
{"question": "The authors believed the banker near the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists believed the authors ."}
{"question": "The professors mentioned the scientist in front of the athletes .", "answer": "The scientist mentioned the professors ."}
{"question": "The doctors stopped the senator behind the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete stopped the doctors ."}
{"question": "The managers advised the authors next to the lawyers .", "answer": "The authors advised the managers ."}
{"question": "The professor supported the actor behind the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist supported the professor ."}
{"question": "The managers in front of the athletes introduced the senators .", "answer": "The senators introduced the athletes ."}
{"question": "The artist in front of the president introduced the scientists .", "answer": "The president introduced the artist ."}
{"question": "The tourists saw the senator behind the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary saw the tourists ."}
{"question": "The doctors admired the senator near the student .", "answer": "The senator admired the student ."}
{"question": "The bankers by the doctors thanked the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist thanked the bankers ."}
{"question": "The tourists avoided the president next to the artists .", "answer": "The president avoided the tourists ."}
{"question": "The judges in front of the students advised the professors .", "answer": "The students advised the judges ."}
{"question": "The actor encouraged the secretaries in front of the president .", "answer": "The secretaries encouraged the president ."}
{"question": "The presidents in front of the scientist recognized the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers recognized the presidents ."}
{"question": "The lawyers helped the professors by the athletes .", "answer": "The professors helped the athletes ."}
{"question": "The artist in front of the lawyer helped the judge .", "answer": "The judge helped the artist ."}
{"question": "The athlete avoided the artist near the student .", "answer": "The artist avoided the student ."}
{"question": "The athletes contacted the scientists by the author .", "answer": "The author contacted the athletes ."}
{"question": "The manager supported the judge next to the athlete .", "answer": "The judge supported the athlete ."}
{"question": "The scientist by the author admired the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist admired the scientist ."}
{"question": "The secretary supported the athlete near the tourists .", "answer": "The athlete supported the tourists ."}
{"question": "The scientists advised the doctor by the secretary .", "answer": "The doctor advised the scientists ."}
{"question": "The actors recognized the professors by the artists .", "answer": "The professors recognized the actors ."}
{"question": "The artist behind the actors helped the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers helped the artist ."}
{"question": "The banker introduced the professors in front of the judges .", "answer": "The professors introduced the banker ."}
{"question": "The judges next to the tourist mentioned the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor mentioned the judges ."}
{"question": "The professors behind the students encouraged the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer encouraged the professors ."}
{"question": "The athletes in front of the tourists believed the scientists .", "answer": "The tourists believed the athletes ."}
{"question": "The scientist near the professor avoided the president .", "answer": "The president avoided the professor ."}
{"question": "The doctor near the scientist admired the judges .", "answer": "The judges admired the scientist ."}
{"question": "The senators stopped the actors next to the judges .", "answer": "The actors stopped the senators ."}
{"question": "The author behind the athletes contacted the actors .", "answer": "The athletes contacted the author ."}
{"question": "The senators behind the athletes admired the banker .", "answer": "The athletes admired the senators ."}
{"question": "The student admired the judges in front of the managers .", "answer": "The judges admired the student ."}
{"question": "The tourists recognized the lawyers behind the judge .", "answer": "The lawyers recognized the judge ."}
{"question": "The presidents in front of the actor admired the senator .", "answer": "The senator admired the presidents ."}
{"question": "The student next to the banker mentioned the artist .", "answer": "The artist mentioned the banker ."}
{"question": "The doctors admired the managers in front of the banker .", "answer": "The managers admired the banker ."}
{"question": "The tourists next to the lawyers believed the judge .", "answer": "The lawyers believed the tourists ."}
{"question": "The athletes in front of the actor advised the senators .", "answer": "The senators advised the athletes ."}
{"question": "The secretary thanked the senators by the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete thanked the secretary ."}
{"question": "The author avoided the senator by the scientists .", "answer": "The senator avoided the scientists ."}
{"question": "The athlete near the judges advised the scientist .", "answer": "The judges advised the athlete ."}
{"question": "The scientists behind the athlete encouraged the actor .", "answer": "The athlete encouraged the scientists ."}
{"question": "The authors near the presidents admired the actor .", "answer": "The actor admired the presidents ."}
{"question": "The actor near the senator supported the judge .", "answer": "The judge supported the senator ."}
{"question": "The scientist called the manager behind the authors .", "answer": "The manager called the authors ."}
{"question": "The senator helped the manager behind the tourist .", "answer": "The manager helped the tourist ."}
{"question": "The athletes behind the author supported the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents supported the author ."}
{"question": "The managers called the authors behind the artist .", "answer": "The artist called the managers ."}
{"question": "The secretary in front of the doctor thanked the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents thanked the secretary ."}
{"question": "The judge introduced the lawyers near the artists .", "answer": "The lawyers introduced the artists ."}
{"question": "The managers helped the scientists near the doctor .", "answer": "The scientists helped the doctor ."}
{"question": "The lawyers encouraged the tourists in front of the student .", "answer": "The student encouraged the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The secretaries near the athletes contacted the author .", "answer": "The author contacted the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The bankers behind the manager stopped the senators .", "answer": "The manager stopped the bankers ."}
{"question": "The judge introduced the senator next to the artist .", "answer": "The senator introduced the judge ."}
{"question": "The judge advised the lawyer next to the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete advised the judge ."}
{"question": "The author believed the bankers behind the manager .", "answer": "The manager believed the author ."}
{"question": "The athletes by the student called the scientists .", "answer": "The student called the athletes ."}
{"question": "The actors saw the professor near the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists saw the actors ."}
{"question": "The doctors recommended the authors behind the manager .", "answer": "The authors recommended the doctors ."}
{"question": "The judges next to the students recognized the artists .", "answer": "The students recognized the judges ."}
{"question": "The judges recommended the lawyers in front of the doctors .", "answer": "The lawyers recommended the judges ."}
{"question": "The artists behind the banker contacted the senators .", "answer": "The senators contacted the artists ."}
{"question": "The student avoided the actor by the scientist .", "answer": "The actor avoided the scientist ."}
{"question": "The secretaries mentioned the professor next to the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors mentioned the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The senator next to the actors saw the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor saw the actors ."}
{"question": "The artist mentioned the presidents behind the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer mentioned the artist ."}
{"question": "The senator by the secretary recommended the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors recommended the secretary ."}
{"question": "The president recognized the athletes near the senators .", "answer": "The athletes recognized the president ."}
{"question": "The senators supported the professor by the doctors .", "answer": "The professor supported the senators ."}
{"question": "The artists next to the tourists admired the student .", "answer": "The tourists admired the artists ."}
{"question": "The tourist next to the lawyer helped the professor .", "answer": "The professor helped the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The judges recommended the senators next to the managers .", "answer": "The managers recommended the judges ."}
{"question": "The professor in front of the actors helped the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist helped the actors ."}
{"question": "The tourists thanked the president near the doctors .", "answer": "The president thanked the tourists ."}
{"question": "The student by the lawyer advised the athlete .", "answer": "The lawyer advised the student ."}
{"question": "The tourists next to the doctors recognized the senator .", "answer": "The doctors recognized the tourists ."}
{"question": "The scientist stopped the secretaries by the actors .", "answer": "The actors stopped the scientist ."}
{"question": "The judge contacted the banker in front of the author .", "answer": "The banker contacted the author ."}
{"question": "The athletes behind the bankers called the artists .", "answer": "The artists called the bankers ."}
{"question": "The authors behind the students encouraged the managers .", "answer": "The managers encouraged the students ."}
{"question": "The artist admired the secretary in front of the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist admired the artist ."}
{"question": "The president in front of the managers saw the students .", "answer": "The students saw the president ."}
{"question": "The authors behind the doctors advised the banker .", "answer": "The banker advised the doctors ."}
{"question": "The secretaries near the students thanked the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist thanked the students ."}
{"question": "The secretaries recommended the authors next to the managers .", "answer": "The managers recommended the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The senator behind the banker stopped the student .", "answer": "The student stopped the senator ."}
{"question": "The secretaries next to the students called the doctor .", "answer": "The students called the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The lawyers behind the senator advised the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary advised the senator ."}
{"question": "The scientist next to the authors avoided the professors .", "answer": "The authors avoided the scientist ."}
{"question": "The secretaries in front of the artists stopped the senator .", "answer": "The senator stopped the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The tourist in front of the athletes stopped the manager .", "answer": "The manager stopped the tourist ."}
{"question": "The doctor introduced the scientists near the lawyers .", "answer": "The scientists introduced the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The scientist behind the students recognized the judge .", "answer": "The students recognized the scientist ."}
{"question": "The manager stopped the lawyers by the professor .", "answer": "The lawyers stopped the professor ."}
{"question": "The artist mentioned the authors behind the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer mentioned the artist ."}
{"question": "The authors behind the athletes encouraged the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries encouraged the athletes ."}
{"question": "The president next to the doctor thanked the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist thanked the doctor ."}
{"question": "The artists next to the actor thanked the managers .", "answer": "The managers thanked the actor ."}
{"question": "The secretaries in front of the senators supported the banker .", "answer": "The senators supported the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The lawyers behind the author saw the student .", "answer": "The student saw the author ."}
{"question": "The senator by the artists helped the managers .", "answer": "The managers helped the senator ."}
{"question": "The secretary near the senators saw the managers .", "answer": "The senators saw the secretary ."}
{"question": "The secretaries mentioned the actor by the doctor .", "answer": "The actor mentioned the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The students mentioned the doctors behind the scientist .", "answer": "The doctors mentioned the students ."}
{"question": "The actors introduced the lawyers in front of the president .", "answer": "The lawyers introduced the actors ."}
{"question": "The scientists supported the senator behind the author .", "answer": "The senator supported the scientists ."}
{"question": "The senators introduced the scientists next to the author .", "answer": "The scientists introduced the author ."}
{"question": "The secretaries in front of the tourists saw the judge .", "answer": "The judge saw the tourists ."}
{"question": "The actors in front of the lawyer saw the artists .", "answer": "The artists saw the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The secretary by the judge avoided the athlete .", "answer": "The judge avoided the secretary ."}
{"question": "The athlete thanked the bankers by the senator .", "answer": "The senator thanked the athlete ."}
{"question": "The lawyer admired the doctors near the author .", "answer": "The doctors admired the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The lawyers near the student recommended the artist .", "answer": "The artist recommended the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The students next to the doctor encouraged the artists .", "answer": "The doctor encouraged the students ."}
{"question": "The professor advised the scientists in front of the judges .", "answer": "The scientists advised the judges ."}
{"question": "The banker contacted the artist by the student .", "answer": "The artist contacted the banker ."}
{"question": "The president supported the senators next to the managers .", "answer": "The senators supported the president ."}
{"question": "The tourist by the professor recommended the senator .", "answer": "The senator recommended the professor ."}
{"question": "The artists avoided the secretaries behind the senators .", "answer": "The secretaries avoided the senators ."}
{"question": "The judge in front of the lawyers stopped the professors .", "answer": "The professors stopped the judge ."}
{"question": "The scientist supported the athletes in front of the manager .", "answer": "The manager supported the scientist ."}
{"question": "The scientists next to the judges introduced the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors introduced the scientists ."}
{"question": "The managers by the judge introduced the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary introduced the managers ."}
{"question": "The athlete by the tourists recommended the senator .", "answer": "The senator recommended the tourists ."}
{"question": "The senator saw the judge near the managers .", "answer": "The judge saw the senator ."}
{"question": "The professor advised the senator behind the judge .", "answer": "The senator advised the judge ."}
{"question": "The student advised the bankers near the authors .", "answer": "The bankers advised the authors ."}
{"question": "The lawyer by the professor avoided the bankers .", "answer": "The professor avoided the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The student in front of the secretaries avoided the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors avoided the student ."}
{"question": "The actor stopped the doctors in front of the professor .", "answer": "The doctors stopped the actor ."}
{"question": "The judge called the lawyer next to the athlete .", "answer": "The lawyer called the judge ."}
{"question": "The presidents near the authors recognized the students .", "answer": "The authors recognized the presidents ."}
{"question": "The athletes by the authors stopped the lawyer .", "answer": "The authors stopped the athletes ."}
{"question": "The actors by the professor recognized the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers recognized the actors ."}
{"question": "The secretary behind the manager introduced the judges .", "answer": "The judges introduced the manager ."}
{"question": "The athletes next to the actor believed the president .", "answer": "The president believed the athletes ."}
{"question": "The presidents helped the professor behind the doctor .", "answer": "The professor helped the presidents ."}
{"question": "The lawyers next to the judges mentioned the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers mentioned the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The tourists near the judge stopped the president .", "answer": "The president stopped the judge ."}
{"question": "The judge next to the manager introduced the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes introduced the manager ."}
{"question": "The professor next to the lawyers helped the judge .", "answer": "The judge helped the professor ."}
{"question": "The lawyers in front of the judge advised the doctor .", "answer": "The judge advised the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The lawyers behind the senator introduced the manager .", "answer": "The manager introduced the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The bankers contacted the actor near the doctors .", "answer": "The actor contacted the doctors ."}
{"question": "The tourists near the athlete avoided the judges .", "answer": "The athlete avoided the tourists ."}
{"question": "The judges in front of the senator contacted the athlete .", "answer": "The senator contacted the judges ."}
{"question": "The athlete in front of the judges called the author .", "answer": "The author called the athlete ."}
{"question": "The students believed the judges next to the secretary .", "answer": "The judges believed the students ."}
{"question": "The students recognized the judges near the bankers .", "answer": "The judges recognized the bankers ."}
{"question": "The judge contacted the professors near the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors contacted the judge ."}
{"question": "The managers by the artist mentioned the presidents .", "answer": "The artist mentioned the managers ."}
{"question": "The authors admired the professor in front of the senator .", "answer": "The professor admired the authors ."}
{"question": "The scientist thanked the senators behind the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors thanked the scientist ."}
{"question": "The actor believed the presidents near the doctors .", "answer": "The presidents believed the actor ."}
{"question": "The lawyer in front of the judge believed the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents believed the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The presidents near the actor stopped the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists stopped the presidents ."}
{"question": "The secretary advised the doctors in front of the tourists .", "answer": "The doctors advised the secretary ."}
{"question": "The lawyer advised the actors behind the authors .", "answer": "The actors advised the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The managers next to the artist thanked the professor .", "answer": "The professor thanked the artist ."}
{"question": "The professor by the manager introduced the judge .", "answer": "The judge introduced the manager ."}
{"question": "The scientist by the professors mentioned the artists .", "answer": "The artists mentioned the professors ."}
{"question": "The doctor near the president thanked the manager .", "answer": "The president thanked the doctor ."}
{"question": "The banker introduced the doctors behind the tourist .", "answer": "The doctors introduced the banker ."}
{"question": "The actors admired the students next to the judge .", "answer": "The students admired the actors ."}
{"question": "The secretaries in front of the doctor contacted the professors .", "answer": "The professors contacted the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The student supported the scientists by the secretaries .", "answer": "The scientists supported the student ."}
{"question": "The banker in front of the athlete helped the authors .", "answer": "The athlete helped the banker ."}
{"question": "The artist recognized the scientist near the bankers .", "answer": "The scientist recognized the bankers ."}
{"question": "The presidents by the student avoided the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers avoided the student ."}
{"question": "The president next to the scientists helped the professors .", "answer": "The scientists helped the president ."}
{"question": "The scientist contacted the artists next to the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers contacted the scientist ."}
{"question": "The manager in front of the banker believed the actor .", "answer": "The banker believed the manager ."}
{"question": "The student near the manager thanked the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists thanked the student ."}
{"question": "The professors encouraged the student in front of the secretaries .", "answer": "The student encouraged the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The managers near the student recognized the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist recognized the student ."}
{"question": "The authors encouraged the judges near the manager .", "answer": "The judges encouraged the authors ."}
{"question": "The artists by the president believed the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor believed the president ."}
{"question": "The actors believed the athlete in front of the artists .", "answer": "The athlete believed the actors ."}
{"question": "The senators near the managers recommended the artists .", "answer": "The artists recommended the managers ."}
{"question": "The athlete by the actor advised the student .", "answer": "The student advised the actor ."}
{"question": "The athlete avoided the judges by the students .", "answer": "The students avoided the athlete ."}
{"question": "The scientist encouraged the secretaries in front of the lawyers .", "answer": "The secretaries encouraged the scientist ."}
{"question": "The president encouraged the secretary near the senators .", "answer": "The secretary encouraged the senators ."}
{"question": "The secretary mentioned the artists next to the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers mentioned the secretary ."}
{"question": "The scientists next to the secretary avoided the professors .", "answer": "The professors avoided the scientists ."}
{"question": "The manager advised the students next to the artist .", "answer": "The artist advised the manager ."}
{"question": "The author stopped the judge next to the artists .", "answer": "The artists stopped the author ."}
{"question": "The athletes next to the judge recommended the senator .", "answer": "The senator recommended the judge ."}
{"question": "The athletes advised the secretary near the judges .", "answer": "The judges advised the athletes ."}
{"question": "The actor called the professor near the managers .", "answer": "The managers called the actor ."}
{"question": "The scientist helped the manager behind the doctor .", "answer": "The manager helped the scientist ."}
{"question": "The student behind the professors avoided the artist .", "answer": "The artist avoided the student ."}
{"question": "The athletes behind the lawyer supported the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries supported the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The manager near the tourists encouraged the president .", "answer": "The tourists encouraged the manager ."}
{"question": "The lawyers recognized the doctors by the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary recognized the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The authors behind the student saw the professors .", "answer": "The student saw the authors ."}
{"question": "The scientists behind the senator recommended the artist .", "answer": "The artist recommended the scientists ."}
{"question": "The tourist in front of the scientist introduced the authors .", "answer": "The authors introduced the tourist ."}
{"question": "The authors encouraged the professors by the senators .", "answer": "The professors encouraged the senators ."}
{"question": "The lawyers near the actors contacted the judge .", "answer": "The actors contacted the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The tourists advised the scientist in front of the student .", "answer": "The student advised the tourists ."}
{"question": "The senator avoided the author near the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete avoided the senator ."}
{"question": "The athletes in front of the doctors encouraged the actor .", "answer": "The doctors encouraged the athletes ."}
{"question": "The lawyer admired the author behind the students .", "answer": "The author admired the students ."}
{"question": "The doctors contacted the bankers behind the professors .", "answer": "The professors contacted the doctors ."}
{"question": "The doctor introduced the scientist in front of the managers .", "answer": "The scientist introduced the doctor ."}
{"question": "The lawyers encouraged the senator behind the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists encouraged the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The senators recognized the managers in front of the tourist .", "answer": "The managers recognized the tourist ."}
{"question": "The banker by the tourist helped the professor .", "answer": "The professor helped the banker ."}
{"question": "The judge saw the secretary by the students .", "answer": "The secretary saw the judge ."}
{"question": "The bankers next to the president avoided the tourist .", "answer": "The president avoided the bankers ."}
{"question": "The doctors supported the student near the president .", "answer": "The president supported the doctors ."}
{"question": "The student saw the president near the managers .", "answer": "The president saw the managers ."}
{"question": "The athletes called the artist next to the manager .", "answer": "The artist called the manager ."}
{"question": "The actor in front of the professor supported the lawyer .", "answer": "The professor supported the actor ."}
{"question": "The president encouraged the actor next to the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist encouraged the president ."}
{"question": "The bankers thanked the doctor in front of the secretary .", "answer": "The doctor thanked the bankers ."}
{"question": "The president thanked the actors next to the doctors .", "answer": "The actors thanked the president ."}
{"question": "The secretary in front of the tourist thanked the student .", "answer": "The student thanked the tourist ."}
{"question": "The author by the actor advised the lawyer .", "answer": "The actor advised the author ."}
{"question": "The lawyer behind the manager believed the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete believed the manager ."}
{"question": "The doctors next to the secretary avoided the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents avoided the doctors ."}
{"question": "The scientist believed the bankers by the senator .", "answer": "The bankers believed the scientist ."}
{"question": "The judge saw the senators by the author .", "answer": "The author saw the judge ."}
{"question": "The artists mentioned the students in front of the scientist .", "answer": "The students mentioned the scientist ."}
{"question": "The tourist avoided the students in front of the scientist .", "answer": "The students avoided the scientist ."}
{"question": "The lawyer called the senator in front of the president .", "answer": "The senator called the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The professors saw the senators next to the athlete .", "answer": "The senators saw the athlete ."}
{"question": "The president by the professors advised the actors .", "answer": "The actors advised the professors ."}
{"question": "The scientist introduced the doctors near the athlete .", "answer": "The doctors introduced the scientist ."}
{"question": "The professor next to the manager recommended the banker .", "answer": "The banker recommended the manager ."}
{"question": "The manager avoided the actor next to the scientist .", "answer": "The actor avoided the manager ."}
{"question": "The secretary by the author encouraged the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist encouraged the author ."}
{"question": "The presidents by the managers stopped the professor .", "answer": "The professor stopped the managers ."}
{"question": "The students admired the professor in front of the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists admired the students ."}
{"question": "The judges near the actors introduced the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents introduced the judges ."}
{"question": "The actor behind the scientist supported the authors .", "answer": "The authors supported the actor ."}
{"question": "The manager encouraged the bankers near the tourist .", "answer": "The bankers encouraged the tourist ."}
{"question": "The author advised the manager in front of the actor .", "answer": "The manager advised the author ."}
{"question": "The senator stopped the president near the actor .", "answer": "The actor stopped the senator ."}
{"question": "The banker avoided the senator near the managers .", "answer": "The senator avoided the managers ."}
{"question": "The tourists in front of the doctors believed the judge .", "answer": "The judge believed the doctors ."}
{"question": "The scientist by the bankers saw the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries saw the scientist ."}
{"question": "The authors called the manager behind the tourists .", "answer": "The manager called the tourists ."}
{"question": "The secretaries encouraged the tourists behind the managers .", "answer": "The managers encouraged the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The manager next to the actor introduced the secretary .", "answer": "The actor introduced the manager ."}
{"question": "The scientists mentioned the artists near the bankers .", "answer": "The artists mentioned the scientists ."}
{"question": "The secretary in front of the athletes recognized the senator .", "answer": "The senator recognized the athletes ."}
{"question": "The authors believed the secretaries next to the senator .", "answer": "The senator believed the authors ."}
{"question": "The lawyer near the scientist believed the president .", "answer": "The scientist believed the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The athletes called the senators next to the authors .", "answer": "The authors called the athletes ."}
{"question": "The athlete advised the tourist behind the managers .", "answer": "The managers advised the athlete ."}
{"question": "The secretaries stopped the president next to the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist stopped the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The professor helped the scientist next to the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents helped the professor ."}
{"question": "The professor next to the senator recommended the artists .", "answer": "The artists recommended the professor ."}
{"question": "The artist in front of the author helped the presidents .", "answer": "The author helped the artist ."}
{"question": "The artist by the banker supported the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete supported the artist ."}
{"question": "The manager mentioned the professor near the actors .", "answer": "The professor mentioned the actors ."}
{"question": "The athletes by the artists thanked the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers thanked the athletes ."}
{"question": "The authors supported the professor next to the banker .", "answer": "The professor supported the authors ."}
{"question": "The authors recommended the athletes by the scientist .", "answer": "The athletes recommended the authors ."}
{"question": "The tourists helped the secretary by the banker .", "answer": "The secretary helped the tourists ."}
{"question": "The artists in front of the authors introduced the banker .", "answer": "The banker introduced the authors ."}
{"question": "The tourists behind the managers encouraged the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary encouraged the tourists ."}
{"question": "The artist by the tourist encouraged the author .", "answer": "The author encouraged the artist ."}
{"question": "The judges behind the bankers believed the professors .", "answer": "The bankers believed the judges ."}
{"question": "The athletes stopped the president near the senators .", "answer": "The president stopped the athletes ."}
{"question": "The secretaries encouraged the bankers next to the professor .", "answer": "The bankers encouraged the professor ."}
{"question": "The president saw the student by the bankers .", "answer": "The student saw the president ."}
{"question": "The artist recognized the doctors behind the secretaries .", "answer": "The doctors recognized the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The lawyer in front of the judges recommended the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes recommended the judges ."}
{"question": "The managers by the lawyers contacted the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists contacted the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The actors introduced the athletes in front of the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor introduced the actors ."}
{"question": "The professors next to the senator introduced the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists introduced the professors ."}
{"question": "The students supported the senator next to the judge .", "answer": "The senator supported the students ."}
{"question": "The banker next to the professors encouraged the judges .", "answer": "The judges encouraged the banker ."}
{"question": "The tourist admired the secretary in front of the student .", "answer": "The student admired the tourist ."}
{"question": "The professor avoided the scientists in front of the lawyers .", "answer": "The scientists avoided the professor ."}
{"question": "The lawyers avoided the authors near the scientists .", "answer": "The authors avoided the scientists ."}
{"question": "The professor behind the athletes saw the author .", "answer": "The athletes saw the professor ."}
{"question": "The tourists thanked the students by the secretaries .", "answer": "The students thanked the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The secretary called the artist near the senators .", "answer": "The artist called the secretary ."}
{"question": "The presidents behind the secretaries saw the senator .", "answer": "The senator saw the presidents ."}
{"question": "The students introduced the senators next to the professors .", "answer": "The senators introduced the students ."}
{"question": "The athletes behind the manager admired the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary admired the manager ."}
{"question": "The author thanked the athletes by the senator .", "answer": "The athletes thanked the author ."}
{"question": "The lawyer stopped the tourist next to the managers .", "answer": "The tourist stopped the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The professor by the secretary supported the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer supported the secretary ."}
{"question": "The judges near the artist contacted the tourists .", "answer": "The artist contacted the judges ."}
{"question": "The banker advised the scientists by the actor .", "answer": "The scientists advised the banker ."}
{"question": "The authors in front of the secretaries encouraged the professors .", "answer": "The professors encouraged the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The judge in front of the scientist supported the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes supported the judge ."}
{"question": "The author in front of the lawyer recommended the senator .", "answer": "The senator recommended the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The doctors encouraged the senator near the managers .", "answer": "The senator encouraged the managers ."}
{"question": "The lawyers thanked the professors behind the actors .", "answer": "The actors thanked the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The judges behind the secretary thanked the author .", "answer": "The secretary thanked the judges ."}
{"question": "The professor behind the scientists helped the lawyer .", "answer": "The scientists helped the professor ."}
{"question": "The manager saw the artist by the tourist .", "answer": "The artist saw the manager ."}
{"question": "The secretaries near the artist called the actors .", "answer": "The actors called the artist ."}
{"question": "The president behind the lawyers thanked the actor .", "answer": "The actor thanked the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The bankers in front of the tourist avoided the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors avoided the bankers ."}
{"question": "The banker called the senator by the tourists .", "answer": "The senator called the tourists ."}
{"question": "The professors introduced the artist in front of the banker .", "answer": "The banker introduced the professors ."}
{"question": "The senators called the student next to the president .", "answer": "The student called the senators ."}
{"question": "The senator believed the tourist by the artist .", "answer": "The tourist believed the artist ."}
{"question": "The actor helped the secretary near the athletes .", "answer": "The secretary helped the actor ."}
{"question": "The tourists recognized the lawyers next to the doctors .", "answer": "The lawyers recognized the tourists ."}
{"question": "The lawyers introduced the bankers next to the judges .", "answer": "The bankers introduced the judges ."}
{"question": "The artists called the tourists near the doctor .", "answer": "The tourists called the artists ."}
{"question": "The athlete in front of the tourists advised the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary advised the athlete ."}
{"question": "The lawyers mentioned the presidents in front of the manager .", "answer": "The presidents mentioned the manager ."}
{"question": "The presidents contacted the doctor near the artist .", "answer": "The doctor contacted the presidents ."}
{"question": "The authors helped the judge behind the secretaries .", "answer": "The judge helped the authors ."}
{"question": "The students supported the scientists behind the doctors .", "answer": "The scientists supported the doctors ."}
{"question": "The senator supported the tourists behind the lawyer .", "answer": "The tourists supported the senator ."}
{"question": "The actor near the tourists called the managers .", "answer": "The managers called the tourists ."}
{"question": "The lawyer believed the athletes near the president .", "answer": "The athletes believed the president ."}
{"question": "The authors near the secretaries contacted the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes contacted the authors ."}
{"question": "The athletes thanked the author behind the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers thanked the athletes ."}
{"question": "The doctors by the presidents advised the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists advised the doctors ."}
{"question": "The artist near the judge advised the scientist .", "answer": "The judge advised the artist ."}
{"question": "The judges recognized the students by the presidents .", "answer": "The students recognized the judges ."}
{"question": "The athlete saw the secretary next to the student .", "answer": "The secretary saw the athlete ."}
{"question": "The secretaries introduced the doctors next to the actor .", "answer": "The doctors introduced the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The secretaries introduced the doctors next to the presidents .", "answer": "The doctors introduced the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The senator by the tourists recommended the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers recommended the tourists ."}
{"question": "The professors behind the senators mentioned the students .", "answer": "The students mentioned the professors ."}
{"question": "The lawyers saw the bankers near the actor .", "answer": "The bankers saw the actor ."}
{"question": "The professors by the athletes advised the managers .", "answer": "The athletes advised the professors ."}
{"question": "The athlete recommended the doctor by the judge .", "answer": "The doctor recommended the judge ."}
{"question": "The student avoided the professor near the scientist .", "answer": "The professor avoided the student ."}
{"question": "The senator in front of the student introduced the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents introduced the senator ."}
{"question": "The secretary in front of the presidents advised the manager .", "answer": "The presidents advised the secretary ."}
{"question": "The doctors advised the actor behind the scientist .", "answer": "The actor advised the scientist ."}
{"question": "The manager introduced the judges in front of the scientists .", "answer": "The judges introduced the manager ."}
{"question": "The tourist thanked the artists in front of the managers .", "answer": "The artists thanked the managers ."}
{"question": "The senator helped the professors in front of the tourist .", "answer": "The professors helped the senator ."}
{"question": "The author believed the banker in front of the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries believed the author ."}
{"question": "The student saw the doctors near the athlete .", "answer": "The doctors saw the student ."}
{"question": "The doctor recognized the judges in front of the professor .", "answer": "The judges recognized the professor ."}
{"question": "The athlete behind the senators thanked the manager .", "answer": "The manager thanked the athlete ."}
{"question": "The lawyers avoided the bankers behind the artists .", "answer": "The bankers avoided the artists ."}
{"question": "The lawyer near the athlete mentioned the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists mentioned the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The actor encouraged the artist next to the presidents .", "answer": "The artist encouraged the presidents ."}
{"question": "The lawyer advised the secretary near the judges .", "answer": "The secretary advised the judges ."}
{"question": "The president thanked the author next to the artist .", "answer": "The author thanked the artist ."}
{"question": "The tourists next to the manager thanked the senator .", "answer": "The senator thanked the tourists ."}
{"question": "The secretary next to the judges stopped the president .", "answer": "The judges stopped the secretary ."}
{"question": "The banker next to the tourists admired the president .", "answer": "The tourists admired the banker ."}
{"question": "The scientists in front of the secretaries encouraged the doctors .", "answer": "The secretaries encouraged the scientists ."}
{"question": "The artist advised the actors next to the doctors .", "answer": "The actors advised the artist ."}
{"question": "The senator thanked the secretaries by the bankers .", "answer": "The secretaries thanked the bankers ."}
{"question": "The scientist admired the professor next to the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete admired the scientist ."}
{"question": "The bankers near the actor saw the lawyers .", "answer": "The actor saw the bankers ."}
{"question": "The actor near the managers saw the doctor .", "answer": "The managers saw the actor ."}
{"question": "The secretaries mentioned the judges in front of the student .", "answer": "The student mentioned the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The senators mentioned the professors by the authors .", "answer": "The professors mentioned the authors ."}
{"question": "The lawyer next to the professor avoided the president .", "answer": "The professor avoided the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The tourist next to the doctors supported the scientists .", "answer": "The doctors supported the tourist ."}
{"question": "The judge by the lawyer called the president .", "answer": "The president called the judge ."}
{"question": "The lawyer supported the athlete next to the artists .", "answer": "The artists supported the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The secretaries behind the scientist introduced the judges .", "answer": "The judges introduced the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The students saw the doctor near the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists saw the students ."}
{"question": "The president helped the manager near the student .", "answer": "The manager helped the student ."}
{"question": "The lawyers advised the manager by the students .", "answer": "The manager advised the students ."}
{"question": "The students admired the lawyers in front of the actor .", "answer": "The actor admired the students ."}
{"question": "The artists recognized the bankers in front of the author .", "answer": "The bankers recognized the artists ."}
{"question": "The professor in front of the lawyers mentioned the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete mentioned the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The secretaries recommended the judges behind the bankers .", "answer": "The judges recommended the bankers ."}
{"question": "The actors in front of the senators thanked the author .", "answer": "The senators thanked the actors ."}
{"question": "The scientist in front of the senators encouraged the author .", "answer": "The senators encouraged the scientist ."}
{"question": "The scientists near the tourist admired the professor .", "answer": "The professor admired the scientists ."}
{"question": "The presidents called the doctor near the judges .", "answer": "The doctor called the judges ."}
{"question": "The professors next to the judge admired the scientist .", "answer": "The judge admired the professors ."}
{"question": "The presidents recognized the manager behind the senators .", "answer": "The senators recognized the presidents ."}
{"question": "The author advised the athletes next to the senator .", "answer": "The senator advised the author ."}
{"question": "The lawyer mentioned the banker next to the managers .", "answer": "The banker mentioned the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The actor saw the senator behind the professors .", "answer": "The senator saw the professors ."}
{"question": "The senators mentioned the banker by the students .", "answer": "The banker mentioned the students ."}
{"question": "The doctor in front of the athlete supported the lawyer .", "answer": "The athlete supported the doctor ."}
{"question": "The presidents next to the manager encouraged the senators .", "answer": "The senators encouraged the presidents ."}
{"question": "The tourists in front of the lawyers supported the banker .", "answer": "The banker supported the tourists ."}
{"question": "The scientist saw the authors next to the manager .", "answer": "The manager saw the scientist ."}
{"question": "The lawyer supported the senators in front of the artist .", "answer": "The artist supported the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The president next to the manager avoided the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor avoided the manager ."}
{"question": "The author advised the judges next to the professor .", "answer": "The professor advised the author ."}
{"question": "The artist next to the lawyer supported the tourist .", "answer": "The lawyer supported the artist ."}
{"question": "The senator next to the actor called the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer called the actor ."}
{"question": "The bankers by the secretaries introduced the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists introduced the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The senator encouraged the doctors next to the judges .", "answer": "The doctors encouraged the judges ."}
{"question": "The scientist helped the artist in front of the managers .", "answer": "The managers helped the scientist ."}
{"question": "The students believed the doctor behind the secretaries .", "answer": "The doctor believed the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The author in front of the scientist stopped the tourist .", "answer": "The scientist stopped the author ."}
{"question": "The authors by the bankers recommended the professors .", "answer": "The bankers recommended the authors ."}
{"question": "The actor contacted the manager behind the professors .", "answer": "The manager contacted the professors ."}
{"question": "The tourists avoided the secretaries by the artist .", "answer": "The secretaries avoided the tourists ."}
{"question": "The author avoided the students by the banker .", "answer": "The students avoided the author ."}
{"question": "The bankers in front of the senators admired the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists admired the senators ."}
{"question": "The artist called the actor by the scientists .", "answer": "The actor called the artist ."}
{"question": "The actor behind the doctor stopped the senators .", "answer": "The senators stopped the actor ."}
{"question": "The presidents near the scientist supported the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary supported the presidents ."}
{"question": "The doctors near the author recognized the professor .", "answer": "The professor recognized the author ."}
{"question": "The managers believed the actor in front of the professors .", "answer": "The actor believed the professors ."}
{"question": "The banker admired the president by the artist .", "answer": "The president admired the banker ."}
{"question": "The managers encouraged the secretaries near the professors .", "answer": "The secretaries encouraged the professors ."}
{"question": "The doctor in front of the manager encouraged the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers encouraged the doctor ."}
{"question": "The banker behind the professor encouraged the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer encouraged the professor ."}
{"question": "The bankers by the presidents introduced the judge .", "answer": "The presidents introduced the bankers ."}
{"question": "The tourists in front of the athlete introduced the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary introduced the athlete ."}
{"question": "The president believed the artists near the authors .", "answer": "The artists believed the authors ."}
{"question": "The tourists behind the doctors advised the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries advised the tourists ."}
{"question": "The secretaries supported the doctors in front of the professors .", "answer": "The professors supported the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The secretary in front of the judges recognized the manager .", "answer": "The manager recognized the judges ."}
{"question": "The tourists believed the lawyer next to the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers believed the tourists ."}
{"question": "The presidents near the managers admired the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete admired the presidents ."}
{"question": "The actor supported the students next to the judge .", "answer": "The students supported the actor ."}
{"question": "The tourist recommended the lawyers behind the artists .", "answer": "The lawyers recommended the tourist ."}
{"question": "The bankers encouraged the lawyers near the secretaries .", "answer": "The lawyers encouraged the bankers ."}
{"question": "The banker in front of the secretaries thanked the professors .", "answer": "The professors thanked the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The tourists advised the doctors behind the judges .", "answer": "The judges advised the tourists ."}
{"question": "The judge mentioned the manager by the tourists .", "answer": "The manager mentioned the judge ."}
{"question": "The student next to the manager stopped the banker .", "answer": "The banker stopped the student ."}
{"question": "The lawyers in front of the actor stopped the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist stopped the actor ."}
{"question": "The professors believed the judges in front of the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary believed the professors ."}
{"question": "The actors admired the presidents next to the bankers .", "answer": "The presidents admired the actors ."}
{"question": "The manager introduced the judge by the lawyer .", "answer": "The judge introduced the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The presidents stopped the doctors in front of the secretary .", "answer": "The doctors stopped the secretary ."}
{"question": "The secretaries stopped the judges by the athletes .", "answer": "The judges stopped the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The manager near the judges stopped the students .", "answer": "The judges stopped the manager ."}
{"question": "The lawyer helped the secretaries next to the tourist .", "answer": "The secretaries helped the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The students near the authors mentioned the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist mentioned the students ."}
{"question": "The athlete in front of the secretary advised the judges .", "answer": "The judges advised the athlete ."}
{"question": "The president near the artists contacted the student .", "answer": "The student contacted the president ."}
{"question": "The president helped the senator in front of the judges .", "answer": "The judges helped the president ."}
{"question": "The lawyer in front of the presidents helped the banker .", "answer": "The banker helped the presidents ."}
{"question": "The judge behind the tourists stopped the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers stopped the judge ."}
{"question": "The senator in front of the athlete mentioned the professors .", "answer": "The professors mentioned the senator ."}
{"question": "The secretaries encouraged the athlete near the authors .", "answer": "The athlete encouraged the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The scientists recommended the professors near the artists .", "answer": "The professors recommended the artists ."}
{"question": "The senator saw the professors by the students .", "answer": "The professors saw the students ."}
{"question": "The senators contacted the author next to the student .", "answer": "The student contacted the senators ."}
{"question": "The senators in front of the scientist believed the manager .", "answer": "The manager believed the scientist ."}
{"question": "The doctor recognized the professor in front of the artists .", "answer": "The professor recognized the doctor ."}
{"question": "The tourist avoided the secretary behind the judge .", "answer": "The secretary avoided the tourist ."}
{"question": "The student recommended the athlete near the scientist .", "answer": "The athlete recommended the scientist ."}
{"question": "The professors thanked the authors by the artist .", "answer": "The artist thanked the professors ."}
{"question": "The professor saw the presidents near the managers .", "answer": "The presidents saw the professor ."}
{"question": "The manager mentioned the president behind the tourists .", "answer": "The president mentioned the tourists ."}
{"question": "The actor helped the athletes by the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer helped the actor ."}
{"question": "The scientists next to the professors thanked the artist .", "answer": "The artist thanked the professors ."}
{"question": "The lawyer called the managers next to the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists called the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The artists in front of the tourists encouraged the author .", "answer": "The author encouraged the tourists ."}
{"question": "The student behind the bankers saw the manager .", "answer": "The bankers saw the student ."}
{"question": "The scientists recognized the artists by the judges .", "answer": "The judges recognized the scientists ."}
{"question": "The secretary called the president next to the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor called the secretary ."}
{"question": "The athletes behind the doctors believed the students .", "answer": "The students believed the doctors ."}
{"question": "The artists near the president mentioned the athlete .", "answer": "The president mentioned the artists ."}
{"question": "The professor avoided the student by the actor .", "answer": "The actor avoided the professor ."}
{"question": "The tourist recommended the doctor in front of the professor .", "answer": "The doctor recommended the tourist ."}
{"question": "The professors supported the lawyers behind the banker .", "answer": "The lawyers supported the professors ."}
{"question": "The actors behind the banker thanked the doctor .", "answer": "The banker thanked the actors ."}
{"question": "The student helped the professor by the senator .", "answer": "The professor helped the senator ."}
{"question": "The professor helped the presidents near the athlete .", "answer": "The presidents helped the athlete ."}
{"question": "The athlete behind the lawyer stopped the tourist .", "answer": "The lawyer stopped the athlete ."}
{"question": "The bankers next to the professors saw the managers .", "answer": "The managers saw the professors ."}
{"question": "The presidents behind the artists introduced the judge .", "answer": "The judge introduced the presidents ."}
{"question": "The doctor called the bankers in front of the lawyers .", "answer": "The bankers called the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The banker recommended the doctors next to the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists recommended the banker ."}
{"question": "The lawyer supported the secretary behind the actors .", "answer": "The secretary supported the actors ."}
{"question": "The artists next to the managers avoided the authors .", "answer": "The managers avoided the artists ."}
{"question": "The athletes near the doctor saw the judges .", "answer": "The judges saw the doctor ."}
{"question": "The judges next to the lawyer saw the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors saw the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The actor recommended the judges near the president .", "answer": "The president recommended the actor ."}
{"question": "The athlete helped the authors next to the doctor .", "answer": "The authors helped the athlete ."}
{"question": "The banker introduced the author behind the scientist .", "answer": "The author introduced the banker ."}
{"question": "The scientists saw the artists in front of the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers saw the scientists ."}
{"question": "The athletes next to the manager recommended the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer recommended the athletes ."}
{"question": "The judges behind the managers called the students .", "answer": "The students called the managers ."}
{"question": "The scientists saw the authors behind the athletes .", "answer": "The authors saw the scientists ."}
{"question": "The bankers saw the author by the secretaries .", "answer": "The author saw the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The bankers believed the judges behind the presidents .", "answer": "The judges believed the presidents ."}
{"question": "The senator believed the actors behind the judge .", "answer": "The judge believed the senator ."}
{"question": "The secretary introduced the actors by the author .", "answer": "The author introduced the secretary ."}
{"question": "The senators behind the artist recommended the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents recommended the artist ."}
{"question": "The lawyers introduced the doctor by the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents introduced the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The authors next to the doctor helped the actor .", "answer": "The actor helped the authors ."}
{"question": "The tourist by the athletes advised the doctors .", "answer": "The athletes advised the tourist ."}
{"question": "The lawyer encouraged the professor in front of the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents encouraged the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The actors believed the judges behind the students .", "answer": "The judges believed the students ."}
{"question": "The secretary next to the judge admired the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers admired the judge ."}
{"question": "The senators mentioned the student in front of the professor .", "answer": "The student mentioned the senators ."}
{"question": "The student by the judge avoided the professors .", "answer": "The professors avoided the student ."}
{"question": "The presidents helped the bankers in front of the student .", "answer": "The bankers helped the student ."}
{"question": "The scientist helped the student by the author .", "answer": "The student helped the author ."}
{"question": "The banker by the professor helped the scientist .", "answer": "The professor helped the banker ."}
{"question": "The actor avoided the secretary next to the lawyer .", "answer": "The secretary avoided the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The lawyer admired the actors by the artists .", "answer": "The actors admired the artists ."}
{"question": "The presidents mentioned the tourists by the banker .", "answer": "The tourists mentioned the presidents ."}
{"question": "The scientists stopped the banker by the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary stopped the scientists ."}
{"question": "The banker next to the judge advised the senator .", "answer": "The senator advised the banker ."}
{"question": "The student next to the artist admired the secretaries .", "answer": "The artist admired the student ."}
{"question": "The professors next to the banker mentioned the author .", "answer": "The author mentioned the professors ."}
{"question": "The author recognized the presidents next to the artist .", "answer": "The presidents recognized the author ."}
{"question": "The artist behind the senator recommended the author .", "answer": "The senator recommended the artist ."}
{"question": "The doctors near the secretary contacted the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer contacted the doctors ."}
{"question": "The banker avoided the judges by the presidents .", "answer": "The judges avoided the presidents ."}
{"question": "The students near the banker introduced the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer introduced the banker ."}
{"question": "The actor advised the lawyers near the presidents .", "answer": "The lawyers advised the presidents ."}
{"question": "The professors by the scientists mentioned the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents mentioned the professors ."}
{"question": "The scientists in front of the professors advised the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors advised the scientists ."}
{"question": "The doctor avoided the artist next to the students .", "answer": "The artist avoided the doctor ."}
{"question": "The lawyer advised the doctor next to the athletes .", "answer": "The doctor advised the athletes ."}
{"question": "The professors behind the lawyers helped the senators .", "answer": "The senators helped the professors ."}
{"question": "The students behind the judge called the scientist .", "answer": "The judge called the students ."}
{"question": "The tourists near the authors avoided the presidents .", "answer": "The authors avoided the tourists ."}
{"question": "The lawyer next to the presidents recommended the judges .", "answer": "The judges recommended the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The secretaries admired the senator behind the professors .", "answer": "The professors admired the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The lawyer called the doctor near the students .", "answer": "The doctor called the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The banker believed the actor behind the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete believed the banker ."}
{"question": "The professor encouraged the student next to the manager .", "answer": "The student encouraged the professor ."}
{"question": "The author next to the actor thanked the president .", "answer": "The actor thanked the author ."}
{"question": "The tourists next to the doctor avoided the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary avoided the tourists ."}
{"question": "The senators called the professors in front of the scientists .", "answer": "The professors called the scientists ."}
{"question": "The artist in front of the professors believed the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers believed the artist ."}
{"question": "The athlete next to the authors introduced the senators .", "answer": "The senators introduced the authors ."}
{"question": "The author near the banker called the senator .", "answer": "The banker called the author ."}
{"question": "The professors thanked the judges by the artist .", "answer": "The judges thanked the professors ."}
{"question": "The students saw the bankers behind the actors .", "answer": "The actors saw the students ."}
{"question": "The presidents in front of the author introduced the lawyer .", "answer": "The author introduced the presidents ."}
{"question": "The athlete by the presidents helped the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists helped the athlete ."}
{"question": "The doctors by the student supported the secretary .", "answer": "The student supported the doctors ."}
{"question": "The president supported the student next to the senator .", "answer": "The student supported the president ."}
{"question": "The artist in front of the author thanked the scientist .", "answer": "The author thanked the artist ."}
{"question": "The actor introduced the athlete next to the tourists .", "answer": "The athlete introduced the tourists ."}
{"question": "The bankers next to the doctor admired the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary admired the bankers ."}
{"question": "The athlete behind the bankers saw the actors .", "answer": "The bankers saw the athlete ."}
{"question": "The artist behind the tourists admired the doctors .", "answer": "The tourists admired the artist ."}
{"question": "The actor contacted the student behind the managers .", "answer": "The student contacted the actor ."}
{"question": "The student next to the senators encouraged the actor .", "answer": "The actor encouraged the senators ."}
{"question": "The athlete recognized the secretaries behind the doctor .", "answer": "The secretaries recognized the athlete ."}
{"question": "The author by the actor thanked the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor thanked the author ."}
{"question": "The tourists near the senator saw the author .", "answer": "The senator saw the tourists ."}
{"question": "The doctors near the judge introduced the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers introduced the doctors ."}
{"question": "The presidents introduced the lawyer next to the banker .", "answer": "The lawyer introduced the banker ."}
{"question": "The lawyer contacted the doctors in front of the actor .", "answer": "The actor contacted the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The student contacted the lawyers in front of the banker .", "answer": "The lawyers contacted the student ."}
{"question": "The bankers behind the scientist avoided the managers .", "answer": "The managers avoided the bankers ."}
{"question": "The athletes recommended the scientists behind the tourists .", "answer": "The scientists recommended the athletes ."}
{"question": "The president supported the artist next to the banker .", "answer": "The banker supported the president ."}
{"question": "The scientists in front of the artists recognized the professors .", "answer": "The artists recognized the scientists ."}
{"question": "The banker mentioned the senator behind the manager .", "answer": "The senator mentioned the manager ."}
{"question": "The lawyer believed the scientists behind the tourists .", "answer": "The scientists believed the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The senators believed the doctor by the actors .", "answer": "The actors believed the senators ."}
{"question": "The doctor near the artist advised the student .", "answer": "The student advised the doctor ."}
{"question": "The tourists contacted the artists by the judge .", "answer": "The judge contacted the tourists ."}
{"question": "The actors by the students contacted the senator .", "answer": "The students contacted the actors ."}
{"question": "The secretary by the tourist contacted the actors .", "answer": "The tourist contacted the secretary ."}
{"question": "The presidents recognized the actor by the tourists .", "answer": "The actor recognized the tourists ."}
{"question": "The lawyer by the professors stopped the athletes .", "answer": "The professors stopped the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The artists encouraged the judges by the professor .", "answer": "The judges encouraged the artists ."}
{"question": "The athlete in front of the actor introduced the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor introduced the actor ."}
{"question": "The presidents next to the judge helped the senators .", "answer": "The senators helped the judge ."}
{"question": "The professors next to the president recommended the artist .", "answer": "The president recommended the professors ."}
{"question": "The author thanked the banker near the professor .", "answer": "The banker thanked the professor ."}
{"question": "The managers encouraged the artists near the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists encouraged the managers ."}
{"question": "The scientist supported the managers by the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete supported the scientist ."}
{"question": "The author by the judge contacted the scientist .", "answer": "The judge contacted the author ."}
{"question": "The professor by the athlete stopped the actors .", "answer": "The actors stopped the professor ."}
{"question": "The athletes by the tourists introduced the judge .", "answer": "The judge introduced the tourists ."}
{"question": "The senators near the tourists recognized the lawyers .", "answer": "The tourists recognized the senators ."}
{"question": "The actors contacted the manager near the artists .", "answer": "The manager contacted the actors ."}
{"question": "The athletes next to the managers avoided the judge .", "answer": "The managers avoided the athletes ."}
{"question": "The senator near the manager saw the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists saw the manager ."}
{"question": "The authors in front of the students recognized the senator .", "answer": "The senator recognized the students ."}
{"question": "The doctor next to the senator thanked the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist thanked the senator ."}
{"question": "The athlete recommended the actor near the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries recommended the athlete ."}
{"question": "The senator behind the athlete saw the student .", "answer": "The athlete saw the senator ."}
{"question": "The artist by the authors contacted the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers contacted the artist ."}
{"question": "The scientists near the judge called the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents called the judge ."}
{"question": "The doctor helped the athlete near the banker .", "answer": "The athlete helped the doctor ."}
{"question": "The bankers near the student contacted the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors contacted the bankers ."}
{"question": "The student by the presidents encouraged the senators .", "answer": "The senators encouraged the presidents ."}
{"question": "The athletes helped the secretary next to the students .", "answer": "The secretary helped the athletes ."}
{"question": "The professors by the students mentioned the secretary .", "answer": "The students mentioned the professors ."}
{"question": "The students in front of the senator contacted the manager .", "answer": "The manager contacted the students ."}
{"question": "The professors recognized the banker behind the athlete .", "answer": "The banker recognized the athlete ."}
{"question": "The lawyer mentioned the manager behind the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists mentioned the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The doctors by the lawyers recommended the banker .", "answer": "The lawyers recommended the doctors ."}
{"question": "The scientist in front of the secretary introduced the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents introduced the secretary ."}
{"question": "The judge by the students advised the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors advised the judge ."}
{"question": "The students helped the doctor in front of the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents helped the students ."}
{"question": "The scientist believed the doctor near the authors .", "answer": "The authors believed the scientist ."}
{"question": "The bankers in front of the athletes saw the senator .", "answer": "The senator saw the bankers ."}
{"question": "The athletes believed the bankers next to the manager .", "answer": "The bankers believed the athletes ."}
{"question": "The professors in front of the manager thanked the students .", "answer": "The manager thanked the professors ."}
{"question": "The actors by the artists mentioned the lawyer .", "answer": "The artists mentioned the actors ."}
{"question": "The judge next to the managers thanked the presidents .", "answer": "The managers thanked the judge ."}
{"question": "The artist called the president by the bankers .", "answer": "The president called the artist ."}
{"question": "The secretary by the doctors supported the student .", "answer": "The student supported the secretary ."}
{"question": "The professors helped the lawyer near the doctor .", "answer": "The lawyer helped the doctor ."}
{"question": "The artist mentioned the scientist near the judge .", "answer": "The scientist mentioned the artist ."}
{"question": "The president advised the student next to the author .", "answer": "The student advised the president ."}
{"question": "The professors in front of the students contacted the author .", "answer": "The students contacted the professors ."}
{"question": "The senators next to the doctors contacted the judge .", "answer": "The doctors contacted the senators ."}
{"question": "The tourists believed the secretaries next to the manager .", "answer": "The secretaries believed the tourists ."}
{"question": "The artist in front of the secretaries believed the student .", "answer": "The student believed the artist ."}
{"question": "The managers in front of the judges believed the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists believed the judges ."}
{"question": "The judge avoided the senator next to the presidents .", "answer": "The senator avoided the presidents ."}
{"question": "The bankers next to the manager called the students .", "answer": "The students called the manager ."}
{"question": "The athlete saw the secretaries by the judge .", "answer": "The secretaries saw the athlete ."}
{"question": "The presidents in front of the judge saw the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer saw the judge ."}
{"question": "The president advised the doctors next to the manager .", "answer": "The manager advised the president ."}
{"question": "The artists behind the student advised the tourist .", "answer": "The student advised the artists ."}
{"question": "The manager behind the doctors advised the artists .", "answer": "The doctors advised the manager ."}
{"question": "The actor in front of the presidents recognized the authors .", "answer": "The authors recognized the actor ."}
{"question": "The tourist called the lawyers in front of the professor .", "answer": "The lawyers called the tourist ."}
{"question": "The author admired the professor by the bankers .", "answer": "The professor admired the author ."}
{"question": "The presidents in front of the senator avoided the lawyer .", "answer": "The senator avoided the presidents ."}
{"question": "The banker in front of the artist helped the judge .", "answer": "The judge helped the artist ."}
{"question": "The bankers in front of the managers mentioned the authors .", "answer": "The managers mentioned the bankers ."}
{"question": "The artist behind the lawyer saw the professor .", "answer": "The professor saw the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The secretary recognized the professor in front of the tourist .", "answer": "The professor recognized the tourist ."}
{"question": "The doctor recognized the bankers by the president .", "answer": "The president recognized the doctor ."}
{"question": "The senator believed the doctor in front of the banker .", "answer": "The doctor believed the banker ."}
{"question": "The professor behind the presidents stopped the artist .", "answer": "The artist stopped the presidents ."}
{"question": "The scientist by the doctors called the president .", "answer": "The doctors called the scientist ."}
{"question": "The scientist admired the author near the banker .", "answer": "The author admired the scientist ."}
{"question": "The secretary recognized the lawyer in front of the actor .", "answer": "The actor recognized the secretary ."}
{"question": "The student behind the author introduced the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers introduced the student ."}
{"question": "The student near the lawyers believed the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary believed the student ."}
{"question": "The actor behind the judge supported the student .", "answer": "The judge supported the actor ."}
{"question": "The tourist behind the president thanked the lawyer .", "answer": "The president thanked the tourist ."}
{"question": "The professor advised the athletes next to the actor .", "answer": "The actor advised the professor ."}
{"question": "The doctors by the artist recognized the presidents .", "answer": "The artist recognized the doctors ."}
{"question": "The professors near the athletes advised the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists advised the athletes ."}
{"question": "The artist helped the banker that admired the secretary .", "answer": "The banker helped the the secretary ."}
{"question": "The actor supported the tourists that the athlete recognized .", "answer": "The tourists supported the athlete ."}
{"question": "The author that the judges helped admired the artists .", "answer": "The artists admired the judges ."}
{"question": "The manager contacted the tourists who the professor believed .", "answer": "The tourists contacted the professor ."}
{"question": "The professor who supported the judge thanked the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer thanked the professor ."}
{"question": "The judge recommended the athletes who the senators saw .", "answer": "The athletes recommended the judge ."}
{"question": "The scientists that the actors called introduced the manager .", "answer": "The actors introduced the scientists ."}
{"question": "The scientists believed the tourists who the students saw .", "answer": "The students believed the scientists ."}
{"question": "The doctor encouraged the professors who helped the bankers .", "answer": "The professors encouraged the the bankers ."}
{"question": "The bankers recognized the professor who helped the president .", "answer": "The president recognized the bankers ."}
{"question": "The professor recommended the senators that the secretaries supported .", "answer": "The secretaries recommended the professor ."}
{"question": "The professors that supported the athletes saw the doctor .", "answer": "The athletes saw the professors ."}
{"question": "The secretaries saw the authors who the lawyer recommended .", "answer": "The lawyer saw the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The doctors that the scientist helped mentioned the senator .", "answer": "The senator mentioned the doctors ."}
{"question": "The author advised the secretary that supported the artists .", "answer": "The artists advised the author ."}
{"question": "The lawyer advised the artist that avoided the professor .", "answer": "The artist advised the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The president saw the senators who the professors encouraged .", "answer": "The senators saw the president ."}
{"question": "The artists believed the tourists who mentioned the scientist .", "answer": "The tourists believed the artists ."}
{"question": "The doctors who the student stopped advised the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers advised the student ."}
{"question": "The judges that the manager stopped supported the professors .", "answer": "The professors supported the manager ."}
{"question": "The managers who stopped the scientist mentioned the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer mentioned the scientist ."}
{"question": "The authors saw the artists who recommended the scientist .", "answer": "The artists saw the the scientist ."}
{"question": "The judge avoided the student that the secretary believed .", "answer": "The secretary avoided the judge ."}
{"question": "The doctor mentioned the artist that the professors saw .", "answer": "The professors mentioned the doctor ."}
{"question": "The senator who recommended the lawyer believed the artist .", "answer": "The lawyer believed the senator ."}
{"question": "The secretary helped the tourists that avoided the lawyers .", "answer": "The tourists helped the the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The student that advised the artist thanked the tourists .", "answer": "The artist thanked the student ."}
{"question": "The lawyer who encouraged the banker called the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents called the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The artist who supported the athletes helped the student .", "answer": "The student helped the athletes ."}
{"question": "The professors recognized the lawyers who contacted the doctor .", "answer": "The lawyers recognized the professors ."}
{"question": "The athlete who the scientist introduced contacted the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists contacted the scientist ."}
{"question": "The banker who the scientist mentioned stopped the artist .", "answer": "The artist stopped the scientist ."}
{"question": "The doctor who the lawyer believed recognized the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents recognized the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The judge advised the students who helped the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents advised the judge ."}
{"question": "The scientist contacted the tourist who advised the president .", "answer": "The president contacted the scientist ."}
{"question": "The students called the secretaries who the judge supported .", "answer": "The secretaries called the judge ."}
{"question": "The artist supported the judge that avoided the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary supported the artist ."}
{"question": "The actor that recommended the judge introduced the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary introduced the judge ."}
{"question": "The senator stopped the scientist that believed the professors .", "answer": "The scientist stopped the senator ."}
{"question": "The senator mentioned the student who the bankers supported .", "answer": "The bankers mentioned the senator ."}
{"question": "The senator who the manager avoided introduced the artists .", "answer": "The artists introduced the manager ."}
{"question": "The doctor that recommended the scientists saw the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents saw the scientists ."}
{"question": "The author recognized the scientist who introduced the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist recognized the author ."}
{"question": "The artist supported the students who saw the presidents .", "answer": "The students supported the artist ."}
{"question": "The doctor saw the artist that encouraged the scientist .", "answer": "The artist saw the doctor ."}
{"question": "The judges who the doctor introduced mentioned the lawyer .", "answer": "The doctor mentioned the judges ."}
{"question": "The scientists believed the athletes that stopped the tourist .", "answer": "The athletes believed the scientists ."}
{"question": "The presidents supported the doctor that the bankers helped .", "answer": "The doctor supported the bankers ."}
{"question": "The student that advised the athlete introduced the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists introduced the athlete ."}
{"question": "The lawyer recognized the professor that supported the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers recognized the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The bankers that recognized the judge contacted the student .", "answer": "The student contacted the judge ."}
{"question": "The secretaries who contacted the banker encouraged the athletes .", "answer": "The banker encouraged the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The artists who the doctor supported called the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer called the doctor ."}
{"question": "The senator believed the manager who thanked the actors .", "answer": "The manager believed the the actors ."}
{"question": "The professor that the senator avoided introduced the judges .", "answer": "The judges introduced the senator ."}
{"question": "The managers believed the judges who the artists admired .", "answer": "The judges believed the managers ."}
{"question": "The scientists saw the author that the senators avoided .", "answer": "The author saw the senators ."}
{"question": "The doctors helped the actors that the athletes recommended .", "answer": "The actors helped the doctors ."}
{"question": "The president called the secretary that helped the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist called the president ."}
{"question": "The managers who advised the scientists admired the artists .", "answer": "The scientists admired the managers ."}
{"question": "The scientists that admired the presidents helped the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor helped the presidents ."}
{"question": "The scientist thanked the judges who mentioned the managers .", "answer": "The judges thanked the scientist ."}
{"question": "The banker that contacted the student supported the senator .", "answer": "The senator supported the student ."}
{"question": "The bankers who the doctors avoided encouraged the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries encouraged the doctors ."}
{"question": "The secretaries admired the athletes who helped the student .", "answer": "The student admired the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The doctors mentioned the secretaries that the scientist helped .", "answer": "The secretaries mentioned the scientist ."}
{"question": "The tourist advised the authors who supported the senators .", "answer": "The authors advised the tourist ."}
{"question": "The tourist that helped the judge introduced the actor .", "answer": "The actor introduced the tourist ."}
{"question": "The artist that helped the author mentioned the banker .", "answer": "The author mentioned the artist ."}
{"question": "The banker advised the senators that the athlete thanked .", "answer": "The senators advised the athlete ."}
{"question": "The managers saw the professor who the secretary introduced .", "answer": "The professor saw the managers ."}
{"question": "The tourists that the athletes supported advised the lawyers .", "answer": "The athletes advised the tourists ."}
{"question": "The student who supported the bankers advised the professor .", "answer": "The professor advised the bankers ."}
{"question": "The actors who avoided the bankers believed the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary believed the actors ."}
{"question": "The managers who the professor introduced believed the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist believed the professor ."}
{"question": "The lawyer advised the banker that admired the professor .", "answer": "The professor advised the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The actors who recommended the doctor admired the banker .", "answer": "The banker admired the doctor ."}
{"question": "The scientist admired the professor who the doctors helped .", "answer": "The professor admired the scientist ."}
{"question": "The lawyer that the secretaries admired helped the student .", "answer": "The secretaries helped the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The secretaries that the artist contacted mentioned the managers .", "answer": "The managers mentioned the artist ."}
{"question": "The bankers stopped the professors who saw the scientists .", "answer": "The professors stopped the bankers ."}
{"question": "The doctor who the bankers thanked helped the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents helped the bankers ."}
{"question": "The senators stopped the bankers that saw the actor .", "answer": "The actor stopped the senators ."}
{"question": "The scientists advised the managers that called the athletes .", "answer": "The managers advised the scientists ."}
{"question": "The artist that the actor stopped avoided the professors .", "answer": "The professors avoided the actor ."}
{"question": "The lawyers that the bankers believed helped the actors .", "answer": "The bankers helped the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The secretary stopped the scientists who recognized the professors .", "answer": "The professors stopped the secretary ."}
{"question": "The doctors stopped the actors who mentioned the artists .", "answer": "The actors stopped the the artists ."}
{"question": "The managers mentioned the students who the judge encouraged .", "answer": "The students mentioned the managers ."}
{"question": "The president that believed the artist encouraged the banker .", "answer": "The banker encouraged the artist ."}
{"question": "The tourist introduced the president who helped the senator .", "answer": "The president introduced the tourist ."}
{"question": "The doctors recognized the athlete that saw the senator .", "answer": "The athlete recognized the doctors ."}
{"question": "The student that helped the bankers mentioned the tourist .", "answer": "The bankers mentioned the student ."}
{"question": "The students recognized the professor that avoided the doctors .", "answer": "The professor recognized the students ."}
{"question": "The bankers admired the professor that avoided the judge .", "answer": "The judge admired the bankers ."}
{"question": "The doctor who thanked the student supported the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers supported the student ."}
{"question": "The author stopped the scientists who the judge introduced .", "answer": "The scientists stopped the author ."}
{"question": "The judge thanked the presidents who recommended the doctors .", "answer": "The presidents thanked the the doctors ."}
{"question": "The senators recognized the artists that the doctors stopped .", "answer": "The artists recognized the doctors ."}
{"question": "The actor that stopped the tourists recommended the judge .", "answer": "The tourists recommended the actor ."}
{"question": "The secretaries mentioned the lawyers who the students recommended .", "answer": "The lawyers mentioned the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The students stopped the tourist who the senators saw .", "answer": "The tourist stopped the students ."}
{"question": "The scientists thanked the senators who mentioned the professor .", "answer": "The senators thanked the scientists ."}
{"question": "The doctor called the managers who the tourist introduced .", "answer": "The managers called the tourist ."}
{"question": "The presidents supported the doctor who the managers contacted .", "answer": "The doctor supported the managers ."}
{"question": "The professor who admired the president mentioned the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists mentioned the president ."}
{"question": "The professor recognized the author that the presidents mentioned .", "answer": "The author recognized the professor ."}
{"question": "The managers admired the scientists that recommended the author .", "answer": "The scientists admired the the author ."}
{"question": "The lawyers saw the students that believed the artist .", "answer": "The artist saw the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The senators introduced the author that believed the manager .", "answer": "The manager introduced the senators ."}
{"question": "The lawyers contacted the presidents that helped the banker .", "answer": "The banker contacted the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The managers who the presidents recommended supported the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer supported the presidents ."}
{"question": "The senator helped the actor who recognized the judge .", "answer": "The judge helped the senator ."}
{"question": "The secretaries who admired the doctors contacted the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers contacted the doctors ."}
{"question": "The senators stopped the students who called the presidents .", "answer": "The students stopped the senators ."}
{"question": "The manager advised the scientists who stopped the president .", "answer": "The scientists advised the the president ."}
{"question": "The lawyer mentioned the tourists that advised the judge .", "answer": "The tourists mentioned the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The athletes who recommended the authors believed the manager .", "answer": "The authors believed the athletes ."}
{"question": "The athletes who stopped the authors supported the senator .", "answer": "The senator supported the authors ."}
{"question": "The students who the manager mentioned helped the actors .", "answer": "The actors helped the students ."}
{"question": "The scientist called the secretary that the senator saw .", "answer": "The secretary called the scientist ."}
{"question": "The athletes that the authors admired recommended the students .", "answer": "The students recommended the athletes ."}
{"question": "The student supported the actor who the manager advised .", "answer": "The actor supported the student ."}
{"question": "The student that the actor contacted believed the tourist .", "answer": "The actor believed the student ."}
{"question": "The actor helped the judges who the manager saw .", "answer": "The judges helped the actor ."}
{"question": "The secretary that thanked the tourists recognized the judge .", "answer": "The judge recognized the secretary ."}
{"question": "The secretaries who advised the actor supported the senators .", "answer": "The actor supported the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The professors who recommended the tourist introduced the secretary .", "answer": "The tourist introduced the professors ."}
{"question": "The secretaries who the banker admired called the actors .", "answer": "The actors called the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The tourist that the professor advised encouraged the actors .", "answer": "The actors encouraged the tourist ."}
{"question": "The authors helped the secretary who the managers recommended .", "answer": "The secretary helped the managers ."}
{"question": "The professors called the judges that the senator thanked .", "answer": "The judges called the professors ."}
{"question": "The judge who stopped the lawyer helped the authors .", "answer": "The lawyer helped the judge ."}
{"question": "The students believed the judges that called the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists believed the students ."}
{"question": "The tourist admired the students that the scientist recommended .", "answer": "The students admired the scientist ."}
{"question": "The artist that believed the president called the professor .", "answer": "The professor called the president ."}
{"question": "The judge avoided the scientist that the senator mentioned .", "answer": "The scientist avoided the senator ."}
{"question": "The tourist who the scientists recommended saw the professor .", "answer": "The professor saw the tourist ."}
{"question": "The manager who mentioned the professors supported the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer supported the manager ."}
{"question": "The actors helped the bankers that believed the secretary .", "answer": "The bankers helped the actors ."}
{"question": "The scientists that contacted the lawyer thanked the athlete .", "answer": "The lawyer thanked the scientists ."}
{"question": "The tourist who advised the doctors stopped the judge .", "answer": "The doctors stopped the tourist ."}
{"question": "The banker supported the professor that stopped the athlete .", "answer": "The professor supported the the athlete ."}
{"question": "The tourist supported the banker who the lawyer mentioned .", "answer": "The lawyer supported the tourist ."}
{"question": "The student contacted the artist who the tourists recommended .", "answer": "The artist contacted the tourists ."}
{"question": "The lawyer who called the actor encouraged the professor .", "answer": "The professor encouraged the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The managers that the lawyer avoided believed the tourist .", "answer": "The lawyer believed the managers ."}
{"question": "The lawyer that the judges recommended contacted the senator .", "answer": "The senator contacted the judges ."}
{"question": "The judge that helped the tourist admired the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers admired the judge ."}
{"question": "The artist stopped the scientist that the authors thanked .", "answer": "The scientist stopped the authors ."}
{"question": "The author encouraged the president that the doctors called .", "answer": "The president encouraged the doctors ."}
{"question": "The author recognized the students that admired the scientists .", "answer": "The students recognized the author ."}
{"question": "The secretary thanked the tourist who the student saw .", "answer": "The tourist thanked the student ."}
{"question": "The doctors who the actor encouraged contacted the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist contacted the doctors ."}
{"question": "The scientists mentioned the manager that the author encouraged .", "answer": "The manager mentioned the author ."}
{"question": "The athlete admired the students who recommended the actor .", "answer": "The actor admired the athlete ."}
{"question": "The lawyers supported the judge who mentioned the professor .", "answer": "The judge supported the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The athlete that the lawyer called believed the professors .", "answer": "The professors believed the athlete ."}
{"question": "The professor stopped the presidents that introduced the tourists .", "answer": "The presidents stopped the the tourists ."}
{"question": "The managers saw the actors that the authors advised .", "answer": "The actors saw the authors ."}
{"question": "The judge who helped the secretary thanked the presidents .", "answer": "The secretary thanked the judge ."}
{"question": "The judges who saw the athletes recommended the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist recommended the judges ."}
{"question": "The president who the actor avoided recognized the senators .", "answer": "The senators recognized the actor ."}
{"question": "The athletes who called the actor supported the scientist .", "answer": "The actor supported the athletes ."}
{"question": "The lawyers that the artist recognized thanked the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary thanked the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The actor that supported the scientist contacted the judges .", "answer": "The judges contacted the scientist ."}
{"question": "The senators that the athletes thanked advised the tourists .", "answer": "The athletes advised the senators ."}
{"question": "The actor advised the bankers who the athlete helped .", "answer": "The athlete advised the actor ."}
{"question": "The senator supported the athlete that the tourists mentioned .", "answer": "The athlete supported the tourists ."}
{"question": "The president thanked the lawyers who the actors stopped .", "answer": "The lawyers thanked the president ."}
{"question": "The manager who recommended the tourist thanked the actor .", "answer": "The actor thanked the tourist ."}
{"question": "The doctor introduced the scientist who believed the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete introduced the doctor ."}
{"question": "The professors who the artist contacted called the athletes .", "answer": "The artist called the professors ."}
{"question": "The author mentioned the doctor that the secretary saw .", "answer": "The doctor mentioned the author ."}
{"question": "The secretary that mentioned the authors believed the senators .", "answer": "The senators believed the secretary ."}
{"question": "The tourist who advised the doctors avoided the presidents .", "answer": "The doctors avoided the tourist ."}
{"question": "The senators introduced the judge that stopped the managers .", "answer": "The judge introduced the the managers ."}
{"question": "The scientists supported the senator that the banker believed .", "answer": "The senator supported the scientists ."}
{"question": "The author avoided the senator who advised the lawyer .", "answer": "The senator avoided the the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The author who called the lawyer recommended the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries recommended the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The scientists supported the judges who the presidents recommended .", "answer": "The judges supported the presidents ."}
{"question": "The artist that the scientists introduced admired the banker .", "answer": "The banker admired the artist ."}
{"question": "The secretaries recognized the lawyer who contacted the judge .", "answer": "The judge recognized the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The professor advised the doctor that thanked the lawyers .", "answer": "The doctor advised the professor ."}
{"question": "The artists avoided the judges who the author supported .", "answer": "The author avoided the artists ."}
{"question": "The presidents thanked the managers who believed the author .", "answer": "The managers thanked the presidents ."}
{"question": "The secretaries who the authors supported recognized the judges .", "answer": "The authors recognized the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The bankers recommended the actor that the senators thanked .", "answer": "The senators recommended the bankers ."}
{"question": "The students that the managers contacted recommended the actor .", "answer": "The managers recommended the students ."}
{"question": "The students contacted the actor that the presidents supported .", "answer": "The presidents contacted the students ."}
{"question": "The athletes helped the students that contacted the senator .", "answer": "The students helped the athletes ."}
{"question": "The senators that called the managers contacted the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists contacted the managers ."}
{"question": "The lawyer that recognized the scientist believed the artists .", "answer": "The artists believed the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The scientists who recognized the managers saw the doctor .", "answer": "The managers saw the scientists ."}
{"question": "The scientists called the judge that stopped the doctors .", "answer": "The judge called the scientists ."}
{"question": "The presidents encouraged the athlete who helped the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers encouraged the presidents ."}
{"question": "The manager saw the student that the actor supported .", "answer": "The actor saw the manager ."}
{"question": "The manager that the senators admired called the lawyer .", "answer": "The senators called the manager ."}
{"question": "The bankers that the senator introduced saw the judge .", "answer": "The judge saw the bankers ."}
{"question": "The secretary avoided the professor that stopped the scientists .", "answer": "The professor avoided the the scientists ."}
{"question": "The banker avoided the lawyers who mentioned the actor .", "answer": "The lawyers avoided the the actor ."}
{"question": "The presidents supported the judge who encouraged the doctors .", "answer": "The judge supported the presidents ."}
{"question": "The professors who helped the managers contacted the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers contacted the professors ."}
{"question": "The tourist avoided the athletes that the bankers advised .", "answer": "The athletes avoided the bankers ."}
{"question": "The artist saw the judges who the students thanked .", "answer": "The judges saw the artist ."}
{"question": "The actor that the secretaries thanked encouraged the students .", "answer": "The students encouraged the actor ."}
{"question": "The scientist that the judge believed recommended the artists .", "answer": "The artists recommended the scientist ."}
{"question": "The student who the actor introduced saw the artist .", "answer": "The actor saw the student ."}
{"question": "The tourist avoided the doctors that recognized the authors .", "answer": "The doctors avoided the the authors ."}
{"question": "The doctor that saw the athletes stopped the bankers .", "answer": "The athletes stopped the doctor ."}
{"question": "The actor supported the athlete who avoided the senator .", "answer": "The senator supported the actor ."}
{"question": "The scientists believed the athlete who the senators recognized .", "answer": "The athlete believed the scientists ."}
{"question": "The athletes who encouraged the bankers admired the senator .", "answer": "The senator admired the bankers ."}
{"question": "The judge advised the author that the lawyer mentioned .", "answer": "The author advised the judge ."}
{"question": "The managers who contacted the artists stopped the presidents .", "answer": "The artists stopped the managers ."}
{"question": "The judge admired the author that the lawyers recommended .", "answer": "The author admired the judge ."}
{"question": "The lawyers helped the bankers that stopped the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists helped the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The professors advised the bankers that contacted the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists advised the professors ."}
{"question": "The actors believed the tourist that the students advised .", "answer": "The students believed the actors ."}
{"question": "The bankers who the actor saw contacted the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists contacted the actor ."}
{"question": "The lawyer that the artist stopped recognized the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor recognized the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The scientist advised the professors that avoided the judges .", "answer": "The professors advised the the judges ."}
{"question": "The secretary that recognized the student stopped the artist .", "answer": "The artist stopped the student ."}
{"question": "The athlete thanked the secretaries that stopped the managers .", "answer": "The secretaries thanked the the managers ."}
{"question": "The authors advised the professor who the artist thanked .", "answer": "The professor advised the artist ."}
{"question": "The presidents supported the banker who advised the actors .", "answer": "The banker supported the presidents ."}
{"question": "The senator thanked the lawyer that the judge mentioned .", "answer": "The lawyer thanked the judge ."}
{"question": "The presidents supported the authors who the manager mentioned .", "answer": "The manager supported the presidents ."}
{"question": "The senator who recognized the artists mentioned the professor .", "answer": "The professor mentioned the artists ."}
{"question": "The author who believed the scientist admired the students .", "answer": "The scientist admired the author ."}
{"question": "The presidents introduced the artists who encouraged the actor .", "answer": "The artists introduced the the actor ."}
{"question": "The senators called the judges who contacted the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor called the senators ."}
{"question": "The president avoided the doctor that stopped the secretary .", "answer": "The doctor avoided the president ."}
{"question": "The presidents contacted the tourists who advised the doctors .", "answer": "The tourists contacted the the doctors ."}
{"question": "The actor supported the senators who contacted the students .", "answer": "The senators supported the actor ."}
{"question": "The manager encouraged the banker that admired the tourist .", "answer": "The banker encouraged the manager ."}
{"question": "The tourist recognized the artist that helped the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete recognized the tourist ."}
{"question": "The lawyers saw the scientists who the athlete recommended .", "answer": "The scientists saw the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The students admired the senator who believed the banker .", "answer": "The senator admired the the banker ."}
{"question": "The doctor that the scientist admired mentioned the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents mentioned the doctor ."}
{"question": "The senator who the doctor avoided mentioned the artists .", "answer": "The artists mentioned the senator ."}
{"question": "The senators supported the professors who helped the banker .", "answer": "The professors supported the senators ."}
{"question": "The lawyers that the manager introduced mentioned the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete mentioned the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The professors who avoided the students helped the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists helped the students ."}
{"question": "The president that the students introduced mentioned the banker .", "answer": "The banker mentioned the students ."}
{"question": "The doctor that the athletes contacted supported the senators .", "answer": "The senators supported the doctor ."}
{"question": "The senator who the artist introduced helped the student .", "answer": "The artist helped the senator ."}
{"question": "The professor called the bankers that the lawyer believed .", "answer": "The bankers called the professor ."}
{"question": "The tourists that the actors helped saw the managers .", "answer": "The managers saw the tourists ."}
{"question": "The tourist who believed the students supported the managers .", "answer": "The students supported the tourist ."}
{"question": "The banker who admired the lawyers helped the judge .", "answer": "The judge helped the banker ."}
{"question": "The professors that called the president avoided the student .", "answer": "The student avoided the president ."}
{"question": "The judges helped the doctor who contacted the manager .", "answer": "The doctor helped the judges ."}
{"question": "The authors called the students who mentioned the banker .", "answer": "The banker called the authors ."}
{"question": "The author encouraged the president that the doctor believed .", "answer": "The doctor encouraged the author ."}
{"question": "The author introduced the athletes who recognized the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors introduced the author ."}
{"question": "The scientists contacted the actor who admired the artists .", "answer": "The actor contacted the the artists ."}
{"question": "The artists that admired the lawyer believed the judges .", "answer": "The judges believed the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The athlete who the student introduced contacted the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists contacted the athlete ."}
{"question": "The secretary admired the scientist that the judge advised .", "answer": "The scientist admired the secretary ."}
{"question": "The athlete supported the actors that helped the student .", "answer": "The student supported the athlete ."}
{"question": "The senators called the actors who the banker helped .", "answer": "The banker called the senators ."}
{"question": "The artist who admired the author called the secretaries .", "answer": "The author called the artist ."}
{"question": "The president admired the scientist who the tourist mentioned .", "answer": "The scientist admired the president ."}
{"question": "The athlete supported the tourist that the president avoided .", "answer": "The president supported the athlete ."}
{"question": "The lawyer who supported the author advised the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists advised the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The doctors who called the senators admired the athletes .", "answer": "The senators admired the doctors ."}
{"question": "The athletes that mentioned the banker supported the senators .", "answer": "The senators supported the athletes ."}
{"question": "The author who encouraged the tourists recognized the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist recognized the tourists ."}
{"question": "The athlete supported the president who the actors called .", "answer": "The president supported the actors ."}
{"question": "The banker advised the scientists that stopped the professors .", "answer": "The professors advised the banker ."}
{"question": "The judge avoided the senators who believed the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists avoided the judge ."}
{"question": "The presidents who recognized the scientist recommended the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists recommended the presidents ."}
{"question": "The banker encouraged the doctors that saw the actor .", "answer": "The doctors encouraged the banker ."}
{"question": "The president thanked the student who avoided the professor .", "answer": "The student thanked the president ."}
{"question": "The tourists advised the actor that contacted the lawyers .", "answer": "The actor advised the tourists ."}
{"question": "The presidents who recognized the author helped the students .", "answer": "The students helped the author ."}
{"question": "The doctor who the lawyers avoided called the judge .", "answer": "The judge called the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The doctors who the actors thanked believed the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers believed the actors ."}
{"question": "The students advised the artist who the lawyers admired .", "answer": "The artist advised the students ."}
{"question": "The judge helped the authors that the manager encouraged .", "answer": "The manager helped the judge ."}
{"question": "The secretaries that the scientists believed recognized the artist .", "answer": "The scientists recognized the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The lawyers called the students that the senator thanked .", "answer": "The senator called the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The managers who the senator helped recognized the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete recognized the managers ."}
{"question": "The senator who the doctor mentioned recognized the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers recognized the senator ."}
{"question": "The managers contacted the secretary who the doctors advised .", "answer": "The doctors contacted the managers ."}
{"question": "The actors that the tourist introduced recognized the banker .", "answer": "The banker recognized the actors ."}
{"question": "The managers stopped the professors who thanked the secretaries .", "answer": "The professors stopped the managers ."}
{"question": "The actor introduced the senator that the scientist recommended .", "answer": "The scientist introduced the actor ."}
{"question": "The managers who mentioned the senators advised the judges .", "answer": "The judges advised the managers ."}
{"question": "The manager mentioned the authors who the students contacted .", "answer": "The authors mentioned the students ."}
{"question": "The professors that called the manager admired the doctors .", "answer": "The manager admired the professors ."}
{"question": "The doctor avoided the scientist that recognized the presidents .", "answer": "The scientist avoided the doctor ."}
{"question": "The doctor advised the presidents who the artists avoided .", "answer": "The presidents advised the doctor ."}
{"question": "The authors who contacted the senator mentioned the athletes .", "answer": "The senator mentioned the authors ."}
{"question": "The presidents that the actor saw contacted the lawyer .", "answer": "The actor contacted the presidents ."}
{"question": "The student supported the artist who the tourists stopped .", "answer": "The artist supported the tourists ."}
{"question": "The artist that the banker mentioned thanked the actor .", "answer": "The banker thanked the artist ."}
{"question": "The tourist admired the professor who the secretary stopped .", "answer": "The secretary admired the tourist ."}
{"question": "The tourists avoided the student who the artists saw .", "answer": "The student avoided the artists ."}
{"question": "The students that the athletes introduced believed the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer believed the athletes ."}
{"question": "The actor that the doctor recognized thanked the lawyers .", "answer": "The doctor thanked the actor ."}
{"question": "The manager stopped the doctors who recognized the senators .", "answer": "The doctors stopped the the senators ."}
{"question": "The professor advised the author that the doctors stopped .", "answer": "The author advised the doctors ."}
{"question": "The tourists that the artist thanked stopped the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete stopped the tourists ."}
{"question": "The actor recommended the athlete that stopped the manager .", "answer": "The athlete recommended the actor ."}
{"question": "The judges saw the doctor that supported the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist saw the judges ."}
{"question": "The artists thanked the actor that recognized the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents thanked the artists ."}
{"question": "The scientist called the banker that the artists contacted .", "answer": "The banker called the artists ."}
{"question": "The athlete who the students recommended contacted the author .", "answer": "The author contacted the students ."}
{"question": "The judge recognized the manager who the actors supported .", "answer": "The manager recognized the judge ."}
{"question": "The presidents who the artist admired mentioned the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries mentioned the artist ."}
{"question": "The authors that the doctors supported introduced the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes introduced the doctors ."}
{"question": "The author recommended the lawyer who the athletes helped .", "answer": "The lawyer recommended the author ."}
{"question": "The athlete mentioned the scientists who helped the artists .", "answer": "The scientists mentioned the the artists ."}
{"question": "The secretaries who helped the athlete saw the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers saw the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The lawyers who the doctor introduced avoided the actor .", "answer": "The actor avoided the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The manager stopped the professor that introduced the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete stopped the manager ."}
{"question": "The student who the judges introduced saw the athlete .", "answer": "The judges saw the student ."}
{"question": "The managers that the bankers supported thanked the judge .", "answer": "The judge thanked the managers ."}
{"question": "The banker who helped the author stopped the artists .", "answer": "The artists stopped the banker ."}
{"question": "The actors called the lawyer that advised the manager .", "answer": "The lawyer called the the manager ."}
{"question": "The secretaries believed the doctors who advised the athletes .", "answer": "The doctors believed the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The scientist who saw the secretaries called the artists .", "answer": "The artists called the scientist ."}
{"question": "The secretary mentioned the athletes who the senator stopped .", "answer": "The athletes mentioned the secretary ."}
{"question": "The presidents who saw the banker thanked the scientist .", "answer": "The banker thanked the presidents ."}
{"question": "The judges that the senators believed contacted the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary contacted the senators ."}
{"question": "The student who the athlete recognized contacted the authors .", "answer": "The authors contacted the athlete ."}
{"question": "The scientists mentioned the professors that admired the judges .", "answer": "The professors mentioned the the judges ."}
{"question": "The managers advised the professor who the actors helped .", "answer": "The professor advised the managers ."}
{"question": "The judges that called the author saw the artist .", "answer": "The author saw the judges ."}
{"question": "The lawyers who the judge recognized admired the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists admired the judge ."}
{"question": "The manager supported the judges that the actor mentioned .", "answer": "The judges supported the actor ."}
{"question": "The tourist that the athletes thanked called the lawyer .", "answer": "The athletes called the tourist ."}
{"question": "The secretary who called the professors mentioned the judge .", "answer": "The judge mentioned the secretary ."}
{"question": "The actor mentioned the doctor that recognized the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents mentioned the actor ."}
{"question": "The students avoided the senator who the doctors advised .", "answer": "The senator avoided the doctors ."}
{"question": "The author encouraged the judges who the managers introduced .", "answer": "The judges encouraged the author ."}
{"question": "The students supported the banker who helped the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors supported the students ."}
{"question": "The athlete believed the actors that mentioned the tourist .", "answer": "The actors believed the the tourist ."}
{"question": "The presidents who the secretary stopped helped the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor helped the secretary ."}
{"question": "The athlete avoided the secretary who believed the senator .", "answer": "The senator avoided the athlete ."}
{"question": "The doctors introduced the tourists that the secretaries helped .", "answer": "The tourists introduced the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The scientists helped the banker that advised the author .", "answer": "The banker helped the scientists ."}
{"question": "The judges encouraged the lawyers that the professor contacted .", "answer": "The professor encouraged the judges ."}
{"question": "The athlete who the doctors supported helped the professors .", "answer": "The professors helped the doctors ."}
{"question": "The doctors who the presidents believed mentioned the athlete .", "answer": "The presidents mentioned the doctors ."}
{"question": "The professors that recommended the managers recognized the senators .", "answer": "The managers recognized the professors ."}
{"question": "The athletes who helped the authors recognized the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents recognized the athletes ."}
{"question": "The student supported the senators who stopped the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists supported the student ."}
{"question": "The bankers introduced the professor that mentioned the judge .", "answer": "The judge introduced the bankers ."}
{"question": "The actors stopped the student who the bankers avoided .", "answer": "The student stopped the actors ."}
{"question": "The author who encouraged the bankers thanked the manager .", "answer": "The manager thanked the author ."}
{"question": "The students recommended the athletes who the secretaries advised .", "answer": "The athletes recommended the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The scientist who the tourists helped thanked the actors .", "answer": "The tourists thanked the scientist ."}
{"question": "The doctor called the managers that avoided the lawyers .", "answer": "The managers called the the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The judge that believed the actors avoided the authors .", "answer": "The authors avoided the actors ."}
{"question": "The athlete supported the actors that the scientists introduced .", "answer": "The actors supported the scientists ."}
{"question": "The judge helped the presidents that the bankers stopped .", "answer": "The presidents helped the judge ."}
{"question": "The student who helped the tourist encouraged the actors .", "answer": "The actors encouraged the tourist ."}
{"question": "The athlete called the authors that the banker mentioned .", "answer": "The authors called the banker ."}
{"question": "The lawyer that helped the actor admired the professors .", "answer": "The professors admired the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The actors that mentioned the senators thanked the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary thanked the senators ."}
{"question": "The student that the bankers saw avoided the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor avoided the student ."}
{"question": "The judge who the authors contacted recommended the students .", "answer": "The students recommended the judge ."}
{"question": "The author supported the artists who saw the tourists .", "answer": "The artists supported the the tourists ."}
{"question": "The secretaries believed the bankers who introduced the scientists .", "answer": "The bankers believed the the scientists ."}
{"question": "The senators who the bankers introduced believed the president .", "answer": "The bankers believed the senators ."}
{"question": "The actors encouraged the president who helped the artist .", "answer": "The president encouraged the actors ."}
{"question": "The secretary supported the bankers who the artist advised .", "answer": "The artist supported the secretary ."}
{"question": "The judge thanked the athlete that the lawyer recognized .", "answer": "The athlete thanked the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The doctor helped the senator that the actor called .", "answer": "The senator helped the actor ."}
{"question": "The students who the author helped stopped the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists stopped the students ."}
{"question": "The lawyers who supported the actor called the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents called the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The president contacted the lawyer that believed the actors .", "answer": "The actors contacted the president ."}
{"question": "The manager that the actors called mentioned the senators .", "answer": "The senators mentioned the manager ."}
{"question": "The professor avoided the manager that the scientists encouraged .", "answer": "The manager avoided the scientists ."}
{"question": "The actor contacted the lawyer who saw the managers .", "answer": "The lawyer contacted the the managers ."}
{"question": "The manager avoided the student that the bankers believed .", "answer": "The student avoided the bankers ."}
{"question": "The senator who encouraged the professor recommended the athlete .", "answer": "The professor recommended the senator ."}
{"question": "The professor stopped the students that the secretary called .", "answer": "The students stopped the secretary ."}
{"question": "The president that the judge thanked saw the banker .", "answer": "The banker saw the judge ."}
{"question": "The student who thanked the athlete recognized the lawyer .", "answer": "The athlete recognized the student ."}
{"question": "The professor supported the doctor that avoided the student .", "answer": "The doctor supported the professor ."}
{"question": "The tourist advised the bankers who the doctors contacted .", "answer": "The bankers advised the doctors ."}
{"question": "The authors who the athletes avoided advised the actors .", "answer": "The athletes advised the authors ."}
{"question": "The secretaries avoided the students that the athlete contacted .", "answer": "The students avoided the athlete ."}
{"question": "The senator that recommended the secretary called the president .", "answer": "The secretary called the senator ."}
{"question": "The doctor stopped the presidents that believed the artist .", "answer": "The presidents stopped the doctor ."}
{"question": "The presidents who recognized the judges supported the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers supported the presidents ."}
{"question": "The artists admired the athlete that saw the senator .", "answer": "The athlete admired the the senator ."}
{"question": "The students who the judges recommended stopped the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist stopped the students ."}
{"question": "The managers introduced the lawyer who the athlete believed .", "answer": "The lawyer introduced the athlete ."}
{"question": "The judge who the actor recognized contacted the artist .", "answer": "The actor contacted the judge ."}
{"question": "The athlete introduced the lawyers that the scientists believed .", "answer": "The lawyers introduced the scientists ."}
{"question": "The scientists saw the professors that the student recommended .", "answer": "The professors saw the scientists ."}
{"question": "The judges contacted the scientists that saw the doctor .", "answer": "The scientists contacted the the doctor ."}
{"question": "The doctor admired the senators who the lawyer recognized .", "answer": "The senators admired the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The senators helped the presidents who the professor supported .", "answer": "The professor helped the senators ."}
{"question": "The judges who recommended the senators introduced the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer introduced the judges ."}
{"question": "The lawyers that helped the managers called the president .", "answer": "The managers called the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The senator supported the president who the bankers thanked .", "answer": "The president supported the senator ."}
{"question": "The student that the athletes admired contacted the artists .", "answer": "The artists contacted the student ."}
{"question": "The author recommended the bankers who advised the secretary .", "answer": "The bankers recommended the author ."}
{"question": "The athletes recommended the doctors that the managers recognized .", "answer": "The managers recommended the athletes ."}
{"question": "The presidents that avoided the actors helped the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist helped the presidents ."}
{"question": "The authors that the tourists mentioned helped the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary helped the tourists ."}
{"question": "The lawyer helped the athlete who believed the artist .", "answer": "The athlete helped the the artist ."}
{"question": "The professor who the president recognized introduced the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries introduced the professor ."}
{"question": "The banker advised the athletes who called the authors .", "answer": "The athletes advised the banker ."}
{"question": "The student supported the bankers that believed the secretary .", "answer": "The bankers supported the the secretary ."}
{"question": "The banker avoided the tourist who the presidents contacted .", "answer": "The presidents avoided the banker ."}
{"question": "The athletes saw the scientists who the senator recommended .", "answer": "The scientists saw the athletes ."}
{"question": "The author who the professors recognized advised the president .", "answer": "The professors advised the author ."}
{"question": "The bankers who the judge introduced recommended the authors .", "answer": "The authors recommended the bankers ."}
{"question": "The scientists who avoided the athletes thanked the artist .", "answer": "The artist thanked the athletes ."}
{"question": "The tourists recommended the artist that the lawyer admired .", "answer": "The artist recommended the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The banker saw the secretaries who advised the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist saw the banker ."}
{"question": "The judge helped the managers who called the artist .", "answer": "The artist helped the judge ."}
{"question": "The athletes that believed the banker thanked the actor .", "answer": "The banker thanked the athletes ."}
{"question": "The secretaries stopped the athlete that the tourists introduced .", "answer": "The tourists stopped the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The actors stopped the judge that supported the artists .", "answer": "The judge stopped the the artists ."}
{"question": "The artists avoided the scientists who recommended the professor .", "answer": "The scientists avoided the the professor ."}
{"question": "The banker saw the manager that recognized the artists .", "answer": "The artists saw the banker ."}
{"question": "The senators who the students recognized recommended the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist recommended the senators ."}
{"question": "The actor that the artist mentioned supported the senators .", "answer": "The senators supported the artist ."}
{"question": "The secretary who the athletes avoided thanked the managers .", "answer": "The managers thanked the athletes ."}
{"question": "The student encouraged the athletes who helped the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist encouraged the student ."}
{"question": "The tourist mentioned the doctors who called the judges .", "answer": "The doctors mentioned the tourist ."}
{"question": "The lawyers that the banker called recognized the author .", "answer": "The author recognized the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The bankers avoided the artist who introduced the president .", "answer": "The artist avoided the the president ."}
{"question": "The manager recognized the senator that the athletes mentioned .", "answer": "The senator recognized the athletes ."}
{"question": "The senators thanked the scientist that introduced the actor .", "answer": "The actor thanked the senators ."}
{"question": "The scientists contacted the secretary that recommended the author .", "answer": "The author contacted the scientists ."}
{"question": "The artists introduced the secretary who the authors encouraged .", "answer": "The secretary introduced the artists ."}
{"question": "The doctors that the lawyers supported recognized the actors .", "answer": "The actors recognized the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The artists called the students that the athlete thanked .", "answer": "The athlete called the artists ."}
{"question": "The managers who called the doctor encouraged the senators .", "answer": "The senators encouraged the managers ."}
{"question": "The professors helped the doctor that the manager mentioned .", "answer": "The doctor helped the manager ."}
{"question": "The bankers who stopped the secretary believed the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists believed the bankers ."}
{"question": "The student who the author contacted advised the senators .", "answer": "The senators advised the student ."}
{"question": "The professor who helped the athletes introduced the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries introduced the professor ."}
{"question": "The student who the actors thanked contacted the manager .", "answer": "The actors contacted the student ."}
{"question": "The presidents that believed the secretaries called the manager .", "answer": "The manager called the presidents ."}
{"question": "The professor who the judge saw called the secretary .", "answer": "The judge called the professor ."}
{"question": "The managers that introduced the lawyers believed the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor believed the managers ."}
{"question": "The lawyers mentioned the senator who helped the bankers .", "answer": "The senator mentioned the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The judge who thanked the senator contacted the actors .", "answer": "The actors contacted the senator ."}
{"question": "The secretaries encouraged the scientists that the lawyer recognized .", "answer": "The scientists encouraged the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The students stopped the tourist that encouraged the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers stopped the students ."}
{"question": "The scientist who supported the judges contacted the president .", "answer": "The judges contacted the scientist ."}
{"question": "The scientist called the lawyers who the manager introduced .", "answer": "The lawyers called the manager ."}
{"question": "The secretaries who admired the authors introduced the scientists .", "answer": "The authors introduced the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The athletes recommended the lawyer that the banker contacted .", "answer": "The lawyer recommended the athletes ."}
{"question": "The secretary thanked the actor that the president saw .", "answer": "The actor thanked the president ."}
{"question": "The secretary that the actors called admired the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist admired the actors ."}
{"question": "The students who thanked the athletes introduced the tourist .", "answer": "The athletes introduced the students ."}
{"question": "The student who recognized the doctor thanked the artists .", "answer": "The artists thanked the student ."}
{"question": "The judges saw the athlete that avoided the tourists .", "answer": "The athlete saw the the tourists ."}
{"question": "The tourists advised the artists that recommended the lawyers .", "answer": "The artists advised the tourists ."}
{"question": "The managers that the athletes avoided saw the president .", "answer": "The athletes saw the managers ."}
{"question": "The professor advised the president that admired the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist advised the professor ."}
{"question": "The manager that the tourist stopped mentioned the doctors .", "answer": "The tourist mentioned the manager ."}
{"question": "The lawyer stopped the authors who the tourists helped .", "answer": "The authors stopped the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The lawyers mentioned the student who the president recommended .", "answer": "The student mentioned the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The actor that the professor recognized encouraged the artist .", "answer": "The artist encouraged the actor ."}
{"question": "The secretary called the authors that the banker contacted .", "answer": "The banker called the secretary ."}
{"question": "The senators who the athletes called advised the author .", "answer": "The athletes advised the senators ."}
{"question": "The doctor who believed the presidents encouraged the author .", "answer": "The author encouraged the presidents ."}
{"question": "The actors that supported the bankers called the scientist .", "answer": "The bankers called the actors ."}
{"question": "The scientists who the tourist helped contacted the actor .", "answer": "The tourist contacted the scientists ."}
{"question": "The artists that thanked the judge helped the presidents .", "answer": "The judge helped the artists ."}
{"question": "The artists saw the actors who the lawyer introduced .", "answer": "The actors saw the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The athletes that contacted the secretaries called the judge .", "answer": "The judge called the athletes ."}
{"question": "The president believed the student who the author admired .", "answer": "The student believed the author ."}
{"question": "The president avoided the managers that mentioned the doctor .", "answer": "The managers avoided the president ."}
{"question": "The actors recognized the managers that the authors avoided .", "answer": "The managers recognized the authors ."}
{"question": "The student who the actors recognized contacted the artist .", "answer": "The artist contacted the actors ."}
{"question": "The doctor that encouraged the secretaries supported the senator .", "answer": "The secretaries supported the doctor ."}
{"question": "The athlete avoided the doctor who helped the scientists .", "answer": "The doctor avoided the athlete ."}
{"question": "The artist stopped the actor who supported the tourist .", "answer": "The actor stopped the artist ."}
{"question": "The doctors that recommended the tourist admired the banker .", "answer": "The tourist admired the doctors ."}
{"question": "The managers called the artist who the professors stopped .", "answer": "The artist called the managers ."}
{"question": "The judge that the presidents believed contacted the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor contacted the presidents ."}
{"question": "The student avoided the scientists who called the lawyers .", "answer": "The scientists avoided the student ."}
{"question": "The president mentioned the lawyers that called the authors .", "answer": "The lawyers mentioned the president ."}
{"question": "The secretary that the artist admired advised the judges .", "answer": "The judges advised the artist ."}
{"question": "The professors mentioned the author who stopped the tourists .", "answer": "The author mentioned the professors ."}
{"question": "The student who recommended the actor believed the presidents .", "answer": "The actor believed the student ."}
{"question": "The doctor mentioned the athletes that supported the author .", "answer": "The athletes mentioned the doctor ."}
{"question": "The bankers believed the professor who advised the senator .", "answer": "The senator believed the bankers ."}
{"question": "The doctors advised the senator who the artist contacted .", "answer": "The senator advised the doctors ."}
{"question": "The judge avoided the scientist who the president advised .", "answer": "The president avoided the judge ."}
{"question": "The artists that the tourist stopped recommended the senator .", "answer": "The senator recommended the tourist ."}
{"question": "The scientists called the secretary that stopped the professor .", "answer": "The professor called the scientists ."}
{"question": "The scientists recognized the presidents that the bankers mentioned .", "answer": "The presidents recognized the bankers ."}
{"question": "The bankers that the judges supported believed the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents believed the judges ."}
{"question": "The doctor admired the scientists that the author helped .", "answer": "The scientists admired the author ."}
{"question": "The bankers recommended the senators who the athletes thanked .", "answer": "The senators recommended the bankers ."}
{"question": "The professors mentioned the president who believed the judge .", "answer": "The president mentioned the professors ."}
{"question": "The tourists that the author advised believed the president .", "answer": "The president believed the author ."}
{"question": "The students supported the artists who advised the presidents .", "answer": "The artists supported the the presidents ."}
{"question": "The presidents that the authors recommended believed the actor .", "answer": "The authors believed the presidents ."}
{"question": "The bankers who the secretaries thanked stopped the managers .", "answer": "The managers stopped the bankers ."}
{"question": "The scientist thanked the secretary who the artist advised .", "answer": "The artist thanked the scientist ."}
{"question": "The judges admired the senators who the students avoided .", "answer": "The students admired the judges ."}
{"question": "The judge introduced the presidents that thanked the managers .", "answer": "The presidents introduced the the managers ."}
{"question": "The judge saw the author that helped the actor .", "answer": "The author saw the the actor ."}
{"question": "The actors mentioned the judges that saw the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor mentioned the actors ."}
{"question": "The doctors who the athlete believed stopped the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries stopped the doctors ."}
{"question": "The tourist that the judges saw recognized the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers recognized the tourist ."}
{"question": "The doctor admired the judge who the athlete helped .", "answer": "The judge admired the doctor ."}
{"question": "The athlete believed the artists who the scientist recognized .", "answer": "The artists believed the athlete ."}
{"question": "The lawyers believed the judge who advised the athlete .", "answer": "The judge believed the the athlete ."}
{"question": "The president who saw the managers introduced the judges .", "answer": "The judges introduced the president ."}
{"question": "The authors that the lawyer mentioned recommended the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors recommended the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The professors who supported the managers thanked the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers thanked the managers ."}
{"question": "The managers contacted the presidents who encouraged the students .", "answer": "The presidents contacted the the students ."}
{"question": "The athlete admired the scientist who helped the student .", "answer": "The scientist admired the athlete ."}
{"question": "The manager stopped the doctor who avoided the scientists .", "answer": "The doctor stopped the the scientists ."}
{"question": "The professors called the tourist that the author stopped .", "answer": "The author called the professors ."}
{"question": "The scientist mentioned the manager that the student recommended .", "answer": "The manager mentioned the scientist ."}
{"question": "The tourist that the presidents helped contacted the manager .", "answer": "The manager contacted the presidents ."}
{"question": "The authors that the tourist supported believed the doctor .", "answer": "The tourist believed the authors ."}
{"question": "The senator believed the artist who the banker supported .", "answer": "The artist believed the senator ."}
{"question": "The actor who supported the manager contacted the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents contacted the actor ."}
{"question": "The banker that the student helped supported the managers .", "answer": "The student supported the banker ."}
{"question": "The judges stopped the athlete who recommended the artists .", "answer": "The athlete stopped the judges ."}
{"question": "The banker that called the professor believed the manager .", "answer": "The professor believed the banker ."}
{"question": "The scientists who supported the lawyers helped the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors helped the scientists ."}
{"question": "The professors recognized the judges who avoided the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries recognized the professors ."}
{"question": "The lawyers who avoided the doctor thanked the banker .", "answer": "The doctor thanked the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The actors contacted the author who stopped the students .", "answer": "The students contacted the actors ."}
{"question": "The professor encouraged the doctors that the bankers avoided .", "answer": "The bankers encouraged the professor ."}
{"question": "The scientists who helped the tourists contacted the artists .", "answer": "The artists contacted the tourists ."}
{"question": "The artist that the authors called recognized the students .", "answer": "The authors recognized the artist ."}
{"question": "The artists who believed the bankers recognized the secretaries .", "answer": "The bankers recognized the artists ."}
{"question": "The athletes that contacted the lawyer avoided the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists avoided the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The manager who saw the doctors introduced the senator .", "answer": "The senator introduced the manager ."}
{"question": "The student introduced the lawyers who saw the artist .", "answer": "The artist introduced the student ."}
{"question": "The judge introduced the tourists that advised the banker .", "answer": "The tourists introduced the the banker ."}
{"question": "The judges who recommended the actors avoided the student .", "answer": "The student avoided the judges ."}
{"question": "The secretary that the presidents admired introduced the professor .", "answer": "The professor introduced the secretary ."}
{"question": "The president that the students helped mentioned the judges .", "answer": "The judges mentioned the students ."}
{"question": "The artists that believed the author introduced the president .", "answer": "The author introduced the artists ."}
{"question": "The scientists who contacted the managers called the artist .", "answer": "The artist called the scientists ."}
{"question": "The tourists thanked the bankers that the authors encouraged .", "answer": "The bankers thanked the authors ."}
{"question": "The artists that avoided the secretary recommended the lawyer .", "answer": "The secretary recommended the artists ."}
{"question": "The tourists who the manager admired advised the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents advised the tourists ."}
{"question": "The managers recognized the tourists that supported the bankers .", "answer": "The tourists recognized the the bankers ."}
{"question": "The artists who recommended the author stopped the president .", "answer": "The president stopped the artists ."}
{"question": "The tourist that the judges recognized mentioned the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents mentioned the tourist ."}
{"question": "The bankers who the actors recommended helped the judges .", "answer": "The actors helped the bankers ."}
{"question": "The lawyers who avoided the bankers introduced the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors introduced the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The artists who the doctors contacted believed the president .", "answer": "The president believed the doctors ."}
{"question": "The athlete who the presidents stopped introduced the manager .", "answer": "The presidents introduced the athlete ."}
{"question": "The presidents stopped the athletes that called the scientist .", "answer": "The athletes stopped the presidents ."}
{"question": "The manager that avoided the students admired the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries admired the students ."}
{"question": "The actors recommended the presidents who mentioned the athlete .", "answer": "The presidents recommended the the athlete ."}
{"question": "The actor contacted the banker that helped the author .", "answer": "The banker contacted the the author ."}
{"question": "The scientist who the author recognized admired the banker .", "answer": "The banker admired the author ."}
{"question": "The artists stopped the banker who the tourists helped .", "answer": "The tourists stopped the artists ."}
{"question": "The artists recommended the secretaries who admired the student .", "answer": "The student recommended the artists ."}
{"question": "The scientists thanked the lawyer that contacted the students .", "answer": "The students thanked the scientists ."}
{"question": "The managers that the professors saw recommended the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes recommended the professors ."}
{"question": "The students that stopped the professor advised the president .", "answer": "The president advised the professor ."}
{"question": "The secretaries mentioned the athlete who stopped the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists mentioned the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The author that the president called recognized the judge .", "answer": "The judge recognized the author ."}
{"question": "The secretary who the presidents avoided admired the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor admired the presidents ."}
{"question": "The judges advised the scientist that the tourist avoided .", "answer": "The tourist advised the judges ."}
{"question": "The authors admired the professor that the scientist saw .", "answer": "The professor admired the authors ."}
{"question": "The athlete who saw the senator called the president .", "answer": "The president called the senator ."}
{"question": "The judges contacted the doctor that saw the bankers .", "answer": "The doctor contacted the judges ."}
{"question": "The doctors who believed the athletes recommended the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers recommended the doctors ."}
{"question": "The doctor that the tourists contacted helped the student .", "answer": "The student helped the tourists ."}
{"question": "The professors who the judge helped admired the author .", "answer": "The judge admired the professors ."}
{"question": "The tourists who the artist avoided called the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor called the artist ."}
{"question": "The tourists mentioned the senators that advised the actor .", "answer": "The senators mentioned the the actor ."}
{"question": "The banker mentioned the student who admired the secretary .", "answer": "The student mentioned the banker ."}
{"question": "The athletes who the senators believed helped the actors .", "answer": "The actors helped the athletes ."}
{"question": "The senators that the scientist admired introduced the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists introduced the scientist ."}
{"question": "The scientist that the tourists mentioned supported the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary supported the scientist ."}
{"question": "The artists stopped the students that encouraged the judges .", "answer": "The students stopped the artists ."}
{"question": "The doctor supported the president who recommended the authors .", "answer": "The president supported the the authors ."}
{"question": "The scientist encouraged the president that saw the banker .", "answer": "The banker encouraged the scientist ."}
{"question": "The tourist who the president contacted supported the athlete .", "answer": "The president supported the tourist ."}
{"question": "The author that the professors avoided recognized the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents recognized the author ."}
{"question": "The senator who the doctor recognized admired the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete admired the senator ."}
{"question": "The lawyer recommended the judges who encouraged the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists recommended the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The judge that encouraged the presidents called the lawyers .", "answer": "The presidents called the judge ."}
{"question": "The judges encouraged the presidents who the secretary helped .", "answer": "The secretary encouraged the judges ."}
{"question": "The authors who advised the lawyer stopped the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists stopped the authors ."}
{"question": "The student that supported the doctors introduced the actors .", "answer": "The actors introduced the student ."}
{"question": "The actor avoided the tourists that the secretary encouraged .", "answer": "The secretary avoided the actor ."}
{"question": "The secretaries who admired the artists recognized the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist recognized the artists ."}
{"question": "The tourist helped the artist who supported the senator .", "answer": "The senator helped the tourist ."}
{"question": "The scientist that the athlete avoided recommended the artist .", "answer": "The artist recommended the scientist ."}
{"question": "The lawyers supported the actor that advised the athlete .", "answer": "The actor supported the the athlete ."}
{"question": "The actor introduced the lawyers who thanked the senators .", "answer": "The lawyers introduced the the senators ."}
{"question": "The secretaries who the authors believed supported the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists supported the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The bankers that the actors saw recommended the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes recommended the actors ."}
{"question": "The scientists supported the senator who the managers encouraged .", "answer": "The senator supported the scientists ."}
{"question": "The students contacted the artist who the senator recognized .", "answer": "The senator contacted the students ."}
{"question": "The banker called the artist that believed the tourists .", "answer": "The artist called the the tourists ."}
{"question": "The doctors believed the presidents that the artists called .", "answer": "The artists believed the doctors ."}
{"question": "The authors encouraged the bankers who the doctor recommended .", "answer": "The doctor encouraged the authors ."}
{"question": "The doctor who helped the tourists advised the professor .", "answer": "The professor advised the tourists ."}
{"question": "The professors thanked the student who the tourists introduced .", "answer": "The student thanked the tourists ."}
{"question": "The judges who the president recommended advised the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist advised the judges ."}
{"question": "The professors supported the president who the tourists contacted .", "answer": "The tourists supported the professors ."}
{"question": "The students recognized the actors that the doctor recommended .", "answer": "The doctor recognized the students ."}
{"question": "The lawyer that the president admired recognized the judges .", "answer": "The judges recognized the president ."}
{"question": "The judge that admired the bankers mentioned the artist .", "answer": "The bankers mentioned the judge ."}
{"question": "The manager called the athlete that recommended the professors .", "answer": "The professors called the manager ."}
{"question": "The authors that the lawyer admired introduced the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors introduced the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The president that believed the banker thanked the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes thanked the banker ."}
{"question": "The president thanked the manager who introduced the judges .", "answer": "The manager thanked the the judges ."}
{"question": "The lawyer avoided the judges who believed the banker .", "answer": "The judges avoided the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The tourist that the president avoided called the student .", "answer": "The president called the tourist ."}
{"question": "The bankers who recommended the president supported the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists supported the president ."}
{"question": "The scientists who the actors called recommended the manager .", "answer": "The manager recommended the actors ."}
{"question": "The actor advised the secretaries that saw the athlete .", "answer": "The secretaries advised the actor ."}
{"question": "The actors that the senator called mentioned the students .", "answer": "The students mentioned the senator ."}
{"question": "The scientist supported the banker who called the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary supported the scientist ."}
{"question": "The professor saw the lawyers that advised the students .", "answer": "The students saw the professor ."}
{"question": "The artists believed the athlete that stopped the lawyers .", "answer": "The athlete believed the artists ."}
{"question": "The lawyer that admired the authors introduced the students .", "answer": "The students introduced the authors ."}
{"question": "The manager saw the secretaries that contacted the artist .", "answer": "The secretaries saw the the artist ."}
{"question": "The tourist called the managers who the doctor encouraged .", "answer": "The doctor called the tourist ."}
{"question": "The judges who contacted the managers introduced the professors .", "answer": "The managers introduced the judges ."}
{"question": "The doctors that the lawyers called avoided the managers .", "answer": "The managers avoided the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The senator thanked the judges who supported the president .", "answer": "The president thanked the senator ."}
{"question": "The actor that advised the banker believed the scientists .", "answer": "The banker believed the actor ."}
{"question": "The athletes who advised the banker recommended the authors .", "answer": "The authors recommended the athletes ."}
{"question": "The professor stopped the scientist who mentioned the actors .", "answer": "The scientist stopped the the actors ."}
{"question": "The scientist thanked the tourists who the actor supported .", "answer": "The actor thanked the scientist ."}
{"question": "The lawyers that the tourist encouraged avoided the professors .", "answer": "The professors avoided the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The author who stopped the managers encouraged the actor .", "answer": "The actor encouraged the managers ."}
{"question": "The author who the doctor thanked supported the professor .", "answer": "The professor supported the author ."}
{"question": "The students who the presidents avoided saw the authors .", "answer": "The authors saw the presidents ."}
{"question": "The senators helped the managers who believed the presidents .", "answer": "The managers helped the the presidents ."}
{"question": "The scientist introduced the professor who saw the banker .", "answer": "The banker introduced the scientist ."}
{"question": "The judges who helped the authors supported the professors .", "answer": "The professors supported the judges ."}
{"question": "The lawyers helped the tourist who thanked the senators .", "answer": "The tourist helped the the senators ."}
{"question": "The actor who the professors saw avoided the banker .", "answer": "The banker avoided the professors ."}
{"question": "The student believed the artist that the managers mentioned .", "answer": "The artist believed the managers ."}
{"question": "The tourist that the secretary recognized admired the banker .", "answer": "The banker admired the tourist ."}
{"question": "The judge helped the secretaries who admired the actor .", "answer": "The secretaries helped the the actor ."}
{"question": "The scientists contacted the presidents who advised the secretaries .", "answer": "The presidents contacted the scientists ."}
{"question": "The athletes encouraged the secretaries that the judges believed .", "answer": "The secretaries encouraged the athletes ."}
{"question": "The artist thanked the athletes that stopped the judge .", "answer": "The judge thanked the artist ."}
{"question": "The tourists who the banker called thanked the president .", "answer": "The president thanked the banker ."}
{"question": "The tourists encouraged the authors who thanked the judges .", "answer": "The authors encouraged the the judges ."}
{"question": "The secretaries admired the president that the scientist stopped .", "answer": "The president admired the scientist ."}
{"question": "The scientists that avoided the actors recognized the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers recognized the scientists ."}
{"question": "The professors encouraged the student who saw the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists encouraged the professors ."}
{"question": "The students who the athlete believed recommended the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents recommended the students ."}
{"question": "The actors who helped the senators mentioned the artist .", "answer": "The artist mentioned the actors ."}
{"question": "The professor who recognized the tourist introduced the presidents .", "answer": "The tourist introduced the professor ."}
{"question": "The scientist that encouraged the athlete introduced the professor .", "answer": "The professor introduced the scientist ."}
{"question": "The bankers who the president admired mentioned the author .", "answer": "The author mentioned the bankers ."}
{"question": "The artists who contacted the actors helped the professor .", "answer": "The professor helped the artists ."}
{"question": "The scientist that the student encouraged helped the author .", "answer": "The author helped the scientist ."}
{"question": "The senators that the lawyers admired supported the authors .", "answer": "The authors supported the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The president who the manager recognized encouraged the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary encouraged the manager ."}
{"question": "The bankers encouraged the authors that the judges saw .", "answer": "The authors encouraged the bankers ."}
{"question": "The scientist mentioned the senators who the professors admired .", "answer": "The senators mentioned the scientist ."}
{"question": "The senators who the bankers introduced contacted the artist .", "answer": "The bankers contacted the senators ."}
{"question": "The tourist who introduced the banker contacted the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries contacted the banker ."}
{"question": "The secretaries that the judges believed encouraged the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor encouraged the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The professors that the authors recognized introduced the senator .", "answer": "The senator introduced the professors ."}
{"question": "The athletes who advised the student helped the managers .", "answer": "The managers helped the athletes ."}
{"question": "The manager thanked the presidents that believed the doctors .", "answer": "The presidents thanked the the doctors ."}
{"question": "The judge who the secretary believed stopped the professors .", "answer": "The professors stopped the secretary ."}
{"question": "The president who the doctor recommended introduced the tourist .", "answer": "The doctor introduced the president ."}
{"question": "The professor avoided the doctor that introduced the senator .", "answer": "The doctor avoided the the senator ."}
{"question": "The lawyer admired the manager that introduced the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents admired the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The scientist who thanked the tourist mentioned the judge .", "answer": "The judge mentioned the scientist ."}
{"question": "The professors that the judge introduced believed the manager .", "answer": "The judge believed the professors ."}
{"question": "The tourists that the artists saw avoided the professor .", "answer": "The artists avoided the tourists ."}
{"question": "The professors who the senator mentioned saw the scientists .", "answer": "The senator saw the professors ."}
{"question": "The scientist that called the banker recognized the manager .", "answer": "The manager recognized the scientist ."}
{"question": "The senators who stopped the tourist avoided the artist .", "answer": "The tourist avoided the senators ."}
{"question": "The artist thanked the author who called the professors .", "answer": "The author thanked the artist ."}
{"question": "The president admired the tourists who the doctor supported .", "answer": "The tourists admired the doctor ."}
{"question": "The judge supported the scientist that the presidents mentioned .", "answer": "The scientist supported the presidents ."}
{"question": "The bankers that encouraged the artists helped the secretaries .", "answer": "The artists helped the bankers ."}
{"question": "The doctor who the scientist stopped supported the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries supported the doctor ."}
{"question": "The author recommended the judges who called the banker .", "answer": "The judges recommended the author ."}
{"question": "The presidents introduced the artist that called the actor .", "answer": "The artist introduced the the actor ."}
{"question": "The judges who helped the presidents introduced the banker .", "answer": "The banker introduced the judges ."}
{"question": "The student avoided the scientist who the president helped .", "answer": "The president avoided the student ."}
{"question": "The professors who the secretary contacted recognized the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists recognized the professors ."}
{"question": "The author admired the scientist that thanked the presidents .", "answer": "The scientist admired the author ."}
{"question": "The authors recommended the senator that the lawyer introduced .", "answer": "The lawyer recommended the authors ."}
{"question": "The presidents who the doctor recommended advised the senator .", "answer": "The doctor advised the presidents ."}
{"question": "The author who the actors recognized introduced the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents introduced the author ."}
{"question": "The tourists thanked the lawyer who the author saw .", "answer": "The lawyer thanked the author ."}
{"question": "The senator believed the tourist who the scientists contacted .", "answer": "The tourist believed the scientists ."}
{"question": "The artists who encouraged the scientists introduced the actor .", "answer": "The actor introduced the artists ."}
{"question": "The professors who the author encouraged thanked the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists thanked the professors ."}
{"question": "The athlete helped the secretary that the lawyers mentioned .", "answer": "The secretary helped the athlete ."}
{"question": "The manager introduced the professors that advised the judges .", "answer": "The professors introduced the manager ."}
{"question": "The senators that the student believed advised the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries advised the senators ."}
{"question": "The managers that the lawyer recognized called the banker .", "answer": "The banker called the managers ."}
{"question": "The president that encouraged the actors introduced the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists introduced the actors ."}
{"question": "The actor stopped the senator that avoided the athlete .", "answer": "The senator stopped the the athlete ."}
{"question": "The lawyer saw the student who admired the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete saw the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The judges who helped the banker admired the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists admired the banker ."}
{"question": "The lawyers introduced the senator that the athletes mentioned .", "answer": "The senator introduced the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The presidents who saw the secretary admired the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers admired the presidents ."}
{"question": "The actors stopped the judge who the authors called .", "answer": "The authors stopped the actors ."}
{"question": "The banker recommended the secretary who helped the doctors .", "answer": "The secretary recommended the the doctors ."}
{"question": "The doctors encouraged the presidents that the secretaries recommended .", "answer": "The presidents encouraged the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The athlete who the presidents avoided supported the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors supported the presidents ."}
{"question": "The authors that contacted the lawyer encouraged the students .", "answer": "The students encouraged the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The tourists called the doctor who the lawyer advised .", "answer": "The lawyer called the tourists ."}
{"question": "The lawyer who the professor thanked avoided the managers .", "answer": "The professor avoided the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The senator that mentioned the actor contacted the artists .", "answer": "The artists contacted the senator ."}
{"question": "The artists encouraged the banker that admired the professors .", "answer": "The banker encouraged the the professors ."}
{"question": "The artist that called the scientist recommended the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries recommended the artist ."}
{"question": "The author saw the actor who the presidents admired .", "answer": "The actor saw the author ."}
{"question": "The artist who the judge called advised the banker .", "answer": "The banker advised the artist ."}
{"question": "The senators helped the doctor who the manager introduced .", "answer": "The doctor helped the senators ."}
{"question": "The doctor that the author recommended believed the artist .", "answer": "The artist believed the author ."}
{"question": "The president that the athlete advised avoided the actors .", "answer": "The athlete avoided the president ."}
{"question": "The artists stopped the actor that the senator recognized .", "answer": "The actor stopped the senator ."}
{"question": "The student who the senator introduced mentioned the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists mentioned the senator ."}
{"question": "The doctors that the tourist mentioned stopped the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary stopped the doctors ."}
{"question": "The president saw the manager that admired the actors .", "answer": "The manager saw the president ."}
{"question": "The actor contacted the athlete who called the tourists .", "answer": "The athlete contacted the the tourists ."}
{"question": "The senators who the authors recommended mentioned the banker .", "answer": "The authors mentioned the senators ."}
{"question": "The secretaries who the actors encouraged stopped the student .", "answer": "The actors stopped the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The author saw the scientists that the artist helped .", "answer": "The scientists saw the artist ."}
{"question": "The president that the senators encouraged thanked the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists thanked the president ."}
{"question": "The senator stopped the secretary who the scientists believed .", "answer": "The secretary stopped the scientists ."}
{"question": "The manager introduced the senators who the artists mentioned .", "answer": "The senators introduced the manager ."}
{"question": "The scientists that the professor stopped called the senators .", "answer": "The senators called the professor ."}
{"question": "The judges that the professors recommended avoided the student .", "answer": "The professors avoided the judges ."}
{"question": "The authors who saw the actors thanked the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers thanked the actors ."}
{"question": "The tourists that the doctor recommended stopped the authors .", "answer": "The doctor stopped the tourists ."}
{"question": "The banker helped the athlete that the lawyer supported .", "answer": "The athlete helped the banker ."}
{"question": "The secretary mentioned the doctor that the artist introduced .", "answer": "The artist mentioned the secretary ."}
{"question": "The scientist who the lawyer helped avoided the professors .", "answer": "The lawyer avoided the scientist ."}
{"question": "The student that thanked the lawyer mentioned the doctor .", "answer": "The lawyer mentioned the student ."}
{"question": "The student recognized the secretary that thanked the judges .", "answer": "The secretary recognized the student ."}
{"question": "The presidents believed the student who thanked the secretaries .", "answer": "The student believed the the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The banker who the actor recommended introduced the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist introduced the banker ."}
{"question": "The senator who the tourist saw admired the actors .", "answer": "The tourist admired the senator ."}
{"question": "The author who saw the manager contacted the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries contacted the manager ."}
{"question": "The tourist helped the scientists who the professor advised .", "answer": "The professor helped the tourist ."}
{"question": "The student called the managers that the bankers encouraged .", "answer": "The managers called the bankers ."}
{"question": "The tourists avoided the bankers who thanked the artist .", "answer": "The bankers avoided the the artist ."}
{"question": "The author encouraged the professor that supported the senators .", "answer": "The professor encouraged the the senators ."}
{"question": "The secretary thanked the professors that the lawyer contacted .", "answer": "The professors thanked the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The athletes supported the bankers that mentioned the professor .", "answer": "The professor supported the athletes ."}
{"question": "The manager recognized the author who thanked the professors .", "answer": "The author recognized the the professors ."}
{"question": "The bankers who helped the doctors believed the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer believed the doctors ."}
{"question": "The president who the banker recommended helped the professors .", "answer": "The professors helped the banker ."}
{"question": "The judge that the scientists supported contacted the authors .", "answer": "The scientists contacted the judge ."}
{"question": "The actor that the doctors avoided introduced the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer introduced the actor ."}
{"question": "The athlete introduced the senators that recommended the lawyers .", "answer": "The senators introduced the athlete ."}
{"question": "The judge helped the actor that believed the doctor .", "answer": "The actor helped the the doctor ."}
{"question": "The scientists who called the doctors thanked the actor .", "answer": "The actor thanked the doctors ."}
{"question": "The professors that the tourists contacted advised the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer advised the tourists ."}
{"question": "The scientists that saw the student encouraged the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers encouraged the scientists ."}
{"question": "The judge that thanked the tourist helped the professor .", "answer": "The professor helped the tourist ."}
{"question": "The artist that the athletes believed helped the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists helped the athletes ."}
{"question": "The bankers that the judge helped recognized the secretaries .", "answer": "The judge recognized the bankers ."}
{"question": "The manager supported the student who called the scientists .", "answer": "The student supported the manager ."}
{"question": "The banker called the athlete who advised the artists .", "answer": "The artists called the banker ."}
{"question": "The president helped the actor that mentioned the professor .", "answer": "The actor helped the president ."}
{"question": "The president who the judges stopped advised the authors .", "answer": "The judges advised the president ."}
{"question": "The artists that the professors helped advised the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers advised the professors ."}
{"question": "The managers that the secretary recognized advised the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists advised the secretary ."}
{"question": "The lawyers that the managers saw believed the judges .", "answer": "The judges believed the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The doctor that the artist recognized saw the judges .", "answer": "The judges saw the doctor ."}
{"question": "The lawyers mentioned the students that the judge introduced .", "answer": "The students mentioned the judge ."}
{"question": "The tourist that the professors stopped mentioned the judges .", "answer": "The professors mentioned the tourist ."}
{"question": "The manager who the senators called avoided the judge .", "answer": "The senators avoided the manager ."}
{"question": "The lawyers recognized the secretaries who introduced the actor .", "answer": "The actor recognized the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The professors that the artists contacted saw the students .", "answer": "The artists saw the professors ."}
{"question": "The author contacted the students who recommended the professors .", "answer": "The students contacted the author ."}
{"question": "The scientists supported the bankers that believed the authors .", "answer": "The bankers supported the the authors ."}
{"question": "The judge that recommended the presidents encouraged the senator .", "answer": "The senator encouraged the judge ."}
{"question": "The lawyer saw the students who stopped the scientists .", "answer": "The students saw the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The professor who the scientist mentioned avoided the banker .", "answer": "The banker avoided the scientist ."}
{"question": "The tourists saw the doctor who recognized the artists .", "answer": "The artists saw the tourists ."}
{"question": "The athlete who stopped the scientists mentioned the judges .", "answer": "The scientists mentioned the athlete ."}
{"question": "The athletes who introduced the lawyer supported the scientist .", "answer": "The lawyer supported the athletes ."}
{"question": "The bankers that the authors supported stopped the tourist .", "answer": "The authors stopped the bankers ."}
{"question": "The athletes recommended the judge that called the manager .", "answer": "The judge recommended the athletes ."}
{"question": "The author who mentioned the students introduced the lawyer .", "answer": "The students introduced the author ."}
{"question": "The lawyers admired the doctor that the manager encouraged .", "answer": "The doctor admired the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The doctor recognized the artists who the managers called .", "answer": "The artists recognized the doctor ."}
{"question": "The manager who encouraged the secretary called the professors .", "answer": "The professors called the secretary ."}
{"question": "The secretaries that recommended the judges encouraged the professor .", "answer": "The judges encouraged the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The actor advised the students who thanked the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents advised the actor ."}
{"question": "The secretaries contacted the doctor who the athletes advised .", "answer": "The doctor contacted the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The lawyers who mentioned the students supported the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist supported the students ."}
{"question": "The athletes that the judges avoided thanked the senator .", "answer": "The senator thanked the judges ."}
{"question": "The judges believed the senator who saw the students .", "answer": "The senator believed the judges ."}
{"question": "The senator contacted the president that the manager saw .", "answer": "The president contacted the senator ."}
{"question": "The president recognized the tourists who the secretary helped .", "answer": "The tourists recognized the president ."}
{"question": "The student encouraged the secretaries that the lawyer recommended .", "answer": "The secretaries encouraged the student ."}
{"question": "The bankers who admired the authors supported the student .", "answer": "The student supported the authors ."}
{"question": "The students who contacted the artists supported the president .", "answer": "The president supported the students ."}
{"question": "The author contacted the scientist that advised the senator .", "answer": "The scientist contacted the author ."}
{"question": "The artist saw the manager that thanked the actors .", "answer": "The manager saw the the actors ."}
{"question": "The judges recommended the bankers who the actors encouraged .", "answer": "The bankers recommended the actors ."}
{"question": "The senator recognized the president that the athlete called .", "answer": "The president recognized the senator ."}
{"question": "The professors encouraged the secretary who the scientist advised .", "answer": "The scientist encouraged the professors ."}
{"question": "The artist that the president saw supported the professors .", "answer": "The president supported the artist ."}
{"question": "The president saw the judge that believed the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists saw the president ."}
{"question": "The tourists that the scientist admired called the manager .", "answer": "The manager called the scientist ."}
{"question": "The senators that the professors contacted encouraged the students .", "answer": "The students encouraged the professors ."}
{"question": "The secretaries mentioned the professors who encouraged the lawyers .", "answer": "The professors mentioned the the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The judge that recognized the bankers mentioned the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers mentioned the bankers ."}
{"question": "The professor who the senator supported called the managers .", "answer": "The managers called the senator ."}
{"question": "The students helped the secretaries who admired the managers .", "answer": "The managers helped the students ."}
{"question": "The scientists admired the manager who the senator mentioned .", "answer": "The manager admired the senator ."}
{"question": "The lawyer that believed the presidents thanked the actors .", "answer": "The actors thanked the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The senators encouraged the tourist who the professor thanked .", "answer": "The professor encouraged the senators ."}
{"question": "The doctors advised the authors who the judges recognized .", "answer": "The authors advised the doctors ."}
{"question": "The artists stopped the actors that the bankers called .", "answer": "The actors stopped the bankers ."}
{"question": "The banker introduced the actors who the author stopped .", "answer": "The actors introduced the author ."}
{"question": "The manager thanked the doctors who the artist recognized .", "answer": "The artist thanked the manager ."}
{"question": "The athletes who introduced the secretary mentioned the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers mentioned the athletes ."}
{"question": "The students that the bankers believed avoided the senators .", "answer": "The senators avoided the bankers ."}
{"question": "The actors that the artist encouraged contacted the author .", "answer": "The author contacted the actors ."}
{"question": "The manager recognized the students that the scientists encouraged .", "answer": "The scientists recognized the manager ."}
{"question": "The actors admired the doctors who the lawyers recognized .", "answer": "The doctors admired the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The judges recommended the banker who stopped the president .", "answer": "The president recommended the judges ."}
{"question": "The secretaries thanked the senator that introduced the professors .", "answer": "The professors thanked the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The student who the professor avoided recommended the judges .", "answer": "The professor recommended the student ."}
{"question": "The professor who introduced the secretaries helped the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer helped the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The judge who the actors contacted called the doctors .", "answer": "The actors called the judge ."}
{"question": "The professors that the student believed recognized the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries recognized the student ."}
{"question": "The president encouraged the athletes that the professor called .", "answer": "The athletes encouraged the professor ."}
{"question": "The lawyers who the scientists encouraged introduced the senators .", "answer": "The senators introduced the scientists ."}
{"question": "The athlete that the students stopped mentioned the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists mentioned the students ."}
{"question": "The judge admired the student who the senators thanked .", "answer": "The senators admired the judge ."}
{"question": "The president stopped the artists who the judges recognized .", "answer": "The artists stopped the president ."}
{"question": "The judges avoided the bankers who saw the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist avoided the judges ."}
{"question": "The managers introduced the president that stopped the author .", "answer": "The president introduced the the author ."}
{"question": "The secretary advised the artist who contacted the presidents .", "answer": "The presidents advised the secretary ."}
{"question": "The athletes who the doctor introduced supported the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries supported the athletes ."}
{"question": "The athlete that the judges thanked helped the secretaries .", "answer": "The judges helped the athlete ."}
{"question": "The scientists who thanked the lawyers encouraged the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists encouraged the scientists ."}
{"question": "The managers advised the professor who called the author .", "answer": "The author advised the managers ."}
{"question": "The senators that the artists recognized contacted the athletes .", "answer": "The artists contacted the senators ."}
{"question": "The artist that admired the actors stopped the authors .", "answer": "The authors stopped the actors ."}
{"question": "The secretary helped the judge that the scientists believed .", "answer": "The judge helped the scientists ."}
{"question": "The professor that the secretaries supported contacted the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers contacted the professor ."}
{"question": "The presidents that the actors supported avoided the doctor .", "answer": "The doctor avoided the presidents ."}
{"question": "The judge that the senator introduced helped the author .", "answer": "The author helped the judge ."}
{"question": "The lawyer that the judges helped called the student .", "answer": "The student called the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The managers avoided the bankers that believed the authors .", "answer": "The bankers avoided the managers ."}
{"question": "The banker that the senator admired saw the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist saw the banker ."}
{"question": "The manager that introduced the actor mentioned the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists mentioned the actor ."}
{"question": "The professor that the lawyers thanked introduced the presidents .", "answer": "The lawyers introduced the professor ."}
{"question": "The managers encouraged the presidents who the professor admired .", "answer": "The professor encouraged the managers ."}
{"question": "The judge saw the professor who mentioned the student .", "answer": "The professor saw the judge ."}
{"question": "The professor who contacted the lawyers stopped the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary stopped the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The actors that the lawyer stopped believed the banker .", "answer": "The banker believed the actors ."}
{"question": "The scientist stopped the student that called the managers .", "answer": "The student stopped the scientist ."}
{"question": "The artists recommended the senator that the scientists saw .", "answer": "The senator recommended the scientists ."}
{"question": "The senators thanked the professors who believed the president .", "answer": "The president thanked the senators ."}
{"question": "The tourists recognized the artist who the authors advised .", "answer": "The artist recognized the tourists ."}
{"question": "The scientist who believed the president advised the secretaries .", "answer": "The secretaries advised the president ."}
{"question": "The presidents thanked the manager that encouraged the judges .", "answer": "The judges thanked the presidents ."}
{"question": "The bankers who contacted the secretaries mentioned the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer mentioned the bankers ."}
{"question": "The actors who the secretaries recognized thanked the tourist .", "answer": "The tourist thanked the actors ."}
{"question": "The authors stopped the athlete who the scientist contacted .", "answer": "The scientist stopped the authors ."}
{"question": "The tourist who advised the scientists recommended the bankers .", "answer": "The scientists recommended the tourist ."}
{"question": "The secretaries supported the student who the authors introduced .", "answer": "The student supported the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The manager who the senator encouraged avoided the actors .", "answer": "The senator avoided the manager ."}
{"question": "The secretary supported the lawyers that the judges helped .", "answer": "The lawyers supported the secretary ."}
{"question": "The students believed the lawyer who saw the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary believed the students ."}
{"question": "The scientists contacted the athlete who the lawyer encouraged .", "answer": "The athlete contacted the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The artists helped the tourists that introduced the author .", "answer": "The tourists helped the the author ."}
{"question": "The tourists that the scientists thanked believed the secretaries .", "answer": "The scientists believed the tourists ."}
{"question": "The actor who admired the secretaries avoided the student .", "answer": "The student avoided the actor ."}
{"question": "The author introduced the actors who the judge contacted .", "answer": "The judge introduced the author ."}
{"question": "The secretaries who the judge stopped recommended the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists recommended the judge ."}
{"question": "The senator recognized the secretary that helped the actor .", "answer": "The secretary recognized the senator ."}
{"question": "The secretaries who the student admired introduced the banker .", "answer": "The student introduced the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The scientist saw the senators who the secretary introduced .", "answer": "The senators saw the secretary ."}
{"question": "The scientists advised the managers who called the senator .", "answer": "The senator advised the scientists ."}
{"question": "The bankers encouraged the president that introduced the lawyer .", "answer": "The president encouraged the bankers ."}
{"question": "The professors avoided the managers who saw the banker .", "answer": "The managers avoided the professors ."}
{"question": "The president contacted the professors that stopped the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors contacted the president ."}
{"question": "The actors that avoided the athletes introduced the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers introduced the actors ."}
{"question": "The artists who encouraged the judge helped the professor .", "answer": "The judge helped the artists ."}
{"question": "The actors advised the senator that admired the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors advised the actors ."}
{"question": "The lawyer who supported the athletes admired the students .", "answer": "The students admired the athletes ."}
{"question": "The artist who advised the tourist helped the senators .", "answer": "The tourist helped the artist ."}
{"question": "The lawyer mentioned the senators who the students admired .", "answer": "The senators mentioned the students ."}
{"question": "The professor who the students advised avoided the artists .", "answer": "The students avoided the professor ."}
{"question": "The artists admired the professor that the senator called .", "answer": "The professor admired the artists ."}
{"question": "The senator who the scientists contacted recommended the actors .", "answer": "The actors recommended the scientists ."}
{"question": "The tourist who the managers avoided recognized the doctors .", "answer": "The doctors recognized the managers ."}
{"question": "The artists called the professors that the judge mentioned .", "answer": "The professors called the judge ."}
{"question": "The senators who the president saw avoided the bankers .", "answer": "The president avoided the senators ."}
{"question": "The senator contacted the lawyer who introduced the bankers .", "answer": "The bankers contacted the senator ."}
{"question": "The artists who the scientist admired saw the athlete .", "answer": "The scientist saw the artists ."}
{"question": "The author contacted the actors who believed the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers contacted the author ."}
{"question": "The scientist mentioned the actors who called the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists mentioned the scientist ."}
{"question": "The doctors introduced the judge that the secretaries called .", "answer": "The judge introduced the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The tourist that the secretaries recommended believed the banker .", "answer": "The secretaries believed the tourist ."}
{"question": "The tourists believed the senator who the banker recommended .", "answer": "The banker believed the tourists ."}
{"question": "The banker supported the tourists who the president recommended .", "answer": "The tourists supported the banker ."}
{"question": "The tourist introduced the secretaries who the athlete believed .", "answer": "The secretaries introduced the athlete ."}
{"question": "The professors who the student called advised the athletes .", "answer": "The student advised the professors ."}
{"question": "The student that the manager saw helped the lawyer .", "answer": "The lawyer helped the manager ."}
{"question": "The scientist who saw the doctors contacted the managers .", "answer": "The managers contacted the doctors ."}
{"question": "The scientist who the judge introduced advised the actors .", "answer": "The actors advised the scientist ."}
{"question": "The senator stopped the athlete that the judge called .", "answer": "The judge stopped the senator ."}
{"question": "The lawyers that the managers mentioned avoided the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists avoided the lawyers ."}
{"question": "The tourist that stopped the student believed the actors .", "answer": "The actors believed the tourist ."}
{"question": "The tourists recommended the judges who saw the banker .", "answer": "The judges recommended the the banker ."}
{"question": "The tourists who advised the banker introduced the senator .", "answer": "The senator introduced the banker ."}
{"question": "The senator recommended the lawyer who the doctor helped .", "answer": "The lawyer recommended the senator ."}
{"question": "The athletes stopped the judge who the scientist mentioned .", "answer": "The judge stopped the scientist ."}
{"question": "The secretaries encouraged the artist that thanked the professor .", "answer": "The professor encouraged the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The artists thanked the athlete that the tourists recommended .", "answer": "The tourists thanked the artists ."}
{"question": "The banker stopped the athletes that the actor called .", "answer": "The athletes stopped the banker ."}
{"question": "The lawyer that the athlete called thanked the professor .", "answer": "The athlete thanked the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The judge who recognized the artist recommended the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary recommended the judge ."}
{"question": "The judges stopped the banker that the author introduced .", "answer": "The banker stopped the author ."}
{"question": "The lawyer that called the student introduced the manager .", "answer": "The manager introduced the student ."}
{"question": "The president who believed the student contacted the actors .", "answer": "The actors contacted the student ."}
{"question": "The bankers that admired the secretary thanked the student .", "answer": "The secretary thanked the bankers ."}
{"question": "The presidents who the scientist thanked mentioned the judges .", "answer": "The scientist mentioned the presidents ."}
{"question": "The secretary who the athlete contacted helped the scientist .", "answer": "The scientist helped the athlete ."}
{"question": "The actor who recognized the scientist saw the judge .", "answer": "The judge saw the scientist ."}
{"question": "The actors contacted the senators that believed the presidents .", "answer": "The senators contacted the the presidents ."}
{"question": "The students recommended the president who the tourist mentioned .", "answer": "The president recommended the tourist ."}
{"question": "The doctor recognized the lawyer who the actor thanked .", "answer": "The lawyer recognized the doctor ."}
{"question": "The senator recommended the doctors that admired the author .", "answer": "The doctors recommended the the author ."}
{"question": "The tourists that the judges mentioned encouraged the banker .", "answer": "The banker encouraged the judges ."}
{"question": "The scientist helped the students that advised the doctor .", "answer": "The students helped the scientist ."}
{"question": "The student introduced the artists who saw the doctors .", "answer": "The artists introduced the the doctors ."}
{"question": "The author admired the judge that avoided the professor .", "answer": "The judge admired the the professor ."}
{"question": "The manager who the artist introduced called the student .", "answer": "The student called the artist ."}
{"question": "The professor encouraged the senators that the actors helped .", "answer": "The senators encouraged the actors ."}
{"question": "The doctors that stopped the scientist supported the manager .", "answer": "The scientist supported the doctors ."}
{"question": "The tourists recommended the artists who mentioned the athlete .", "answer": "The artists recommended the tourists ."}
{"question": "The secretary that the actors recognized believed the professor .", "answer": "The professor believed the actors ."}
{"question": "The students that the professor recommended advised the lawyers .", "answer": "The professor advised the students ."}
{"question": "The tourist that recognized the judges helped the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers helped the tourist ."}
{"question": "The actor who introduced the secretaries recognized the athletes .", "answer": "The athletes recognized the actor ."}
{"question": "The actors who called the doctors thanked the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete thanked the actors ."}
{"question": "The senator that the professors advised believed the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers believed the senator ."}
{"question": "The athletes who the judges recognized avoided the secretary .", "answer": "The secretary avoided the judges ."}
{"question": "The student admired the presidents who introduced the actor .", "answer": "The presidents admired the the actor ."}
{"question": "The judge who the doctors supported called the lawyer .", "answer": "The doctors called the judge ."}
{"question": "The judges who the actor helped recommended the scientists .", "answer": "The scientists recommended the actor ."}
{"question": "The tourists that saw the judges recommended the student .", "answer": "The student recommended the judges ."}
{"question": "The banker contacted the actors who the judges stopped .", "answer": "The actors contacted the banker ."}
{"question": "The athlete contacted the judge that the actor thanked .", "answer": "The judge contacted the actor ."}
{"question": "The scientist supported the tourist that mentioned the judges .", "answer": "The judges supported the scientist ."}
{"question": "The president that the banker advised encouraged the tourist .", "answer": "The banker encouraged the president ."}
{"question": "The secretary recognized the author that the tourist advised .", "answer": "The tourist recognized the secretary ."}
{"question": "The managers who encouraged the athletes thanked the senator .", "answer": "The senator thanked the managers ."}
{"question": "The artists mentioned the tourists who the doctor saw .", "answer": "The tourists mentioned the doctor ."}
{"question": "The lawyer who the manager believed contacted the artists .", "answer": "The manager contacted the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The scientist thanked the secretary that the actors called .", "answer": "The actors thanked the scientist ."}
{"question": "The author that the professor recognized contacted the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete contacted the author ."}
{"question": "The manager that the students contacted admired the judges .", "answer": "The judges admired the students ."}
{"question": "The athlete who recommended the doctors advised the banker .", "answer": "The doctors advised the athlete ."}
{"question": "The judges who thanked the bankers recognized the athlete .", "answer": "The athlete recognized the judges ."}
{"question": "The scientist stopped the athlete who the student supported .", "answer": "The athlete stopped the student ."}
{"question": "The professor called the senator who the athlete recommended .", "answer": "The senator called the professor ."}
{"question": "The tourists who recognized the lawyer thanked the actors .", "answer": "The actors thanked the tourists ."}
{"question": "The managers that the senators helped saw the judge .", "answer": "The senators saw the managers ."}
{"question": "The lawyer that the judge recognized introduced the author .", "answer": "The judge introduced the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The scientist mentioned the secretary that the artist thanked .", "answer": "The secretary mentioned the scientist ."}
{"question": "The presidents stopped the artist who the bankers contacted .", "answer": "The artist stopped the bankers ."}
{"question": "The judges encouraged the actors that helped the doctors .", "answer": "The actors encouraged the judges ."}
{"question": "The artist who saw the actor believed the professor .", "answer": "The professor believed the actor ."}
{"question": "The presidents supported the actors who thanked the senators .", "answer": "The actors supported the the senators ."}
{"question": "The judge avoided the actors that recommended the professors .", "answer": "The professors avoided the judge ."}
{"question": "The lawyer that the bankers helped avoided the artist .", "answer": "The bankers avoided the lawyer ."}
{"question": "The secretary stopped the tourists who believed the managers .", "answer": "The tourists stopped the secretary ."}
{"question": "The artist that the actor stopped believed the secretaries .", "answer": "The actor believed the artist ."}
{"question": "The doctors that introduced the manager mentioned the author .", "answer": "The author mentioned the doctors ."}
{"question": "The presidents who helped the authors saw the senator .", "answer": "The senator saw the presidents ."}
{"question": "The doctor who believed the tourist recommended the lawyers .", "answer": "The lawyers recommended the doctor ."}
{"question": "The tourist that the authors recognized stopped the lawyer .", "answer": "The authors stopped the tourist ."}
{"question": "The student mentioned the doctor that believed the author .", "answer": "The doctor mentioned the student ."}
{"question": "The doctors that the tourist advised contacted the banker .", "answer": "The tourist contacted the doctors ."}
{"question": "The students stopped the judge who the presidents recommended .", "answer": "The presidents stopped the students ."}
{"question": "The secretaries that the presidents avoided admired the athletes .", "answer": "The presidents admired the secretaries ."}
{"question": "The tourist who the doctors thanked encouraged the artists .", "answer": "The doctors encouraged the tourist ."}
{"question": "The doctors encouraged the judge who the scientist advised .", "answer": "The judge encouraged the doctors ."}
{"question": "The professor supported the secretaries that the banker stopped .", "answer": "The banker supported the professor ."}
{"question": "The judges that the senators mentioned avoided the actor .", "answer": "The actor avoided the judges ."}
{"question": "The artist advised the doctors who the students recommended .", "answer": "The students advised the artist ."}
{"question": "The bankers that the author saw stopped the tourists .", "answer": "The tourists stopped the author ."}
